<root><thread><filename>quigley-d_myfriends_29.txt</filename><name>  What's up?</name><id>EPT001</id><email order="1"><date></date><from>   "Horn, Brian A." &lt;bhorn@trilegiant.com@ENRON</from><to>     Dutch Quigley</to><subject>  What's up?</subject><text><sentence id="EPT001_001">I thought about you when I heard about Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_002">Were you affected?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_003">Give  me a  call and we can meet up sometime.
</sentence><signature> Brian A. Horn, MCSE  Manager of Technical Operations  Trilegiant - Houston  Office       832.486.8265  Fax           832.486.8265  Cell          713.501.6447 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date></date><from> 	Dutch.Quigley@enron.com [mailto:Dutch.Quigley@enron.com]</from><to>	Horn, Brian A.</to><subject>	RE: What's up?</subject><text><sentence id="EPT001_004">Hey Bro,  My wife worked here also and has been let go.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_005">I work for the Natural Gas Trading group that they are trying to sell.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_006">Should know by the end of the week about my job.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_007">I was just talking to Kevin Crawford about you 2 weeks ago when we were in Vegas.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_008">Good to know that you are still out there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_009">How are you doing these days ?
</sentence><signature>Dutch </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 3 Dec 2001 15:18:18 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- "Horn, Brian A." &lt;bhorn@trilegiant.com@ENRON</from><to>X- Quigley, Dutch &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DQUIGLE</to><subject> RE: What's up?</subject><text><sentence id="EPT001_010">Doing alright.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_011">Kendal is working downtown for a Management Consulting firm.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_012">I'm still working for the same marketing, where I am head of the IT division.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_013">We bought a house in Memorial last year, and are still in the process of renovating it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_014">It didn't need a lot, but we are taking our time getting the way we want it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_015">When I say "we" I mean Kendal.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_016">I learned that my opinion didn't matter after a few weeks of buying the place.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_017">:)  I saw Dave Peterson a while back.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_018">We talked about having a Sammy get together this spring.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_019">Maybe a long weekend at Padre or Cancun.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_020">I get great Travel benefits and can get condos at resorts for $200/ wk.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_021">I might also be able to get enough free airline tickets to take care of you and Howard (the three musketeers).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_022">Let me know if you would be interested.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT001_023">Let me know you have some free time after the holidays and we can hook up.
</sentence><signature>Brian A. Horn, MCSE Manager of Technical Operations Trilegiant - Houston Office       832.486.8265 Fax           832.486.8265 Cell          713.501.6447 </signature></text></email></thread></root>
