<root><thread><filename>martin_t_inbox_327.txt</filename><name> Thursday's match</name><id>EPT004</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 9 Apr 2002 18:42:46 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Alan Kaniss [mailto:alan@nnu.com]</from><to> Allen J. Michel (E-mail); Redmond, Brian; Buddy Ellisor (E-mail);</to><subject> Thursday's match</subject><text><sentence id="EPT004_001">We play the dreaded team from Ponderosa on Thursday at home.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_002">They have won only one point to our 2.5 so far this year.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_003">We will have three courts but I believe they only have 5 players so I am not sure how quickly we will finish.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_004">As a reminder, tomorrow night is the first night long sleeves are allowed in league play, so plan accordingly.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_005">Last week Allen and I were the only ones who showed up at Westador for the make up game.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_006">While it had been officially cancelled Allen had purchased the shrimp that Ken has now required.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_007">Because it could not be stored, he and I were forced to eat several pounds and wash it down with imported beer.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_008">Let this be a lesson for all, Thursday night is our night out, rain or shine.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_009">On a rather humorous note, you should have heard Allen's explanation to the Harris County deputy who wanted to know what two guys in shorts were doing in the front seat of a Black Lexus, in a pitch black parking lot.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_010">Finally, in a further attempt to get all our members involved each week, we have asked Carl to act as our official "coin man."
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_011">Carl has studied at the prestigious "Denver Institute of Coin &amp; Stamp Valuation" and is licensed to provide expert analysis of your coin and stamp collections.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_012">Consequently, in an effort to keep him off of the tennis courts, Ken has asked that if you have any old coins, bring them with you each week and Carl will pour over them and give you a professional estimate of their value by the end of the evening.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_013">For those of you going on the cruise he has two evening seminars scheduled to discuss the benefits of owning coins issued from the Denver mint between the years 1956-72.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_014">I understand from Carl that the presentation is spellbinding.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_015">This is just another example of the benefits of being a member in good standing of the Northgate 2, C level, tennis team.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_016">One last note of interest, Ken has already assigned all the good lines for this match to his close buddies.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_017">If you do not know what line you are playing when you read this message, that should tell you about your relationship with our new leader.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_018">Your humble, but not bitter, ex-leader, 
</sentence><signature>Alan C. Kaniss 281-397-7530 (Direct) 281-507-9138 (Cell) </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Tue, 9 Apr 2002 18:42:46 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Redmond, Brian [mailto:Brian.Redmond@ENRON.com]</from><to> Alan Kaniss</to><subject> RE: Thursday's match</subject><text><sentence id="EPT004_019">Alan:  I'm at the hollowed halls of Harvard Bus.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_020">School trying to recuruit a few more good men/women to become Enronites and will not make it back in time for the game.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_021">Seems like when I'm in town it rains and when I'm not it shines - maybe someone is trying to tell me something.
</sentence><signature>Good Luck, Brian </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Tue, 9 Apr 2002 18:42:46 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Alan Kaniss [mailto:alan@nnu.com]</from><to> Redmond, Brian</to><subject> RE: Thursday's match</subject><text><sentence id="EPT004_022">Thanks for the note.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_023">We'll try and survive until your return.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_024">You would have liked these guys, they are truly our level of competition so it should be fun.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_025">Have a safe trip back.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_026">PS- Jason has gone to work on the trading floor for someone named Fletch ?. 
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_027">Do I assume he is part of your group?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT004_028">If so, I want to thank you and Tom if your fingerprints are on this move.
</sentence><signature>Alan </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 22 Oct 2001 12:16:51 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Redmond, Brian &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=BREDMON</from><to>X- Martin, Thomas A. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Tmartin</to><subject> FW: Thursday's match</subject><text><sentence id="EPT004_029">FYI
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
