<root><thread><filename>quigley-d_myfriends_87.txt</filename><name>  Cakes</name><id>EPT008</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 10 Oct 2000 03:00:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>   moshuffle@hotmail.com@ENRON</from><to>     Quigley, Dutch</to><subject>  Cakes</subject><text><sentence id="EPT008_001">Here's a few of the cakes that we make at the bakery.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_002">I'm hoping to  document the rest of the cakes, petit fours, breads, and morning  pastries that we do over the next few days.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 12:23:13 -0600</date><from> Dutch.Quigley@enron.com</from><to> moshuffle@hotmail.com</to><subject> RE: Cakes</subject><text><sentence id="EPT008_003">Mojo,  that is sweet , pardon the pun those cakes look great , what is in the casino cake ? it looks pretty cool  
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_004">How are things going for you ?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_005">Have you settled into a groove yet ?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_006">This past weekend was great for me.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_007">I spent the entire weekend with Kay , we had dinner with my parents on sat.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_008">Night and just hung out the entire weekend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_009">I have had a very different out look on life lately and it has been working well for me.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_010">I have started to ask alot more questions instead of always assuming the answer.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_011">It has been working well for me.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_012">Hope all is good with you.
</sentence><signature>Laters  dq </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 11:20:07 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- "Monique Sanchez" &lt;moshuffle@hotmail.com@ENRON</from><to>X- Quigley, Dutch &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DQUIGLE</to><subject> RE: Cakes</subject><text><sentence id="EPT008_013">Yo papa,  The casino cake is basically a rasberry lovers cake...the decorative rings are a thin layer of biscuit (cake) with raspberry jam on it..then it is rolled up and sliced thin to get those little circular designs.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_014">You line a pan with those rings, then fill the pan partially with bavarian creme (vanilla flavored cream), a layer of rasperry, then more cream, then a layer of sponge cake....it is interesting...my top pic is our chocolate pistachio and the cheesecake which needs to be added to the album.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_015">I am glad to hear that you had a nice weekend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_016">I'm starting to realize that its not enough to want things to work out a certain way.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_017">Intentions are good but actions are critical.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_018">Things just don't happen magically on their own.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_019">Heard natty puked today, hope you were on the right side of that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT008_020">I'll talk to you later.
</sentence><signature>Mo </signature></text></email></thread></root>
