<root><thread><filename>scott-s_personal_42.txt</filename><name>  austin</name><id>EPT034</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 6 Aug 2001 13:51:16 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Paul Thomas &lt;paul_jonathan_thomas@yahoo.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-Paul+20Thomas+20+3Cpaul+5Fjonathan+5Fthomas+40yahoo+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>   "'susan.scott@enron.com'" &lt;susan.scott@enron.com</to><subject>  austin</subject><text><sentence id="EPT034_001">OK! Since our last attempt to go to Austin was foiled by a bout of stomach virus, we will go THIS weekend for much needed wig control!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_002">Might you be available for a visit ?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_003">Just thought I'd clue you in since you haven't seen bug for a while!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_004">I picked up her portraits today at lunch and they look good!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_005">If we meet in Austin this weekend I will hand deliver, otherwise I'll mail or FedEx.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_006">What address would you prefer, home or office?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_007">Let me know!
</sentence><signature>Karin </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 6 Aug 2001 13:51:16 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Susan.Scott@enron.com [mailto:Susan.Scott@enron.com]</from><to> Shelton, Karin</to><subject> Re: Susan's busy week</subject><text><sentence id="EPT034_008">Hi! Sorry to hear about the stomach virus and I hope you are feeling much better.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_009">Just back from Cali.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_010">It was a fun trip!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_011">I'm in need of a Bug fix, especially after comparing niece/nephew notes with (and bragging a lot to) Sue, Edd and Craig over the weekend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_012">Unfortunately, I have to stay in Houston this weekend for a wedding.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_013">Was contemplating visiting the weekend of Nov. 11 but you know that's totally D.E.'s call.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_014">If you mail photos, I'd suggest sending to me at my office, c/o Enron Transportation Services, 1400 Smith St., Room 4788 (very important), Houston 77002.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_015">That way they will not get mangled or wet.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_016">Did you dress the little one up for Halloween?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_017">Have a good day!
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 1 Nov 2000 03:11:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- "Shelton, Karin" &lt;kss@overlandpartners.com</from><to>X- "'Susan.Scott@enron.com'" &lt;Susan.Scott@enron.com</to><subject> RE: Susan's busy week</subject><text><sentence id="EPT034_018">Bug had a busy Halloween at school- Big kids dressed up trick or treated at all the classrooms and bug was the only baby still awake during this time so they put her in a high chair to watch all of the action.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_019">She fell asleep on the short ride home which she never does.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_020">We bought her an outifit to wear at Old Navy that's not really a "costume".
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_021">It is an orange one piece thing with these cute smiling spiders on it that says "silly spiders".
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_022">It was a little boyish, but the pumpkin motif suit was on white t-shirt material and I knew it would be totally stained by the end of the day.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_023">The orange hid those pesky carrots and peaches!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_024">We took pictures of her holding on to the gourd jack-o-lantern yesterday morning.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_025">I think she enjoyed watching the kids come to our door for candy, but she really didn't like the doorbell much at all.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_026">The "Hamlets" slummed it and left their million dollar house area of Alamo Heights to come trick or treat on the old street.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_027">They brought new baby whose name sounds like Frayton - not sure how to spell - but it was fun to see them again.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT034_028">Well, we will hook up another weekend but in the meantime I will send portraits and hopefully some other pics your way.
</sentence><signature>Karin </signature></text></email></thread></root>
