<root><thread><filename>scholtes-d_outbox_personal_18.txt</filename><name> FW: 650 11th update Nov 15 morning</name><id>EPT021</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 11 Dec 2001 14:21:37 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Will, Lisa [mailto:Lisa.Will@powerex.com]</from><to> 'Diana Scholtes'</to><subject> FW: 650 11th update Nov 15 morning</subject><text><sentence id="EPT021_001">Hi Diana...haven't spoken to you in awhile so thought I'd drop you a  note.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_002">Hope all is well amongst this crazy market and confusing time.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_003">I assume you are in your new house and wondered how you are enjoying it  as I  can't really imagine EVER moving in.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_004">I am sure it will happen one day!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_005">Below is a picture Mark took yesterday (just proof that it is really  moving  ahead!) and thought I'd forward to you...
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_006">perhaps you could give me your  opinion, based on it's current stage of construction, how much longer I  might be at my in-laws!?!?!?!?
</sentence><signature> Take care!  Lisa</signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Tue, 11 Dec 2001 14:21:37 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Scholtes, Diana[SMTP:Diana.Scholtes@enron.com]</from><to> 	lisa.will@BCHydro.bc.ca</to><subject> 	RE: 650 11th update Nov 15 morning</subject><text><sentence id="EPT021_007">Hi!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_008">It has been a long time!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_009">As you know things here are very shaky.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_010">I can't believe the big E has crumbled!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_011">Who would have ever guessed!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_012">Everyone is completely disappointed and mostly pissed off.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_013">I'll have to  give you the inside scoop sometime when we get together!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_014">And we need  to!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_015">I'll be traveling around making my rounds to find out what's in the  market place soon.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_016">So, hopefully I'll get a chance to see you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_017">Any  chance of you and Mark coming down?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_018">We have plenty of room for the two  of you; you're always welcome.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_019">I love your house!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_020">Thanks for sending  the picture.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_021">Its so exciting but its also a lot of work!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_022">I'm glad I'm  done!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_023">It's nice to be in the house, but also funny all the work and  effort you put in and how exciting it is all those months while you're  in the process....all to be completely indifferent with it afterwards!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_024">Its very strange, but what to do? Natalie, I can't believe is 3! And a  very terrible 3. 
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_025">My hands are full!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_026">I'm contemplating of putting her  in ski school this winter.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_027">She quite the daring child, so I think  she'll enjoy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_028">Ask Mark for me if this is too young.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_029">She won't think  so, its mostly my fear.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_030">=) You'll get a kick of the pictures I've  attached.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_031">One of them is my depiction a young Penny Lane.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_032">Hopefully you  saw Almost Famous to understand my analogy!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_033">You'll also notice the  Beagle that Bill bought for Natalie.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_034">HAHA!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_035">His name is Presley.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_036">She's  absolutely in love with him.
</sentence><signature> Keep in touch!  Diana   </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Fri, 16 Nov 2001 15:23:48 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Will, Lisa &lt;Lisa.Will@powerex.com</from><to>X- Scholtes, Diana &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DSCHOLT</to><subject> RE: 650 11th update Nov 15 morning</subject><text><sentence id="EPT021_037">THanks for the pics!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_038">They're great...one thing, I can not believe you got another dog!!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_039">That story still kills me!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_040">Glad to hear your house has worked out so nicely...
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_041">I trust that you've sold your other house and all is good.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_042">I would love to get together with you anytime soon...
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_043">if you are not going to be around here in the near future, I will come there and see you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_044">I've not been to your trade floor for years now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_045">Just let me know when you thought you might be around here and if not, I'll make arrangements to go down there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_046">I hope that you're not in a panic yet...you just never know until the full shakeout hapens what will take place.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_047">I have forwarded you below a couple of pics of the dogs (my parents-in-law's dog and my dog, Oakley) Oakley is the chocolate one.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT021_048">I will be sure to keep in touch with you and pls do the same.
</sentence><signature>Cheers! &lt;&lt;17080007.jpg  &lt;&lt;17080009.jpg Lisa </signature></text></email></thread></root>
