<root><thread><filename>scott-s_inbox_49.txt</filename><name></name><id>EPT037</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 18 Oct 2000 10:03:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>   "Emily Hillegeist" &lt;ehillegeist@hotmail.com@ENRON</from><to>     sscott5@enron.com</to><subject></subject><text><sentence id="EPT037_001">glad the trip was so smashing.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_002">am pouting rt now b/c have to finish  next  law paper by tues- while evryone else travels.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_003">liz and kerrie are in  stockholm, mom and dad in colorado...me stuck, w/ pulled groin muscle,  and  am hobbling around like a circus freak.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_004">sounds like kates is off to  dallas.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_005">think she's definitely ready for a chge of scenery.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_006">and she's waited  long  enough! would seattle be a potential destination?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_007">could you do your  same  job there?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_008">i guess so.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_009">could be really fab- i'm up for anyone from the  grp  offering alternative vacation destinations.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_010">everyone always raves about  seattle- isn't that were the begining of the ashley judd film double  jeopardy takes place?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_011">gorgeous!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_012">plus, if it has austin-like qualities,  how  could you go wrong?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_013">like kates, you may be in need of a chge of  scenery-  even if it were just for a yr or so.....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_014">what will prob happen is kates  will  move to dallas, you'll move to seattle, and the next day i'll be offered  curator position or dream art law job in houston starting at about $  100,000+......
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_015">then it will be me and the marrieds alone, stuck in  houston!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_016">NB kitchen has been totally renovated- mom said it looks totally  different,  but can't really imagine it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_017">may be meeting brit and arden in NB sept  15-  save the date just in case it becomes a big party..... ok, am off.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_018">rented  the house of mirth...again.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_019">i really liked it for some reason....ok,  chat  soon- 
</sentence><signature> e </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 30 Jul 2001 09:49:13 -0500</date><from> Susan.M.Scott@enron.com</from><to> ehillegeist@hotmail.com</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT037_020">Good luck with the paper...
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_021">I know how inspired you get when deadlines start approaching, so I'm sure it'll be fabulous.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_022">Sorry about the pulled muscle.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_023">What exactly does that do to the marathon plans?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_024">Will you be able to compete still, or are you just going to hit all the wine stops now?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_025">I think you're right about Katy's move to Dallas.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_026">I have a feeling she's actually going to really like being there and working.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_027">I pretty sure the folks are still helping out with living expenses, etc. so she won't have to make too big of an adjustment right off the bat.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_028">As for me, Seattle could definitely be a destination but it would require a job change.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_029">Enron doesn't have any offices up there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_030">The closest office is Portland and for obvious and now unavoidable reasons I don't see a move there any time soon.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_031">You are right about not being able to go wrong with a place possessing Austin-like qualities...they are highly desirable.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_032">I will most certainly try to keep the September date open...it would be great to see Britney and Arden.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_033">We had Susan E.'s bachelorette party Saturday night (plus a bridal shower earlier that day).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_034">Lisa hosted Laura White's at the apartment the same night.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_035">I got to see and visit with Jenny Kenair (sp?), Janie Pitman, Rachel Pack among others.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_036">Very interesting.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_037">The two bachelorette parties met up at Black Swan for late night dancing.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_038">Lis was in rare form.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_039">I knew it was bad when she ran up and started hugging me....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_040">I think she almost crushed Susan and Kelly.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_041">Anyway, it was actually pretty fun and I've decided I really like Susan's sister Betsy...good sense of humor and not at all be-boppy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_042">I did manage to trick her into doing the V-I-C-T-O-R-Y cheer at Black Swan though.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_043">I thought it was pretty darn funny myself...she was mortified when she realized I'd got her to do a cheer.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_044">Once again...best of luck banging out your opus.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_045">Talk to you soon.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_046">If you're looking to procrastinate a little this evening you can give me a buzz on my cell.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_047">I'd try calling 5 pm or after.
</sentence><signature>Sue </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 30 Jul 2001 09:05:30 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- "Emily Hillegeist" &lt;ehillegeist@hotmail.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-+22Emily+20Hillegeist+22+20+3Cehillegeist+40hotmail+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Scott, Susan M. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SSCOTT5</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT037_048">from what i hear, her high rise appt is pretty much the reason for the season, so to speak.....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_049">although she did sound a bit inspired about the possibility of doing some buying work in the silver dept, which would involve trips to the orient.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_050">all this is second hand of course- was severly hung over when niki talked to her on sun after the party.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_051">i was a shameful girl sat night- although i inflicted damage on no one but myself.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_052">had mini pms-induced temper tantrum/self-pity party at the bar w/ niki, her friend, nima and wenus, then wandered off to catch the night bus at trafalger square....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_053">needless to say, was so drunk i passed out on the bus, and slept waaaaaaay past my stop, ending up somewhere in acton- the equiv of living in lakewood, then waking up in hempstead.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_054">had 3 pounds to my name, no money on houston acct to pulse $ out, and at 4 am, not too many cabs haunting the gangster area of acton.....was a pitiful scene.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_055">had to bribe a mini cab to drop me off as close to ladbrok grove as 3 pounds would take me, then hobbled home about 3 miles in heels, whiney and drunk.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_056">very sad.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_057">no matter.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_058">am almost done w/ dreaded paper!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_059">well, maybe it is time for susan to explore new territories.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_060">am pretty damn sure there are other alternatives to enron in the seattle area that offer job description close to what you're doing or want to do.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_061">enron is not the only game in town- and shouldn't hold you back from having new experineces or making inspired decisions.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_062">could warrant some research.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_063">keep me posted.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT037_064">back to smae old, same old.....chat soon- will try to call after finish said paper later tonight.
</sentence><signature>e </signature></text></email></thread></root>
