<root><thread><filename>fischer-m_personal_13.txt</filename><name>  Leon Kent and Lloyds</name><id>EPT018</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 29 Nov 2000 04:14:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- BDCash@bth12.med.navy.mil (Cash, Brooks D.)</from><to>   "'Mary Fischer'" &lt;mfischer@enron.com</to><subject>  Leon Kent and Lloyds</subject><text><sentence id="EPT018_001">Hey Mary-- your pal, Leon Kent, called me about Lloyds.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_002">In my clients, I've got four or five Lloyds members.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_003">some took the Equitas settlement, some remain Lloyds names, and some just quit answering the mail.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_004">My basic advice to Leon is -- ignore them, they aren't going to make you the test case for going after assets in Texas.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_005">But, before I give it to him, is there anything new at Lloyds that you are aware of?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_006">What are you doing about it?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_007">Hope all is well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_008">Did you get my answer on the trust issues?
</sentence><signature>David David Donnelly Gainer, Donnelly &amp; Desroches, L.C. Certified Public Accountants Post Oak Office 1177 West Loop South #600 Houston TX 77027 phone 713 621 8090 ext 28 direct line 713 965 5555 fax 713 621 6907 alternate email sgainercpa@aol.com website www.gddcpa.com </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 29 Nov 2000 04:14:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from> mfischer@enron.com [mailto:mfischer@enron.com]</from><to> donnelly@gddcpa.com</to><subject> Re: Leon Kent and Lloyds</subject><text><sentence id="EPT018_009">David,  Thanks for your reply on the trusts.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_010">I've been meaning to e-mail you back for the last week.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_011">It has been on my list of things to do and of course I'm procrastinating.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_012">I even promised my brother John I would get back with you on Monday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_013">Well I didn't fulfill that promise but I'm just one day late.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_014">Leon Kent is still alive!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_015">Tell Leon that I get monthly correspondance from Equitas and that I trash it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_016">They are still trying to get names to rejoin.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_017">There is nothing knew that is happening at Lloyd's except the usual propaganda that is put out by the groups that were formed in hopes of suing Lloyd's.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_018">They tend to send out material saying that Lloyd's can still come after names after they have settled with Equitas.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_019">Back to the trusts - I really was hoping that you/the firm would take over.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_020">When I said that I wouldn't handle the accounting of the trusts because of family difficulties, I was refering to my oldest brother, John, who has a law degree and knows enough to ask questions and he keeps asking questions that I get stressed trying to answer and then we get into an arguement.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_021">I wanted someone who knows what their doing to handle the trusts because he won't ask them any questions and it is worth it to me so I can have peace and quiet.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_022">(George knows John.)
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_023">John had heard good press about you and was very comfortable if you were interested in handling the trusts once Chase Bank is removed as trustee.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_024">Bill who is extremely easy going will go with anything.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_025">I hope that work has slowed down now that the 15th is over and that you've had a chance to catch your breath.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 29 Nov 2000 04:14:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from> mfischer@enron.com [mailto:mfischer@enron.com]</from><to>   "'mfischer@enron.com'" &lt;mfischer@enron.com</to><subject>  RE: Leon Kent and Lloyds</subject><text><sentence id="EPT018_026">Hey Mary--  
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_027">Our informal policy is to not accept executorships/trustee positions, but we do make exceptions.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_028">If you think that I'm not exposing myself to much liability, I'll be glad to do it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_029">Yes Leon is alive.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_030">When he called yesterday, he reminded me twice that he was 83 and at least once asked me who he was talking to.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_031">I was about to call him and tell him not to worry about Lloyds, but another client just called and said "Lloyds is breathing down my neck"  
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_032">The possible Lloyds exposure is one more reason to keep the assets in the trust---  
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_033">Let me know if you want to go forward with the trust-- 
</sentence><signature>David David Donnelly Gainer, Donnelly &amp; Desroches, L.C. Certified Public Accountants Post Oak Office 1177 West Loop South #600 Houston TX 77027 phone 713 621 8090 ext 28 direct line 713 965 5555 fax 713 621 6907 alternate email sgainercpa@aol.com website www.gddcpa.com </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Wed, 29 Nov 2000 04:14:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from> mfischer@enron.com</from><to> donnelly@gddcpa.com</to><subject> RE: Leon Kent and Lloyds</subject><text><sentence id="EPT018_034">David,  I would like to go forward with using you as a trustee.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_035">I don't think that you will be exposing yourself to any liability.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_036">The next question is what will your monthly fee be?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_037">Would you be available to meet with John and hopefully Bill and myself.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_038">John will be in town July 2nd through the 5th.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_039">Would you be available during one of those days?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_040">As soon as I can find it I will mail you a copy of the trust agreement.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_041">Thanks for all the help and should I be worried about Lloyds?
</sentence><signature>Mary </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Wed, 29 Nov 2000 04:14:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from> mfischer@enron.com</from><to>	"'mfischer@enron.com '" &lt;mfischer@enron.com</to><subject>	RE: Leon Kent and Lloyds</subject><text><sentence id="EPT018_042">Mary--  I'm not sure what me fee would be, but once I get a better idea of what is required, I can provide it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_043">I cannot imagine that it would be too much--you know that we try to bill according to the value provided to the client.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_044">Unfortunately, I will be out of town (visiting my new grandson, Luca Pelizzoli Bishop, in Tanzania) from June 29 to July 21.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_045">I would like to meet with all of the beneficiaries as soon as possible, however.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_046">When will John be in town again?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_047">At the very least, let's meet with you and Bill--  Lloyd's--Jeanne Long follows the ALM/ANA information fairly closely.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_048">Evidently, there was a fairly significant court case which a Texas Name lost last week.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_049">I do not know the details, but she is somewhat concerned.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_050">I still cannot imagine that the courts in Texas will allow some foreigner to come here and take assets from honest Texans.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_051">Jeanne tells me that there is a lot of politics involved, that the FBI is interested in pursuing Lloyds on some securities fraud or investment scam charges, but that the British government is trying to intervene.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_052">I've got no idea what it means, but if I were you, I would consider all my decisions with the thought of protection against a bad court outcome as a possibility.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_053">As a practical matter, this means: Keep all trust or estate assets in the trust or estate, minimize your non-exempt assets, and maximize your exempt assets, such as taking any exposed funds and putting them into pension funds or paying off a mortgage on a homestead.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_054">If you would like to come in to discuss asset protection, I would be glad to talk to you -- on a friend basis rather than a charge basis.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT018_055">let me know when you find the trust agreement-- 
</sentence><signature>David </signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Wed, 29 Aug 2001 20:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Mary Fischer</from><to>X- mfischer41 &lt;mfischer41@aol.com</to><subject> RE: Leon Kent and Lloyds</subject><text><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
