<root><thread><filename>shankman-j_personal_16.txt</filename><name> Re:</name><id>EPT016</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 13 Jun 2000 03:16:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Madeleine Todd &lt;madeleinet@earthlink.net</from><to>X- jdasovic@enron.com</to><subject> Re:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT016_001">Happy Birthday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_002">(Imagine a chorus singing).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_003">Hope  you've been well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_004">How's the family?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_005">Details, please.Generally, things  have been status  quo around here--swamped in the office, although I've been on a lot of  dates these last few months.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_006">Surprisingly, I don't  hate them all.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_007">I've  been travelling quite a bit and am ready for a little home life.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_008">(Australia, London, Mexico, various U.S.etc,  although, I'm trying not to go to Nigeria for a big deal we are working on.)
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_009">I'm putting in a pool,  and hopefully, that will help me "vacation at home" a little.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_010">It should  be down in 2 months.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_011">Of course it should have been  done last year, but  I have no time to do anything.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_012">Drop a line when you can....   
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_013">Lots of love and hugs, 
</sentence><signature> Jeff </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 6 Jun 2001 11:10:06 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Adam and Nicole Lesser &lt;furie-lesser@rocketmail.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-Adam+20and+20Nicole+20Lesser+20+3Cfurie-lesser+40rocketmail+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Shankman, Jeffrey A. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JSHANKM</to><subject> Re:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT016_014">Hi Jeff,  Happy Birthday to you too!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_015">I've been meaning to call or write, but the last two weeks have been a little crazy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_016">Our cat had to have surgery 2 weeks ago, last week Maddie was sick all week, and on Sunday she feel off the front steps and got a big black eye (very impressive).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_017">Not too much else is going on.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_018">I'm still working 3 days a week, but will be going up to 4 in the fall.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_019">I feel pretty mixed about it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_020">I'm hoping that I'll actually be less stressed because I'll have more time to get my job done and won't have to do so much work at home.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_021">Of course I don't want to be away from Maddie, but she's pretty happy going to day care, and we'll enjoy the extra income.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_022">We haven't traveled too much.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_023">In October we went to Oregon, March to Baltimore to visit family, and May to Florida.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_024">Sounds like you have been having some great adventures!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_025">Maddie travels pretty well but we're not up for foreign travel yet.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_026">Adam has begun a private practice.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_027">So far lots of referrals but few actual clients.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_028">It takes a while for these things to fall into place.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_029">Maddie is doing well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_030">She wasn't really eating last fall and winter, but she is getting back on track and gaining weight.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_031">She's lots of fun - silly and flirty like her mother.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_032">I'm going to be in big trouble when she goes to Kutz.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_033">I can't remember when I spoke to you last, but we had kind of a difficult fall/winter.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_034">Two friends died, plus a few older relatives.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_035">It's made us very grateful for what we have.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_036">We're hoping that the cluster of bad things is gone now that spring is here!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_037">Well, I'd love to talk to you sometime to hear more about all your dates (I need to live vicariously through you).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_038">I have a great Jewish girl for you here, but I don't know if she would ever move to Houston.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT016_039">Good luck with work stuff, and take good care of yourself.
</sentence><signature>Lots of love, Nicole </signature></text></email></thread></root>
