<root><thread><filename>mckay-j_personal_56.txt</filename><name>	Currency</name><id>EPT019</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 29 Aug 2001 20:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	"Jeffrey R. Pearson"</from><to>	Mckay, Jonathan</to><subject>	Currency</subject><text><sentence id="EPT019_001">Jon, I am unsure if you got my message the other day, but I am  looking  at  doing around 20000 US worth of currency.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_002">The bank last week was  charging me  a couple of hundred points, so anything less would be appreciated.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_003">I  would  like to hold off longer, but my first tuition bill is due Sept 10,  so  I need  the money by then.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_004">If you can't help, I will probably try and cut a deal with my bank  or  a new  bank down here.
</sentence><signature> Thanks!   Jeff </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 29 Aug 2001 20:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Mckay, Jonathan [mailto:Jonathan.McKay@enron.com]</from><to> Jeffrey.R.Pearson@Dartmouth.EDU</to><subject> RE: Currency</subject><text><sentence id="EPT019_005">How's about US$10,000 to get started or do you need US$20,000 right  away?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_006">I'm not sure Enron is going to do the trade with me but I would  be glad to help you out.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_007">Do you just want to mail cheques to each  other  or do something else?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_008">If Enron does the currency trade that I want to  do, I'd be happy to do what every volume you need.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_009">Let me know what you want to do.
</sentence><signature> Jon </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 29 Aug 2001 20:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	"Jeffrey R. Pearson"</from><to>	Mckay, Jonathan</to><subject>	RE: Currency</subject><text><sentence id="EPT019_010">I would love to do closer to 15000, but 10 will definately work.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_011">I  have  about 14000 in tuition bills due in several weeks, and need to definately  convert some money.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_012">Why don't you choose a rate, and e-mail me the  rate and  your address (work is probably best, although I don't believe I have  any  cards here and will need the address again!).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_013">I will rush you a  check,  which you can cash and then rush me back a check.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_014">I really appreciate your help, and will hopefully talk to you soon (we  will  have to talk one of these afternoons, as I am generally around and  have no  classes!).
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Wed, 29 Aug 2001 20:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Mckay, Jonathan [mailto:Jonathan.McKay@enron.com]</from><to> Jeffrey.R.Pearson@Dartmouth.EDU</to><subject> RE: Currency</subject><text><sentence id="EPT019_015">How about 1.5460 as the rate.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_016">I'll just send you a cheque for USD$20,000 and you can mail me the appropriate amount back.(Laura
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_017">Scott agreed to do the amount that I wanted to swap with her).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_018">Where should I send the cheque?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Fri, 31 Aug 2001 11:45:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- "Jeffrey R. Pearson" &lt;Jeffrey.R.Pearson@Dartmouth.EDU@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-+22Jeffrey+20R+2E+20Pearson+22+20+3CJeffrey+2ER+2EPearson+40Dartmouth+2EEDU+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Mckay, Jonathan &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JMCKAY1</to><subject> RE: Currency</subject><text><sentence id="EPT019_019">Awesome, I owe you many beers when I get back at Christmas (assuming you are also home at xmas!).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_020">You can send me the check to: Jeff Pearson T'03 Tuck School of Business 316 Byrne Hall Dartmouth College Hanover NH, 03755-9000 I will courier you a check for the money on Tuesday!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_021">If possible, can you please also courier the check to me, I have to pay my tuition by the 10th and need to ensure that I have the money.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT019_022">I will include an extra 15 on the check to cover the cost of the courier!
</sentence><signature>Thanks </signature></text></email></thread></root>
