<root><thread><filename>shankman-j_personal_24.txt</filename><name></name><id>EPT023</id><email order="1"><date> Thu, 28 Sep 2000 10:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Shankman, Jeffrey A. [ mailto:Jeffrey.A.Shankman@ENRON.com]</from><to> elizabeth.danes@capitalz.com</to><subject></subject><text><sentence id="EPT023_001">Hi Elizabeth,   I'm Penny and Sam Britell's friend (Sam's from college) who have   mentioned (truthfully, insisted) that we should get together for a drink   next time I'm in NYC.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_002">I'll be in new york sunday the 7th through the 14th and would love to  get together for that drink Penny and Sam keep telling me about.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_003">Fortunately I have a pretty open schedule next week, so if you have any time, I'd like to meet you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_004">I'll be staying at the Penninsula next week, or feel free to call me on my cell phone at 713 854 4952.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_005">As well, I'll be checking voicemail in   the office (713) 853 1761.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_006">I'll be out of the office the next two days, but leave a message if you   have time.
</sentence><signature> Regards,  Jeff </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Thu, 28 Sep 2000 10:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Elizabeth Danes &lt;Elizabeth.Danes@capitalz.com@ENRON</from><to> Shankman, Jeffrey A.</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT023_007">Jeff,   Hi there......sounds like Penny has been equally emphatic on both sides   about meeting...
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_008">So sorry not to have responded earlier ...it has been such a completely   psychotic week for me.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_009">I have been in London and Stockholm this week - I   don't think I slept more than 3 hours a night all week.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_010">I am on my way   tomorrow to India (Bombay and Bangalore)...London on Thursday...and back  to   New York on Thursday night or Friday morning.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_011">Friday and Saturday (April  13   &amp; 14) are fairly free for me - would Friday night work for you?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_012">It will be difficult for me to reach you from India- given schedule and  time   difference, but I will be accessing email.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_013">I can be reached on a mobile   number in Europe on today and on Thursday - ++44 7990 973 620.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_014">As of  Friday   - in New York, the best place to reach me is on - 1 917 862 6552.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_015">By the   way, how is the Peninsula post-renovations?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_016">I liked it before the   renovations - am sure its even more wonderful.
</sentence><signature> Elizabeth </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Thu, 28 Sep 2000 10:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Jeffrey.A.Shankman@enron.com [mailto:Jeffrey.A.Shankman@enron.com]</from><to> Elizabeth.Danes@capitalz.com</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT023_017">Hi Elizabeth, I was finally able to access email remotely--Hope your trips went well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_018">Friday may end up being a little difficult, but I'll know tomorrow (friday).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_019">I'm free saturday as well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_020">Give me a call on my cell at 713 854 4952 or leave a msg at the hotel.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_021">I hope you were able to get my voice mail I left in your office and another one on you intl cell number.... 
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_022">I've never been to India, but as you know we have business there, and most people don't use the word delightful in describing the trip there-- 
</sentence><signature>Best, Jeff </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Thu, 12 Apr 2001 11:18:48 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Elizabeth Danes &lt;Elizabeth.Danes@capitalz.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-Elizabeth+20Danes+20+3CElizabeth+2EDanes+40capitalz+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Shankman, Jeffrey A. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JSHANKM</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT023_023">Trip was great - did I really describe India as delightful??..perhaps "intriguing" might have been more appropriate.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_024">Hard to miss the headlines - are you involved at all? I'll try calling you shortly.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_025">I fly back to New York first thing tomorrow (I missed my flight - traffic on a holiday weekend here is the worst I have ever witnessed).
</sentence><sentence id="EPT023_026">Hopefully, we'll catch up later today.
</sentence><signature>Elizabeth </signature></text></email></thread></root>
