<root><thread><filename>nemec-g_personal_1.txt</filename><name> RE: 650 11th update Nov 15 morning</name><id>EPT022</id><email order="1"><date> Fri, 16 Nov 2001 15:23:48 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Will, Lisa &lt;Lisa.Will@powerex.com</from><to>X- Scholtes, Diana &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DSCHOLT</to><subject> RE: 650 11th update Nov 15 morning</subject><text><signature></signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Fri, 16 Nov 2001 15:23:48 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Will, Lisa &lt;Lisa.Will@powerex.com</from><to>Howton"                   &lt;Gerald.Nemec@enron.com</to><subject>.org                     Re: Hello!</subject><text><sentence id="EPT022_001">Hi Gerald,  I am still here!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_002">Sorry for not getting back to you sooner..... 
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_003">My brother's baby passed away from SID's the week I got back from Cabo and so we have been dealing with the funeral and all of the emotions that go with losing someone.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_004">I think the whole ordeal is harder when it is a baby....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_005">So needless to say I have been out of the office way too much and I am so very much behind!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_006">Good news!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_007">I have some pictures that I will be sending to you next week!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_008">That way you will not be able to forget what I look like....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_009">I keep forgetting them in my truck but I will make it a priority to send them to you by Tues.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_010">How is everything going for you?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_011">Keeping busy with work and hopefully your social life?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_012">I think that you are the type that works way too many hours!!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_013">I am sure that one day you will balance everything out...  
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_014">Well it has been a full day ( I know it is only 3:00... ) and it is also Friday so I am going to call it good and go home, take a nap and get up in a couple of hours and head down to Seattle with Julie and Angie...  
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_015">Have a great weekend and I will talk to you Tuesday!
</sentence><signature>Take Care, Dee </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Fri, 16 Nov 2001 15:23:48 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Will, Lisa &lt;Lisa.Will@powerex.com</from><to>Howton"                   &lt;Gerald.Nemec@enron.com</to><subject>.org                     Re: Hello!</subject><text><sentence id="EPT022_016">Hi Dee,  I am really sorry to hear about your brother's child.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_017">I hope everything with you and your family is as well as it can be right now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_018">I will say a prayer for yall.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_019">I am doing good.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_020">Staying busy with work as you suggested.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_021">Actually we closed our big deal last Thursday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_022">That will allow my hours to become somewhat more normal in the near future.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_023">They are planning a trip to reward those who worked so hard on this deal.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_024">Guess where?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_025">Cabo.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_026">Went to Austin this past weekend to watch my beloved Longhorns play.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_027">They won, fortunately.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_028">It was good to see some old friends and hang out.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_029">I wouldn't mind moving back to Austin, but the jobs there just don't pay as much as in Houston.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_030">Everyone wants to stay in Austin after school, so they can lowball you on the cash.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_031">Looking forward to the pictures.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_032">Need to refresh my memory of Cabo.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_033">Take care and talk to you later.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Thu, 28 Sep 2000 10:21:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- "Karry Howton" &lt;howton.k@ghc.org</from><to>X- &lt;Gerald.Nemec@enron.com</to><subject> Re: Hello!</subject><text><sentence id="EPT022_034">Last set!
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_035">I do have a couple of more rolls to develop.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_036">Those I think are of Cabo Wabo so there should be some good ones.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_037">I will send them on just as soon as I get them back.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT022_038">Take care and have a great weekend!
</sentence><signature>Dee </signature></text></email></thread></root>
