<root><thread><filename>beck-s_personal_19.txt</filename><name> the latest . . .</name><id>EPT042</id><email order="1"><date> Thu, 8 Nov 2001 08:52:31 -0800 (PST)</date><from> White, Cara [mailto:CWhite@texas.usta.com]</from><to> 'cwhite@viviance.com'</to><subject> the latest . . .</subject><text><sentence id="EPT042_001">Hello, Sista -   Sally and I spoke this morning (I know you guys spoke last night as well)  -  and here's the latest idea:   
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_002">Since August, Sept., and Oct. are pretty much impossible for a trip, how  about we schedule a trip - possibly to NYC or San Fran. - during  THanksgiving.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_003">This seems ideal since we always get together anyway at  that  time - and nobody will have to remove kids from school.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_004">Sally thinks  maybe  we could travel Tuesday - Saturday and avoid some of the Thanksgiving  travel  MADNESS.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_005">Also, it pushes the travel even further into the year, which may  help you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_006">Then, we can have a family dinner for Mom and Dad on June 2 somewhere in  Austin.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_007">We can include Maryann and Fabe and San Antonio cousins IF mom  and  dad would like that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_008">Thoughts?
</sentence><signature>-Cara   Cara White  Community Development Coordinator  USTA Texas Section  1-888-883-6388  cWhite@texas.usta.com </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Thu, 8 Nov 2001 08:52:31 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Cindy White [SMTP:cwhite@viviance.com]</from><to> White, Cara</to><subject> RE: the latest . . .</subject><text><sentence id="EPT042_009">Cara,   Just talked to Sally.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_010">I think a very nice dinner in Austin sounds great.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_011">I  also think going somewhere for Thanksgiving sounds fun--and a lot more  feasible for me financially.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_012">(We $tart the orthodontia today....) I
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_013"> will  look at restaurants in the next couple of days and send you two some  options.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_014">It would be nice to find someplace very, very nice that Mom and  Dad haven't been to before.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_015">Also think we should have them picked up in a  limo....   Whew.....
</sentence><signature> Cindy  </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Thu, 8 Nov 2001 08:52:31 -0800 (PST)</date><from> White, Cara [mailto:CWhite@texas.usta.com]</from><to> 'Cindy White'</to><subject> RE: the latest . . .</subject><text><sentence id="EPT042_016">okay - I would advise this though: Since we may all be spending $$ on a trip on Nov. as well, I think we can be a bit judicious about what we do in June.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_017">I don't think we need to do anything on the order that we did it 10 years ago . . .
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_018">I'll be thinking of some restaurant ideas as well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_019">I tell you what might be nice: Jeffrey's has a private dining area (think called Josephine's house) - we had Crockett Int.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_020">Christmas there last year - and Sally had some Enron doo there - I think we could decorate it a bit and it would be quite nice.
</sentence><signature>-c. </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Tue, 30 Jan 2001 02:46:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- "Cindy White" &lt;cwhite@viviance.com</from><to>X- "White, Cara" &lt;CWhite@texas.usta.com</to><subject> RE: the latest . . .</subject><text><sentence id="EPT042_021">Jeffrey's/Josephine sounds excellent.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_022">I could go for the decorating thing--that would be fun for me....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_023">I still think somethign like a limo is in order.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT042_024">It may not be our personalities but I think Mother likes a big to-do.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
