<root><thread><filename>scott-s_inbox_116.txt</filename><name></name><id>EPT009</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 11:20:07 -0800 (PST)</date><from>   "Emily Hillegeist" &lt;ehillegeist@hotmail.com@ENRON</from><to>     sscott5@enron.com</to><subject></subject><text><sentence id="EPT009_001">where are you?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_002">it's been ages since i heard from you- are you ok? you  know  it makes me nervous when you go AWOL.....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_003">matt called this morning and he  sounds really bad. is doing that oh-so-familiar over-analyzing and  internalizing that would make almost anyone suicidal considering the situation.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_004">just want to be home so badly.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_005">feel so isolated here.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_006">wish  we  were all out on the walker's patio now chatting, and i was with mom and  dad  and harls.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_007">i think that's the only place where i'd feel safe and  reassured  and as close to happy as i could be right now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_008">kind of like the way  everyone described josh's funeral.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_009">horrifying, but as good a company to  rebound with as you could find probably.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_010">has been such a long and  draining  month emotionally and physically, and am just gutted.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_011">hope you're a bit  more  buoyant rt now han i am.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_012">am trying to get home asap, but mom and dad  don't  want me to fly.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_013">am not worried about it, and am going to try to get on  first flight possible anyways, so may see y'all soon....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_014">pls email and  let me  know you're still alive and in proportionally good spirits...
</sentence><signature>e </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 12 Sep 2001 16:17:48 -0500</date><from> Susan.M.Scott@enron.com</from><to> ehillegeist@hotmail.com</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT009_015">Mine is sscott5_2000.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_016">If you go to yahoo's home page you can try to install it yourself (eek!!!) or use the search on your computer (go to Start..Search...For Files or Folders) and type in Yahoo Messenger.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_017">If you still have it on your computer it will show up in the search area and you can just double click on it...that should bring it up.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_018">I'm doing alright.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_019">And you hit the nail on the head with the Josh comment....that's exactly what I've been reminded of.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_020">That feeling of uncertainty...loss of youthful bravado, sadness, injured sense of security...all of it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_021">Everyone in the Scott household is fine.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_022">Dad actually flew over NY yesterday morning before the first plane hit.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_023">He was coming from Manchester, NH.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_024">He said is was an absolutely beautiful day and that they flew right over Central Park...no idea how dramatically that skyline would change.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_025">The first they heard of the events that they must have just missed was when they landed in Nashville.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_026">He's still in Nashville right now obviously, but he's okay and that's what's important.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_027">I'm hoping with the limited flights they're allowing that Dad will be able to make it back to Houston soon, but it appears the FAA's just trying to get the passengers who are stranded back home so he may just be stuck somewhere else as a result.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_028">Chuck and Chris were supposed to fly out tomorrow morning from Seoul but they too have been delayed - indefinitely.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_029">The Army has put a hold on all duty station transfers which means we have no idea when they'll be leaving Korea or where exactly Chuck will be going.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_030">The stories and connections of the people on the news and those around me is horrifying and deeply saddening.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_031">A large number of people we do business with are based in NY and have lost countless friends and colleagues in the WTC's destruction.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_032">Chuck has some pledge brother's who are working up there, but we've heard that both of them are okay.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_033">I wish you were back home as well....I was on the phone with my Mom off and on all day yesterday and I must say it would've been nice to been back home on the couch with her.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_034">I did talk to Jen yesterday worried about LA and what was going on there, but she was fine as well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_035">She said they'd shut down the airport and several major roads surrounding it, but nothing else of concern.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_036">We evacuated the Enron building around 9:30 yesterday morning...it was disconcerting.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_037">I walked down the 32 flights of stairs to get to my parking garage and had only one desire...to get out of downtown.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_038">There were rumors flying that Houston was another target and given the size of our building, our international presence (esp. in regards to oil/natural gas) and our CEO's connections to the President...I think everyone figured Enron would be a logical target.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_039">Fortunately, those fears were unfounded.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_040">On a lighter note...I'm very anxious to hear all about your marathon experience...including the trip there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_041">Sounds like it was a doozey.
</sentence><signature>Love ya, Sue  </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 12 Sep 2001 14:59:56 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- "Emily Hillegeist" &lt;ehillegeist@hotmail.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-+22Emily+20Hillegeist+22+20+3Cehillegeist+40hotmail+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Scott, Susan M. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SSCOTT5</to><subject> RE:</subject><text><sentence id="EPT009_042">damn! just got kicked off aol for the umpteenth time today....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_043">tried to figure out this messenger business, but only have aol messenger, i think.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_044">and after all the dissertation-induced computer trauma this last moth, installing it could prove to be the proverbial straw, you know.....
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_045">good to hear about chuck sr. was worried about him when i heard about the missing planes.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_046">am sure both chucks will be ok.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_047">gals enron was spared as well, but what an ordeal.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_048">geez.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_049">makes becoming a carpenter and living in NB look reaaaaaly attractive right about now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_050">city, schmitty.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_051">a beer out on the deck rt now would be super cathrtic, i think.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_052">i know y'all aren't getting all the graphic footage there that we are here of the middle eastern countries' parades and parties in the streets rt now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_053">so unreal and sickening.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_054">how can people be that evil?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_055">really sad- you know michael?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_056">loud, london michael?
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_057">turns out he just flew back here from a meeting mon morning at the WTC, and his entire US office of cantor fitzgerald was based on the top 5-10 stories of the WTC.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_058">no one has been heard from.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_059">terrifying.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_060">it's just so isolated and lonely here rt now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_061">want to be home so badly, and i get so funky in these kinds of situations: you know, ultra sentimental and nostalgic and weepy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_062">and matt didn't help- he did one of those "i'm so worried that our friends/family don't know how loved and appreciated they are" bits, and that's one of those deep-rooted fears that you just never want to deal with because we count on lisa to be the "hallmark" aspect of our grp, and no one else.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_063">i chalk it up to a frightening lack of estrogen amongst us all....either way, not something i want to start thinking about, b/c it's just opening pandora's box, and can't stop.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_064">still hoping to make it home on fri or sat, and matt said he's going to houston on fri for a business thing, so maybe we will all get to chill this weekend if the stars are alligned.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_065">have fingers crossed.
</sentence><sentence id="EPT009_066">ok- bk to the bbc and cking on flight possiblities....chat soon- 
</sentence><signature>e </signature></text></email></thread></root>
