<root><thread><filename>quigley-d_myfriends_523.txt</filename><name>Hello from UT
</name><id>EPS075</id><email order="1"><date>Sun, 25 Nov 2001 17:23:16 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>moshuffle@hotmail.com
</from><to>jon.chapman@enron.com
</to><subject>Hello from UT
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS075_001">Hola,  If all recipients would please be soooo kind as to respond back with a home mailing address....except for suebob and jojo..got your's already.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_002">Well, we I made it safely to UT.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_003">We made the drive in about 2 days getting to Provo the 2nd evening and Park City the following morning.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_004">Now I am reminded why they always say that it is much safer to fly than to drive cross country.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_005">The first day we NARROWLY avoided running out of gas in NOWHERE texas...and I also got a speeding warning from a state trooper.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_006">The 2nd day of driving across UT on a two-land highway from Moab to Provo was harsh...it was snowing..i had a deathgrip on the steering wheel while oncoming cars blinded me with their headlights and john slept.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_007">Those are just the bad parts but it was well worth the time hanging with John and seeing the country.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_008">I've met my 3 roomates, Jimmy, James &amp; Thomas... and they seem normal and to John's delight none of them will be gracing a "Gorgeous Hunks of Park City Utah" calendar anytime soon.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_009">It has been snowing almost non-stop since I've been here...and it seems that everyone is off to ski or board here in town.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_010">I'm trying my best to hold off until the end of the week when all of my skiing and boarding activities will be free.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_011">I am scheduled to start this thurs at the bakery.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_012">I'm considering picking up another part time job just to keep things interesting, but I'm going to see how things go with a 40hr schedule first.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_013">I hope everyone is doing well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_014">I just wanted to say hello and most importantly get everyones home address.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS075_015">So take care all and I'll be in touch.
</sentence><signature>Sno-mo </signature></text></email></thread></root>
