<root><thread><filename>dasovich-j_personal_47.txt</filename><name>God Bless Texas
</name><id>EPS021</id><email order="1"><date>Fri, 8 Oct 1999 09:54:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>joan.wagner@bus.utexas.edu
</from><to>jeff.dasovich@enron.com
</to><subject>God Bless Texas
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS021_001">I'm taking a break from my telecom research on "the last mile."
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_002">Whoda thunk?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_003">My prof repeatedly refers to the RBOCs as dinosaurs and lunkheads.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_004">Gotta love that required Info Systems class.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_005">Life in Texas is pretty swell, despite the midterm anxiety.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_006">The weather couldn't be more perfect and Friday afternoons are ideal for mountain biking.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_007">I've decided if you're not falling down, you're not riding hard enough.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_008">There's great singletrack just down the hill from our place.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_009">Sometimes it feels like a glorified placement agency around here and the core classes could more aptly be named chore classes, but for the most part we're having fun.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_010">I have tons (well, 400 actually) of interesting and smart classmates and I even like the ones fixated on grades (mostly).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_011">I'm writing for the Texas Business Weekly, the student paper for the b-school.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_012">I did the cover for the next issue and even got to interview the Dean.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_013">It's fun and challenging -- a nice change from all the number crunching.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_014">Oh, and I'm playing intramural football.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_015">I got to play QB for one series in the last game.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_016">We were marching down that field, then ZOWIE, interception!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_017">Not to worry, our team is so bad we lose by the mercy rule.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_018">I didn't know there was a mercy rule in football.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_019">Ted's doing great.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_020">He started out as a product analyst for voice and a local telecom firm.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_021">That wasn't so exciting.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_022">But a couple months ago he got an offer within the same firm to become a Strategic Alliances Manager so now he fancies himself a deal-maker.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_023">He's much happier and more engaged by his work, which is a joy for me to see.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_024">And he's building a circle of friends there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_025">We're going to a wine-tasting tonight that's being hosted by one of his co-workers.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_026">Have any recommendations for "Tuscan" wines?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_027">He's also being a trooper about taking care of me and the domestic duties during this school thing.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_028">Danger:  I could really get used to that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_029">Nice to know we still like each other -- we celebrated our 5th anniversary last month.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_030">How are things with you?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS021_031">Still bringing enlightenment to the world?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
