<root><thread><filename>jones-t_sent_115.txt</filename><name>I'm German bound
</name><id>EPS074</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 16 Jun 1999 04:32:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>tana.jones@enron.com
</from><to>jon.chapman@enron.com
</to><subject>I'm German bound
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS074_001">Just wanted to drop you a note before I leave for Germany tomorrow.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_002">I'm looking forward to the cooler weather.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_003">I got some good bargains on post winter sweaters this weekend because no one in Houston is even thinking about buying a sweater!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_004">I spent more money on clothes than I ever have at one sitting!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_005">My backyard is really looking good.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_006">It's almost all planted, maybe 90% done.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_007">I've planted a few new trees, a Japanese Red Maple, and a Saucer Magnolia (which has lovely little pink fragrant blossoms).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_008">It will be a while before they look like trees, though.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_009">Right now they kinda look like tall bushes.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_010">I've planted a lot of tropical plants, I've got a ten ft. plumeria (which is what they make the Hawaiian leis out of) which has little little yellow fragrant blossoms, and an Australian fern tree, which is about 7 ft. tall and looks kinda like a palm.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_011">They're in pots, because I'll have to take them in during hard freezed.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_012">I've planted lots of climbing pink, yellow and white roses and one mauve hybrid.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_013">It will take a while before they fill out.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_014">Also, two pink/purple crape myrtles, which should add a lot of color.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_015">Those are those colorful small trees that bloom all over Houston.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_016">I've planted a lot of stuff with scent, and stuff to attract birds and butterflies.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_017">I hope the next time you come it will have filled out a bit.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_018">Right now we've been having so much rain that they're drowning a bit.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_019">I need a little sun to make them bloom.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_020">And then there's my St. Francis fountain.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_021">He's just lovely!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_022">Also, the central air is done.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_023">No more noise from window units.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_024">Now he's painting my bedrooms, the front one a real pale blue, and the back one a real pale pink.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_025">I hope when I get back from Europe it will all be over and I can start cleaning up all the dust.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_026">I'll have 3 days to recuperate because of the 4th of July holiday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_027">You and Sue were going to spruce up your garden a bit.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_028">Have you been able to do anything?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_029">I'm so glad I got to see your house.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_030">Now when you talk about things I can picture what you're talking about.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_031">Also, when I get back from Europe I'm going to get some cats again.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_032">I'm looking forward to that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_033">I think I'm finally over mourning the demise of poor Willow.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_034">Mark said he didn't have a lot of time to visit with you when he was there because you were in Teeside a lot of the time.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_035">I'm sorry he didn't get a chance to see your car.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_036">I was trying to describe it to him and I don't think I gave it justice.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_037">It was good talking to you the other day!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS074_038">I'll give you a call when I get back.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
