<root><thread><filename>kuykendall-t_sent_178.txt</filename><name>Re: long lost friend
</name><id>EPS035</id><email order="1"><date>Mon, 18 Dec 2000 05:37:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>tori.kuykendall@enron.com
</from><to>reagantgo@aol.com
</to><subject>Re: long lost friend
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS035_001">I'm so glad you wrote me back - sounds like you're a very busy person, but it looks like you're getting to do what you wanted to do.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_002">As for me, I got married to a great guy named Patrick that i met during our last semester at UT.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_003">We actually got set up on a blind date by Rachel Hanson.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_004">Anyway, we'll be married 6 years in June and we're expecting our first child in June.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_005">I spent a few years after college as a clothing buyer for Foley's, but I now am doing something completely different that I absolutely love.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_006">I work for Enron - big energy trading company - wasnt sure if you knew who we were.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_007">I'm trading natural gas, and it's a really fun job that's fast-paced and challenging.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_008">My hubby is an account manager for an internet company that has not yet gone public but their prospects are looking pretty good.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_009">We bought a house in Sugarland about 3.5 years ago, but we sold it in August and moved into a new house that we built in Katy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_010">We wanted to be close to my parents and also closer to San Antonio - where Pat is from - his parents still live there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_011">Anyway - I guess that's it in a nutshell.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_012">Oh yeah - and my address is: 4419 Stackstone Ln.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_013">Katy, TX 77450 I hope we can keep in touch.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_014">I'm not travelling right now, but if you ever make it to Houston - I'd love to see you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS035_015">Give me some more details in the next email!
</sentence><signature>Take Care and Happy Holidays! Love, Tori </signature></text></email></thread></root>
