<root><thread><filename>taylor-m_sent_486.txt</filename><name>Re: Cruise itinerary
</name><id>EPS016</id><email order="1"><date>Thu, 23 Sep 1999 07:30:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>mark.taylor@enron.com
</from><to>mzeleanor@juno.com
</to><subject>Re: Cruise itinerary
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS016_001">Thanks for your note.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_002">If you are still trying to decide about shore excursions, I was just remembering my trip and have the following observations:  I found the volcano on the Big Island to be marginally interesting, not particularly pretty, and from where I was staying (Kona), a very long day.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_003">Kauai was very beautiful - the Na Pali coast is particularly spectacular (that coast and the nearby beaches are where South Pacific was filmed) but it is quite rugged and nearly inaccessible as I remember it except on foot or by boat.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_004">I would highly recommend seeing it by boat if that option is available, otherwise, you can just drive up to the end of the road and get a pretty good view.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_005">There is also a river boat trip I didn't get to take so I can't recommend it - it was popular with visitors.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_006">I didn't make it to Maui but I've always thought it would be fun to go to the top of the mountain to watch the sunrise (in a car or bus) and then ride down the hill on a bicycle.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_007">There was a bay near Honolulu on Oahu (near Diamond Head) where I did my first-ever snorkeling.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_008">It was very popular (crowded) but a lot of fun and while there were plenty of fish to see the reef itself was pretty dead (not a lot of pretty coral).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_009">I found the web site for the dolphin lab where I worked but a quick look didn't indicate they have a visitors center.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_010">You might call them when you are there if you have the extra time and want to go. http://dolphin-institute.org/
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_011">As far as your clothes are concerned, since you won't have to carry them yourselves, why not  take them all!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS016_012">Have a great trip!
</sentence><signature>Love, Mark</signature></text></email></thread></root>
