<root><thread><filename>gilbertsmith-d_personal_21.txt</filename><name>hi
</name><id>EPS083</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 9 May 2001 11:36:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>jenny.latham@enron.com
</from><to>doug.gilbert-smith@enron.com
</to><subject>hi
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS083_001">Hi Doug-E-Gee,  I haven't chatted with you in a while and wanted to catch up.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_002">How are things back at the factory?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_003">I heard about some changes over there - are they really not going to trade Southeast?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_004">That sounds like a bunch of crap.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_005">What's the story there?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_006">I can't say that I miss all that although I just haven't had a chance to get frustrated with things here.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_007">I'm sure that will co= me soon enough.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_008">Actually things have been as good as could be expected (work-wise).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_009">I like the people in my group and have made some good progress in getting everything in place.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_010">The true test will come once the business r= amps up, but at least in theory I'm on the right track (hopefully).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_011">Enough about yucky work.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_012">I think I've found a place in South Ken.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_013">It's not perfect (and very expensive), but it meets enough of my criteria to justi= fy calling off the search.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_014">It will be great to have that part of the move completely done.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_015">I'm scheduled to move in on Monday provided I can get an advance in ?'s.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_016">My first paycheck doesn't come until May 20, but I always assumed I would get my bonus right away.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_017">Not the case.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_018">I don't want to mess with transferring dollars at this point.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_019">Anyway, huge pain in the ass, but it should work out.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_020">When do you think you might be able to join Killian on a trip over?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_021">I promise to be more fun than your grumpy little brother.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_022">We're supposed to go out on Friday and were starting to plan the details.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_023">Of course his new girlfriend freaked out and insisted on meeting us after dinner.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_024">Based on my last (and only) experience, I can definitely do without that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_025">I told Jamie that my weekends were too precious to deal with a bunch of shit like that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_026">Anyway, we may still have dinner, but I'm out after that.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_027">I'm going to meet Stacey in Paris on Saturday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_028">Should be fun to take the train over (not in a hijacking way).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_029">Tracey was in town last weekend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_030">She was so excited that I took her to a Tex-Mex place since she hasn't found anything good in NY.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_031">Aren't you going there in mid-June?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_032">Clark, Tori and Laura (as in Bubby and) are coming here over Memorial Day.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_033">We're going to fly to Venice for a few nights then come back to London for the last night of their trip.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_034">Laura forgot (hmmmm) about a charity event commitment she has scheduled for that weekend, so she may not make it after all.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_035">Of course the tickets (purchased by moi) are non-refundable, non-transferrable.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_036">Looks like a romantic weekend for three!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_037">Hope all is going well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS083_038">Sorry you're not coming over with Killian although we can be extra-naughty this way.
</sentence><signature> Jenny.</signature></text></email></thread></root>
