<root><thread><filename>white-s_personal_9.txt</filename><name>Wedding Plans
</name><id>EPS014</id><email order="1"><date>Thu, 19 Jul 2001 13:20:21 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>cchurchill@oldcastleglass.com
</from><to>anita.fam@enron.com
</to><subject>Wedding Plans
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS014_001">The BIG day is almost here, less than a month away!!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_002">I hope everyone is as excited as I am!!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_003">I wanted to give you a heads up on times and what is going on for that weekend so you can begin making plans if you haven't already.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_004">Friday August 10 I think some of the guys are getting together to play golf.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_005">My dad, grandad, brother, Kevin Galloway, and whoever else will be playing at a location to be decided.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_006">If you are interested and will be in Dallas Friday morning, let Kevin or myself know.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_007">The girls will be relaxing and taking care of last minute details (nails, facials, tea, etc...)  Friday night 
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_008">Please be at the church between 5:45 and 6:00.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_009">Traffic can be bad at this time of the evening, so please allow plenty of time.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_010">In order to be at dinner by 7:30, rehearsal must start at 6:15.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_011">Maggiano's is five minutes from the church so as soon as the rehearsal is over you can start drinking beer again.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_012">Most of our family and Jason and I are staying at AmeriSuites on Friday so if you are staying at a hotel, try to book it there.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_013">You need to book by July 27 to get the discounted rate.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_014">All the hotel information is on the back of the directions sent with the wedding invitations.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_015">Saturday August 12 Guys:  You are on your own, but Jason is not to hang out at the bar all day.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_016">(Sorry Kevin, no paybacks!)
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_017">Girls:  Luncheon is at the Zodiac room at downtown Nieman's.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_018">If anyone needs help with transportation, please let me know.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_019">Wedding Time  Guys:  Please be at the church by 6:15.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_020">You need to come dressed, but bring your tux coat on a hanger as it will be very hot!!  
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_021">Pictures will be taken with guys and Jason's family before the ceremony.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_022">Girls:  Please be at the church by 5:30.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_023">You can bring your dresses, but have hair and make up already done.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_024">Pictures will be taken with girls and my immediate family before the ceremony.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_025">Vocalists should be there by 6:30 to practice with organist.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_026">House party should be there by 6:45 guest will begin arriving around 7:00.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_027">There will not be a mass (you non-Catholics are off the hook(except Jason!), Catholics will have to go to mass on Sunday!!)  
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_028">Reception As soon as the ceremony is over, stay around for pictures.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_029">We are only allowed 20 minutes so we will need to be attentive to the photographer so he can make sure he gets all the pictures in the allotted 20 minutes.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_030">Everyone will then go to the Tower Club downtown for the reception.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_031">We should be there by 8:45, unless we take a detour in the limo!!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_032">Last call will be at 12:30 and there are plenty of places to go out afterwards if you would like.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_033">West end and Deep Ellum are a short cab ride away.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_034">I think that is everything.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_035">Please feel free to call or E-mail me if you have any questions!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_036">Thank you for everyone for being a part of this special time with Jason and I.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS014_037">We look forward to seeing everyone soon!!!
</sentence><signature>Chris and Jason </signature></text></email></thread></root>
