<root><thread><filename>beck-s_personal_26.txt</filename><name>stuff
</name><id>EPS052</id><email order="1"><date>Fri, 6 Oct 2000 03:02:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>cwhite@viviance.com
</from><to>sally.beck@enron.com
</to><subject>stuff
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS052_001">Hi, Sally...  
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_002">Wanted to apologize for the way I probably sounded on the phone--lots was going on here and you caught me at a brain-overload moment!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_003">Thanks for sending the Enron article--thought it was great--brought it in to the office to show you off here...  
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_004">Pictures of the girls were much appreciated--can't really believe how old they look.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_005">Brigeda's has taken possession of them and put them on her bulletin board--although she wanted BIGGER ones like Grandmom--told her Grandmoms always got bigger ones....
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_006">Brigeda gets her picture taken next week and will send you one--last year's was so dorky we didn't circulate them much...  
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_007">Dad actually seemed better yesterday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_008">He was making jokes and his voice was a little stronger--he's on pain medication for his tongue--I think giving him something to make him relax really does help--he wasn't loopy just not quite so tense.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_009">He seemed very "up" for the dr's appt in Houston.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_010">I told him you asked Fabe for the best ENT in Houston and that this guy was in your church and did Meagan's tonsils.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_011">He liked all of that information a lot...thanks again for arranging this.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_012">Mom and I decided if anyone could get him to a doctor on short notice you would be able to do it--now the pressure is on!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS052_013">Hope you have a great weekend--Brigeda and I are looking forward to see you guys next weekend.
</sentence><signature>Cindy </signature></text></email></thread></root>
