<root><thread><filename>beck-s_personal_24.txt</filename><name>hi and things</name><id>EPS023</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 1 Nov 2000 07:09:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>cwhite@texas.usta.com</from><to>sally.beck@enron.com</to><subject>hi and things</subject><text><sentence id="EPS023_001">Hi, Sal.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_002">Just saying hello.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_003">Hope your interviews at OU went well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_004">You are quite the interviewing queen!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_005">Maybe you should write a book (or article) sometime on "Keys to Snagging the Right Employee!".
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_006">Good news about Dad, huh?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_007">So glad you were able to get him to see your doctor to start the ball rolling on finding new answers for him.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_008">It is a lot of work to find the right answers for our healthcare!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_009">We are starting to think more about the baby's room . . .
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_010">I think we're leaning towards using your bed, if that's still okay.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_011">Did you say that the changing table would be available, too?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_012">Is it light wood also?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_013">I think we will probably get our own bed linens - but what do your look like?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_014">Boyish?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_015">Do you think it's better to use a rocker or a glider?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_016">Sorry we didn't make it for a fall trip.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_017">It seems that almost every weekend one of us has been gone - Chris leaves for Asia on Thursday for 2 weeks - it's a nonstop whirlwind of travel!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_018">Thanksgiving should be fun . . . what shall we bring?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_019">Is there any sort of a plan for Friday?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_020">I had my monthly doctor's appointment today:  the baby is still in there and her mom is getting very fat!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS023_021">I have really enjoyed my Halloween nutcracker this season!
</sentence><signature>Love, CaraCara WhiteCommunity Development CoordinatorUSTA Texas Section1-888-883-6388cWhite@texas.usta.com</signature></text></email></thread></root>
