<root><thread><filename>staab-t_personal_20.txt</filename><name>Bowl Bonanza $,2,700.00
</name><id>EPS071</id><email order="1"><date>Fri, 21 Dec 2001 09:59:08 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>bill.rubinsky@usa.xerox.com
</from><to>bill.rubinsky@enron.com, wizig'.'bobby@enron.com, green'.'chuck@enron.com, 
</to><subject>Bowl Bonanza $,2,700.00
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS071_001">Friends,  If anyone can't open the grid, please reply back to me and give me your mailing address or fax number and I'll either fax or mail you a hard copy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_002">Pot is $2,700.00!!  IMPORTANT...
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_003">If you brought people into the pool, please distribute a copy of the grid to them.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_004">IMPORTANT... TRACKING SOFTWARE.....
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_005">There is a tracking software imbedded in this excel spreadsheet to track winners for you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_006">To use, simply type the name of the winner of each bowl in the blank line under the pairings and then tab.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_007">Software will total the number of winners for each person in the left most column (there is a "0" there now).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_008">You must type the name exactly as it appears in the list of picks and not as it appears in the pairing grid on top.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_009">Hence, Tx AM must be tracked as "A &amp; M ", Cincin as "Cinn" etc.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_010">It's pretty cool and should save you hours of time.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_011">(Gunter - far cry from when you last played and I use to type this up on a "Memorywriter", huh?) 
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_012">Since I of course don't trust this medium at all, the "official winner" will be the person from my manual calculations!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_013">(Should be the same but I'm not taking any chances.)
</sentence><sentence id="EPS071_014">Good Luck, Happy Holidays and if TEXAS doesn't start winnng it's bowl games, I am going to give up doing this Bowl Bonanza!!! Hook'em!
</sentence><signature>Bill Rubinsky (713) 721-3378 </signature></text></email></thread></root>
