<root><thread><filename>scott-s_inbox_86.txt</filename><name>Wedding Details
</name><id>EPS027</id><email order="1"><date>Fri, 24 Aug 2001 08:06:09 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>susan_s_edwards@yahoo.com
</from><to>jenniferbeechner@yahoo.com, lgillet@enron.com, katyhester@hotmail.com, 
</to><subject>Wedding Details
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS027_001">Hi Girls, I'll be Mrs.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_002">Susan Williams in 8 DAYS!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_003">I'm so excited and nervous and stressed all at the same time.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_004">This has been a hectic week not only with wedding errands but also trying to get my life wrapped up before I take off for three weeks.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_005">Before I leave town, I want to make sure you all know what's going on next weekend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_006">I think most of you (with the exception of Katie) will be getting in town on Friday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_007">If anyone will be in Park City by 11:00 am on Friday, I'd love for you to come to the bridal luncheon my grandmother is having for me.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_008">If you can make it, let me know.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_009">Friday night I've got the rehearsal at the church at 5:30.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_010">The rehearsal dinner starts at 7:00 pm at the Marriot.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_011">Dinner will be very casual.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_012">You may want to wear or bring something with long sleeves because dinner is outside and it gets chilly at night (low 60's) in Park City.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_013">After dinner, it will be time to ditch the families and head to Main Street where we will have our choice of two or three bars -all very laid back hole-in-the-wall type places.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_014">On Saturday morning, I would like to have breakfast with all of you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_015">I want to spend some qualit! y time with you before the day gets hectic.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_016">The location is to-be-announced.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_017">I'll scope out a good breakfast place when I get to Park City.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_018">Unfortunately, we'll have to eat early - around 9:30am -so if any of you have to much fun on Friday night, I'll know why  you aren't there ; ) 
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_019">The wedding will be at 3:00pm.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_020">The church is on Main Street (at the top of the hill).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_021">The parking situation is kind of confusing  because you can't park on Main Street and the parking lot is on the street that runs behind the church.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_022">You may want to check the church out ahead of time so you know where it is.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_023">The ceremony will be approx 1 hour.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_024">The reception is at Stein Eriksen Lodge which is up the mountain a few miles.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_025">It doesn't start until 5:00 which gives you some time to kill between the wedding and reception.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_026">This will give Eric and I time to take pictures at the church wi! thout having to miss any of the reception.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_027">I figure by the time you freshen up, drive up to Stein Eriksen (which is a beautiful drive up the mountain) and  you can have a  drink at the bar it will be five o'clock.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_028">After the reception, you are on your own.... Now my request....Can everyone let me know when they are getting into town and where they are staying?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_029">I've got that information for most of you but I just want to verify.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_030">Also, Kelly and Laura - if your husbands want to play golf on Friday morning with Eric and his friends, let me know.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_031">FYI - If anyone wants to treat themselves to a message,manicure/pedicure,etc. while in Park City the number for the Belle Salon is  (435)655-8250.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_032">My mom and I leaving on Monday.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_033">If any of you want to get in touch with me, my cell phone is the best place to reach me (832)515-3066.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_034">I can't wait to see all of you next weekend!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_035">I'm so excited that all of you are coming to the wedding.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS027_036">Each of you is very special to me and it means so much to have you there on my wedding day.
</sentence><signature>Love, Susan </signature></text></email></thread></root>
