<root><thread><filename>richey-c_personal_6.txt</filename><name>portland...
</name><id>EPS095</id><email order="1"><date>Sun, 13 Jan 2002 10:40:25 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>mgiattina@aol.com
</from><to>cooper.richey@enron.com
</to><subject>portland...
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS095_001">Hey Cooper,  Well, I don't know if you remember, but I'm heading out to Portland for an interview.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_002">Prob little to no chance I'll end up there, but what the hell, I've never been and it can't hurt to visit.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_003">I remember you saying that you knew Brinda's email.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_004">Do you think you could send it to me?  I'll be there the 14th.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_005">Otherwise, don't really know what to say.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_006">I'm pretty much still reeling from what happened.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_007">I meant it when I said that nothing like this has happened in the last 8 years.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_008">Unfortunately, my future with Steve is looking a little rocky right now, but I still don't know what my motivation was (drunkenness never an excuse...) and I've been pretty upset.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_009">I haven't seen Steve yet, and to be honest I don't think now is the time to bring this sort of thing up to him.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_010">I decide where I will move in feb, and I think it's best if steve and I go our own ways amicably, without this mess (yes, feeble excuse).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_011">Anyway, don't mean to bring up all this crap, b/c it's not yours, but we've been friends for a long time and I respect you and like you, and I really don't want you to think that this is a frequent occurence.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_012">I do wish I was a little more sober, not b/c it would've changed much, but I think it might've been better all around.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_013">So, any advice on Portland or SF would be appreciated (one night in each).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS095_014">Call 646 342 3507 or email.
</sentence><signature>Later, Mara</signature></text></email></thread></root>
