<root><thread><filename>nemec-g_personal_15.txt</filename><name>I'm sorry..........
</name><id>EPS039</id><email order="1"><date>Tue, 5 Oct 1999 12:55:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>lnemec@ect.enron.com
</from><to>gerald.nemec@enron.com
</to><subject>I'm sorry..........
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS039_001">that I have not been a good friend to you lately.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_002">You deserve to be treated better.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_003">I know I am being totally selfish but at the same time can't seem to stop myself.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_004">I wish I knew of a way to make things between us better.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_005">Sometimes I feel like this last three months has just been a dream that I am going to wake up from and everything will be back the way it was before we started drifting apart.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_006">I can't tell you enough how sorry I am for not talking to you before things got so twisted.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_007">Unfortunately, I don't know how to find my way back to you now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_008">I know you find it hard to believe anything I say, but I hope you know that I loved you more than anything when we got married and I still love you even now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_009">You are a wonderful, caring, beautiful person that I am so very glad to have had in my life.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_010">I will never forget you and will always have a special place in my heart for you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_011">This may seem like this is easy for me, but it isn't.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_012">I have just been struggling with this longer than you have.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_013">I never wanted this to happen, I wanted to love you for the rest of my life and make our marriage a priority.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_014">I am sorry I failed you.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS039_015">As far away as it seems now, I hope we can continue to be friends someday.
</sentence><signature>Lisa </signature></text></email></thread></root>
