<root><thread><filename>kuykendall-t_sent_5.txt</filename><name>customer service complaint
</name><id>EPS038</id><email order="1"><date>Mon, 27 Nov 2000 07:07:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>tori.kuykendall@enron.com
</from><to>custo@coair.com
</to><subject>customer service complaint
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS038_001">Hello , my name is Tori Kuykendall (One Pass BJ927934).
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_002">My husband, Patrick( One Pass VF751282), and I have been One Pass members for a few years now as well as elite members on several occasions.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_003">We also use Chase Continental Visa exclusively, and my husband is a President's Club member.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_004">I have made Continental my airline of choice for as long as I can remember booking my own travel arrangements and have been a very satisfied customer in the past.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_005">This morning, however, I had a very bad experience.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_006">I booked tickets for a vacation back on September 4th for a trip from Houston to New York on December 1.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_007">Since I booked the ticket, I became pregnant and found out from my doctor last week that I will still be unable to travel on December 1st due to complications with my pregnancy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_008">My doctor indicated to me that I may not be able to fly at all during my pregnancy, which is due to end in June.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_009">I spoke to Leroy Peterson this morning to explain the situation, and he indicated that all he could do was give me credit that would expire on September 5th, 2001 and that a $75 service would be charged to me next time I book a ticket for me or my husband.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_010">I understand that this is the same policy that you would have given me if I had just decided that I didn't feel like taking a vacation this weekend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_011">In my opinion, this is an unacceptable policy in the event of medical complications.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_012">As you can see with my situation, it is unlikely that my husband and I will be able to plan a vacation by September of 2001 considering we will hopefully have a 2 month old child.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_013">I repeatedly asked Leroy if there was anyone else who could help me or anyone I could talk to in order to get some kind of exception to your policy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_014">I indicated that I could provide a doctor's note if necessary.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_015">He was very rude to me, stating "You don't have to ask me 7 different times for the same thing - I already told you NO!"  I had to cancel a flight for work about a month ago on Southwest airlines for the same reason, but I was hoping that I would be able to fly again by now.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_016">For your information, your competitor was very helpful.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_017">They accepted my doctor's note, gave me a credit good for one year, and will allow me to change the ticket to another person's name if I am still unable to use it.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_018">That ticket was also booked as a non-refundable fare.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_019">Although I have always used Continental  for my personal travel, the treatment I have had in this difficult time has definitely made me second-guess my future choices.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS038_020">If there is anything you can do to help, I would greatly appreciate it.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
