<root><thread><filename>jones-t_sent_58.txt</filename><name>Re: Tana!
</name><id>EPS051</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 26 May 1999 03:16:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>tana.jones@enron.com
</from><to>rex01@dellnet.com, rex04@msn.com, dkreiman@mcleodusa.net, 
</to><subject>Re: Tana!
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS051_001">John, it's good to hear from you!
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_002">A few things on your paralegal friend.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_003">First, we don't currently have any openings, though we have tended to hire paralegals with a lot of experience.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_004">Most of the paralegals in our group have about 15-25 years experience.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_005">Also, we recently hired someone, and I don't anticipate us hiring for awhile.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_006">Most of Enron's litigation work is done out of Enron Corp.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_007">They do have a big litigation group up there, and that would be the most obvious place to start.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_008">Chuck Cheek is the head lawyer for that group.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_009">You could forward her resume up there with a note, it might get it more personal attention.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_010">Also, keep watching (or she can watch, it online) the job bank, they advertise paralegal jobs there from time to time with all the Enron companies.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_011">Another group that might be interested in hiring paralegals, and might hire paralegals with less experience, is the Global Contracts Group headed up by Mary Solmonson.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_012">They're always looking for people, and it might be a good way for your friend to get her foot in the door at ECT.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_013">Also, if her undergraduate degree was in business, obviously, she might have some more options in other groups.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_014">As far as running goes, I'm trying to get back into shape.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_015">I'm just surviving 3 miles around the park, and this weekend I plan to double my mileage to 6.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_016">It sounds like we're both not in fighting form.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS051_017">But I do want to start training in July with Houston Fit for the Houston Marathon again.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
