<root><thread><filename>scott-s_personal_32.txt</filename><name>Necesito consejos
</name><id>EPS053</id><email order="1"><date>Mon, 16 Oct 2000 10:51:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>ktgotts@aol.com
</from><to>susan.scott@enron.com
</to><subject>Necesito consejos
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS053_001">Susan,  I don't know if my dad told you, but I am at Tulane law school and enjoying it very much.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_002">The work is challeging, but I am really happy with the my choice of paths.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_003">The campus is beautiful, the people are normal, the town is amazing (a bit distracting at times), and my professors and the law school in general are fantastic.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_004">I am writing you to ask for your advice.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_005">They are beginning to apply the job search pressure to us (it is already the 8th week) and I am trying to figure out my best course of action.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_006">I have heard that most of the big firms in Houston aren't even looking for students after only their 1st year-- that they prefer to interview after the 2nd year for summer clerk positions and then associate jobs.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_007">Do you know of any smaller firms or specific attorneys that I might be able to pursue with a letter and resume?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_008">What did you do after your first year?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_009">Did you stay in Texas?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_010">I do know that I want to practice in Houston, so I think that working there during this, my first summer, would be a smart idea.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_011">It will at least give me more time to make contacts/ meet people.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_012">What do you think?
</sentence><sentence id="EPS053_013">Any thoughts/advice you have would be greatly appreciated.
</sentence><signature>Thank you, Katy</signature></text></email></thread></root>
