<root><thread><filename>quigley-d_myfriends_26.txt</filename><name>Fwd: Chris Simms brings balance to the force
</name><id>EPS098</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 5 Dec 2001 06:32:47 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>markm@cajunusa.com
</from><to>a..shankman@enron.com
</to><subject>Fwd: Chris Simms brings balance to the force
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS098_001">Many people are concerned with the state of Chris Simms confidence going into next season now that he has been benched for the bowl game.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_002">There is no reason for panic as the scenario shall play out like this.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_003">The Longhorns and Huskies will be tied at 28 late in the fourth quarter of the Holiday Bowl.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_004">Applewhite will lead the Horns on a miraculous 50-yd drive down to the Washington 30-yd line with only 10 sec left on the clock.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_005">Between plays Applewhite will look over at the Golden Boy standing on the sideline and recognize that the time is now for Simms to fulfill his Destiny.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_006">As the Star Wars music plays in the background, Applewhite will lead the Horns up to the line of scrimmage.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_007">In Obi-Wan Kenobi-to-Darth Vader fashion, Major will look across the line at the Huskies defense and say,"Strike me down and I shall become more powerful than you could ever imagine."
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_008">As the ball is snapped, Major drops back in the pocket and then stands motionless, allowing the Huskies linebackers to pummel him.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_009">Simms screams, "NO!!!" as Major lies motionless on the field.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_010">Major is carted off the field with numerous broken bones while the Golden Boy takes his warm-up tosses on the sideline.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_011">The clock sits at 4 seconds remaining as Simms trots onto the field.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_012">Only enough time for one try at the endzone.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_013">Simms walks to the line, takes the snap and begins to look over the field.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_014">As Simms prepares to unload a blazing bullet pass right into the hands of a Washington safety, he hears Major's voice in his mind, "Use the force Chris, read the field".
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_015">The Golden Boy brings his throwing arm down, the Star Wars music plays once again, and Chris looks over the entire field for the first time since playing the School for the Blind back in Jersey.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_016">Simms spots Roy Williams wide open, closes his eyes, and fires a 30 yd touchdown pass for the victory.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_017">And hence the legend of the Golden Boy is alive and well.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS098_018">Stay tuned for the next episode as Chris learns that his father is not ex-player/broadcaster Phil Simms, but is actually broadcaster Dennis Miller 
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
