<root><thread><filename>scholtes-d_outbox_personal_31.txt</filename><name>(no subject)
</name><id>EPS085</id><email order="1"><date>Tue, 24 Jul 2001 03:02:15 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>wscholtes@aol.com
</from><to>diana.scholtes@enron.com
</to><subject>(no subject)
</subject><text><sentence id="EPS085_001">Diana,  It's obvious that I am no longer useful to you besides as a baby sitter.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_002">There is absolutely no love, respect or feelings for me whatsoever.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_003">I have outlived my welcome.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_004">It appears that you have gotten everything you've ever wanted and now are discarding me and our relationship.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_005">The horrible thing is that I'm not sure how long this has been going on.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_006">It seems that every time we have problems, I buy you something new and our relationship miraculously heals itself.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_007">I now believe (and have probably always believed) that if I wouldn't have decided to build the house, you'd have already left me.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_008">That's a shame, because I will never forgive you for allowing me to sell MY home (and the girls home) and then discarding our marriage sending me and my family out into the streets without the most important material thing Jennifer and Lindsay have ever had.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_009">I look back at our 9 years of marriage, especially the last five years and the only time I can remember truly being loved and appreciated was when you were pregnant with Natalie.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_010">You blame me for not being as good to you as I was when you were pregnant, but I say that you were the one who changed after you had Natalie.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_011">Not that you weren't that way before you were pregnant, you were just different during the pregnancy.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_012">I''ve played this game much too long.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_013">I need to be loved, appreciated and respected.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_014">I'm neither of those.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_015">I deserve better and maybe, since you are obviously so unhappy, you do too.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_016">I'm positive the effect on Natalie will be devastating.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_017">That's why we have decided to drag this out this long.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_018">But our relationship, if you can call it that, has degraded to a very low and dangerous point.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_019">That's why I have decided to move into an apartment after the girls go home.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_020">I have already been looking, I just need to decide where to move.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_021">As for custody, I'm sure we will have differing opinions and we will have to discuss them in person.
</sentence><sentence id="EPS085_022">I would appreciate it if you could make some time over the next couple days to discuss with me the timing of my move and discuss how we are going to handle it with our parents, friends and mostly the kids.
</sentence><signature>Bitterly, Bill Scholtes</signature></text></email></thread></root>
