<root><thread><filename>scott-s_inbox_66.txt</filename><name>hey
</name><id>ECS083</id><email order="1"><date>Fri, 3 Aug 2001 00:16:42 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>cscott_korea@yahoo.com
</from><to>sscott5@enron.com
</to><subject>hey
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS083_001">Susan, I mailed your tickets today.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_002">They said that the fastest I could get them there is 7-10 days.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_003">We should be able to make it, just keep checking your mail.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_004">Your itenerary is as follows: Tuesday, August 14 IAH to SFO    9:20am - 11:15am on Continental 531 SFO to Korea 1:00pm - 4:50pm on Korean Air 24, you will arrive on Wednesday, August 15 Sunday, August 26 Korea to LAX   3:00pm - 10:30am on Korean Air LAX to IAH       12:20pm - 5:49pm on Continental, you will arrive back in Houston on Sunday, 26th Anyway, I think that's it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_005">I hope the itenerary is ok.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_006">As far as packing I would bring clothes for hot, humid weather (about like Houston).
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_007">Nothing we do is very dressy.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_008">I would say a nice shorts outfit or skirt is about as dressy as it gets here.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_009">Wear comfortable, and shoes you really don't care about.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_010">The monsoon season may be ending soon, but the streets are disgusting year around.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_011">Bring your running shoes and I will try to keep you training for the marathon.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_012">There is an ATM on post here that we can use free of charge, so don't worry about cash too much.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_013">You can always write us a check.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_014">We can also cash a check for up to $300/day.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_015">Definitely do not change any money.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_016">There are some places around here that give pretty good rates.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_017">I would pack light and bring an extra suitcase.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_018">You may want to buy some pottery here, or some fragile items so make sure you have extra room on your carry on.&amp;n! bsp; Of course there's always mailing things, too.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_019">There is a DMZ tour on the 18th, 21st, 23rd, and 25th.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_020">Probably one of the Saturdays would be better for Chuck.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_021">If we do go somewhere, we should plan on going the first weekend you are here.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_022">That DMZ tour on the Saturday before you leave would be a long day, but you don't fly out until 3:00 the next day, so I think we could do it if you are game.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_023">Can't wait to take you around here and you can see what we've been doing the past year here!
</sentence><sentence id="ECS083_024">Have a good weekend!
</sentence><signature>-Chris </signature></text></email></thread></root>
