<root><thread><filename>scott-s_inbox_163.txt</filename><name>Your Role in Computer Virus Protection
</name><id>ECS069</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 3 Oct 2001 19:06:36 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>no.address@enron.com
</from><to>carol.clair@enron.com
</to><subject>Your Role in Computer Virus Protection
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS069_001">As you are aware, there have recently been a number of virus attacks released and spread across the Internet.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_002">Although Enron continually readdresses and updates its virus protection procedures, new viruses will continue to be released and pose a threat to Enron's computing environment.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_003">Therefore, it is very important that all Enron employees understand their responsibilities in helping Enron stay virus free.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_004">If you receive a file via Email or any other means and you are unfamiliar with the sender or the purpose of the file, please do not automatically open/launch the file.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_005">One of the key elements of a virus attack is the innocent nature of its delivery.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_006">Viruses can cause a significant amount of damage, including data loss and service outage.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_007">Viruses such as the Melissa, ILOVEYOU, AnnaKournikova, and the recent Nimda virus, caused organizations billions of dollars.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_008">Sometimes new viruses can breach the environment before the virus scanning software has been updated to detect &amp; quarantine them.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_009">Every employee in the Enron organization has a responsibility to keep our computing environment virus-free.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS069_010">If you believe you have a file that looks suspicious, delete it or contact your Resolution Center to obtain their assistance.
</sentence><signature>North America Resolution Center - x31411 ETS Solution Center - x54745 European Resolution Center - x36777 EES Help Desk - x 39797 Prevention &amp; Detection = PROTECTION! </signature></text></email></thread></root>
