<root><thread><filename>lavorato-j_inbox_76.txt</filename><name>Northwest Reserves
</name><id>ECS095</id><email order="1"><date>Mon, 19 Nov 2001 09:49:51 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>tim.belden@enron.com
</from><to>wes.colwell@enron.com, georganne.hodges@enron.com
</to><subject>Northwest Reserves
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS095_001">We currently have $21.4 million in reserve for potential Northwest refunds.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_002">$10 million currently sits in the LTCA book and $11.4 currently sits in the LTNW book.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_003">During the summer, FERC initiated an investigation into the potential of unjust and unreasonable spot prices in the northwest from December of 2000 through June of 2001.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_004">Seatlle City Light, Tacoma City Light, Eugene Water and Electric Board, and Sacramento Municipal Utility District all filed claims at FERC for refunds from EPMI.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_005">The claims totaled close to $100 million.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_006">However, many of these claims were, on their face, spurious.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_007">For example, Eugene Water and Electric Board filed for refund of forward purchases which was clearly outside the scope of FERC's proceeding.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_008">We hired consultants from Charles River Associates (CRA) to help us with this process.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_009">One of their tasks was to apply the CAISO competitive benchmark pricing methodology to the Northwest market.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_010">That is, CRA attempted to reverse engineer the CAISO's methodology in order to estimate our Northwest risk.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_011">I was informed by our litigation team that EPMI's realistic potential exposure using this methodology was roughly $30 million.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_012">We decided to reserve roughly 2/3 of this amount which came to about $21 million.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_013">In September a FERC Adminitrative Law Judge heard the case and submitted a draft decision to the FERC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_014">The draft decision recommended against any refunds.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_015">This draft decision is supposed to come in front of the FERC commissioners for approval before the end of the year.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS095_016">If this draft decision is approved, it would be appropriate to remove these reserves.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
