<root><thread><filename>germany-c_personal_12.txt</filename><name>MRI Information
</name><id>ECS021</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 17 Apr 2002 16:29:03 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>jeffk@schouston.com
</from><to>edmund.cooper@enron.com
</to><subject>MRI Information
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS021_001">Chris,   Thanks again for taking a few moments  to speak with me.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_002">We appreciate you letting us help you out in preparing  for your impending "life after Enron."
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_003">Please don't be overwhelmed by the  detail we ask for in the forms.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_004">The reason we ask for such detail is that  this information, along with your resume and any verbal help you can offer, is  what we will use in preparing a marketing presentation for whichever suitors you  choose.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_005">We take this information, work with you to promote your most  attractive professional assets, and hope to create a bidding war for your  services.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_006">With the quality of people that are in the market right  now (most of whom you know and/or used to work with), we are finding that some  companies will even make an opening for the right person with the right track  record.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_007">Your ability to create $1.6 million last year, while working under  Enron's credit issues, will speak highly of you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_008">I am sure that  we will find you a new position when you are ready.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_009">At MRI,  we are growing our credibility and increasing our options with every placement;  be sure to thank the guys you know that we have placed when we get you a better  position than what they have!
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_010">In addition to this information, we also need you to put  together a list of companies (as many as you can think of) that you would like  to work for and a list of 12 references.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_011">I'm sure Al told you most of  that, but I just wanted make sure.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_012">Don't put yourself under too much  pressure to get that stuff done completely; we'll work through whatever you want  clarified over the phone.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_013">If you have any questions at all, please don't hesitate  to call me at 713/627-0880.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_014">You can also e-mail me at jeffk@schouston.com .
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_015">Thanks again for  letting us help you out.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS021_016">Sincerely, 
</sentence><signature>Jeff Keene  - MRI Stationary.gif  - CAREER DEVELOPMENT WORKSHEETmaster.doc  - past achievements.doc </signature></text></email></thread></root>
