<root><thread><filename>jones-t_sent_88.txt</filename><name>Re: Merrill
</name><id>ECS068</id><email order="1"><date>Thu, 3 Jun 1999 04:58:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>tana.jones@enron.com
</from><to>carol.clair@enron.com
</to><subject>Re: Merrill
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS068_001">I'm working on the Merrill/Belco assignment of trades with, I guess, Sara.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_002">Mark Taylor signed off yesterday on the assignment that appears to again have been executed by Fred without Legal's initials.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_003">It appears the date Fred signed it is about the time Mark Taylor talked to him about not signing contractual documents without Legal's initials.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_004">There appears to be two differences in the redone confirms Merrill sent us: 
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_005">(1)  they added a Fallback Reference Price, and (2) they have changed the settlement and/or payment dates in the confirms.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_006">Bernice said Sara signed off on a similar Fallback Reference Price in some confirms she had previously done with Merrill, so I briefly discussed this with Sara before she had to leave for lunch.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_007">We'll look at it some more after lunch.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_008">On the change in the settlement/payment dates, I told Bernice they were changing the deal and she needed the business guy on the transactions to sign off on that change.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_009">She was going to take the confirms to Fred and get him to sign off that that is what he's agreed to.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_010">Now, if Sara doesn't know anything about the additional Fallback Reference Price, we'll obviously have to take that back to the dealmaker to sign off on too.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_011">Are you also working on this?
</sentence><sentence id="ECS068_012">So that's what's going on...
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
