<root><thread><filename>jones-t_sent_451.txt</filename><name>Re: What's New
</name><id>ECS031</id><email order="1"><date>Mon, 1 Nov 1999 02:43:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>tana.jones@enron.com
</from><to>fishkinc@hotmail.com
</to><subject>Re: What's New
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS031_001">Now that the cat is out of the bag I can tell you about the other big project I have been working on.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_002">The press releases went out last week.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_003">Mark Taylor was also the host of this year's ECT Legal Conference (which takes alot of work to put together!), which we just had on Thursday and Friday.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_004">You may have read in the papers about our new Enron Online, our new web based commodity trading system.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_005">You can view it at www.EnronOnline.com.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_006">Mark has been the lead attorney on that project which has been an enormous amount of work for him.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_007">Besides being Mark's aide-de-camp on EOL generally, I have been working on the counterparty approval lists for the financial contracts, which has meant going through every counterparty we have to determine whether we should approve them for online trading.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_008">As you can imagine, that has meant looking at thousands of counterparties, contracts and legal issues and trading restrictions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_009">As far as my "Fishkin" project (as Mark and I call it), I recently went to an internal class on Project Management and am redefining my project goals, objectives, etc.  
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_010">We've found a few new software programs we've been looking at, some we found out Enron already has.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_011">Mark and I are discussing what we've seen, defining and redefining what we want, and hope to finalize our thoughts soon.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_012">Mark and I are currently designing the swap jurisdictional database in a Lotus Notes format, and hope this week to get the computer people to design the software.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_013">This would be my database of foreign derivative laws, ISDA opinions and the like.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_014">We need that up and going desperately.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_015">We, have been having to look alot at foreign laws for the online trading project as well as general trading questions lately, and it should be a slam dunk to put this database together and start loading the information.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_016">So that's been what I've been up to, let me know your thoughts about EOL!  
</sentence><sentence id="ECS031_017">P.S.  Thanks for the article!
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
