<root><thread><filename>martin-t_inbox_383.txt</filename><name>Lunch Budget
</name><id>ECS023</id><email order="1"><date>Tue, 9 Oct 2001 15:13:27 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>laura.vuittonet@enron.com
</from><to>a..martin@enron.com
</to><subject>Lunch Budget
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS023_001">Tom, I probably should have explained what my problems are, and why it took me so long to get this to you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_002">Daniel is the person in charge of the lunches, and he has not had an opportunity to prepare the monthly spreadsheets for August and September, which show the total amounts per day, and how much each cost center is charged.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_003">He's come up with a percentage, according to how many total people he orders for, then according to how many people are in each group, and he charges each cost center accordingly.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_004">I've attached the 2 worksheets that he's provided me, which are for June and July, however there were fewer people in our group because since then he has added Brian Redmond and his group to our budget.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_005">Daniel is working on preparing the spreadsheets for August and September.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_006">I've told Ina that I'm needing them for a project for you, so I'm sure that they will be ready soon.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_007">I thought that I could just look at what's been charged to our cost center each month, but it was too difficult to figure out which invoices were from which lunch because they don't always hit the cost center the month during or after they were invoiced.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_008">They are also sometimes charged on a credit card and then billed in a huge lump sum.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_009">I've simply made a spreadsheet showing selected restaurants and the average price of what we've been charged for June and July, and then I've shown what it will cost for 15 people to eat if we order it separately.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_010">I've included tips and delivery charges, since we're billed for those as well.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS023_011">Let's talk about it tomorrow.
</sentence><signature>Laura</signature></text></email></thread></root>
