<root><thread><filename>jones-t_sent_502.txt</filename><name>Re: Lower Colorado River Authority-see Lotus Notes
</name><id>ECS010</id><email order="1"><date>Mon, 29 Nov 1999 09:50:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>tana.jones@enron.com
</from><to>tanya.rohauer@enron.com
</to><subject>Re: Lower Colorado River Authority-see Lotus Notes
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS010_001">I asked  Richard Ramirez if there was a business contact and he said he didn't know, but he was going to get back to me.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_002">I think in his job in Fuel and Energy Risk Management, he is probably the business contact.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_003">He probably makes the decisions about fuel purchases and derivatives hedging.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_004">He also wanted to get a power enabling agreement in place.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_005">I spoke to Liz Sager and she said we already had a power trade on the books and except for authority issues, there was no reason not to do financial energy.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_006">As far as sending my Lotus Notes comment, I just did that manually.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_007">I spoke to the Lotus Notes people before I went on vacation, and among other changes, they are going to try and fix it so we can just click on the email address and it will notify people to see Lotus Notes.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_008">Of course, the only groups that will have access to the comment sections of Lotus Notes (for confidentiality purposes) will continue to be Legal and Credit.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_009">But we are going to open everything but the comments and "priority" screens to any interested business people.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_010">I'm going to move the "restrictions" bar right after the name so when the business people look the first thing they will see will be any restrictions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS010_011">Then, I'm going to add a drop down for online trading, approved or not, and then a comment screen (that only Legal and Credit can see) so we will have some notes about why we approved them or not (some of us are getting old and can't remember things!).
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
