<root><thread><filename>scott-s_inbox_106.txt</filename><name>Important Message
</name><id>ECS038</id><email order="1"><date>Sun, 9 Sep 2001 16:53:53 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>40enron@enron.com
</from><to>gary.bryan@enron.com
</to><subject>Important Message
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS038_001">It is my sincere honor to once again lead the Enron team in this year's Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation (JDRF) Walk scheduled to take place on Sunday, October 28th, at Greenspoint Mall.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_002">I continue to serve on the board of JDRF representing Enron and will be Enron's corporate executive for this year's fundraising efforts.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_003">As many of you may already know, I am an insulin dependent diabetic myself.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_004">Even though I know how difficult this disease can be to manage with the multiple finger pricks for blood samples and several shots each day, I cannot imagine how difficult it is for a small child with this disease.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_005">Taking insulin does not cure the disease nor prevent the development of complications; insulin is simply their life support system and without it they would die.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_006">Enron continues to be a major corporate sponsor for JDRF again this year.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_007">JDRF is a very efficient organization in which approximately 85% of all money raised goes directly to research.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_008">Enron's goal this year is to raise $400,000 and we need your help.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_009">Enron has been the number 1 walk team for 6 years in a row and we are not ready to give up first place!
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_010">We need team leaders, walkers and volunteers to help us reach our goal.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_011">The theme for the walk this year is "Mission: Possible" and we would like to have you join us for this great event.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_012">The Walk is truly a blast and we had about 600 Enron people participate last year and everyone enjoyed it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_013">If you are interested in volunteering to be a walker or a team leader, or if you would like to make a pledge, you may call any of the steering committee members listed below.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_014">If you are interested in being a team leader, please contact one of the following people immediately so that you may be included in the first important and informative training session taking place this week.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_015">In addition, you may go to cr.enron.com and sign up as a volunteer online if you prefer.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS038_016">Thank you very much for your support.
</sentence><signature>Mike McConnell </signature></text></email></thread></root>
