<root><thread><filename>lavorato-j_inbox_321.txt</filename><name>Jeff McMahon Named CFO
</name><id>ECS037</id><email order="1"><date>Wed, 24 Oct 2001 13:50:19 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>no.address@enron.com
</from><to>gary.bryan@enron.com
</to><subject>Jeff McMahon Named CFO
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS037_001">Today we announced the appointment of Jeff McMahon as Enron's chief financial officer.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_002">In my continued discussions with the financial community yesterday and today, it became clear that this move was required to restore investor confidence.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_003">Jeff has unparalleled qualifications and a deep and thorough understanding of Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_004">He is already on the job and hard at work on the issues before us.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_005">Andy Fastow will be on a leave of absence from the company.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_006">Jeff had been serving as chairman and CEO of Enron Industrial Markets.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_007">He joined Enron in 1994 and spent three years in the London office as chief financial officer for Enron's European operations.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_008">Upon returning to the U.S., Jeff was executive vice president of finance and treasurer for Enron Corp.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_009">In 2000, he was named president and chief operating officer of Enron Net Works.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_010">I know all of you are concerned about the continuing decline in our share price.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_011">I am too, and we are working very hard to turn it around.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_012">Appointing Jeff as CFO is one important step in that process.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_013">But most of the solution involves just continuing to do our jobs with excellence.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_014">The fundamentals of our business are strong, and I think the market will begin to see that as we continue to perform.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS037_015">Please join me in giving Jeff your full support, and thank you for all of your continued hard work.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
