<root><thread><filename>gilbertsmith-d_personal_22.txt</filename><name>Gas Meeting
</name><id>ECS022</id><email order="1"><date>Tue, 24 Apr 2001 22:38:00 -0700 (PDT)
</date><from>larry.jester@enron.com
</from><to>doug.gilbert-smith@enron.com
</to><subject>Gas Meeting
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS022_001">Doug,  I had two very positive meetings this evening  with Tom Martin and Jim Schwieger.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_002">They are looking for a Carthage Hub physical trader.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_003">Tom is planning on talking I think to Lavorato to discuss the details.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_004">It's interesting because with the HPL sale now their physical guys are moving into an environment where they don't have an asset to trade around and have to be flat daily.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_005">Gee, I wonder what that's like?
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_006">Given ERCOT liquidity and vol I had to chuckle on the inside (welcome to the real world).
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_007">I really appreciate your support during all of this.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_008">Some bosses could consider a situation like this a slight against them and bear out their resentment personally or to others to stymie that person's movement.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_009">You have been nothing but a class act in that regard, and although I indeed would have liked a look at the ST-ERCOT book, I don't hold that against you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_010">In fact I don't even hold it against management.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_011">It's no different than trading.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_012">Just because someone smart is selling it doesn't mean it won't get bid up and run through them.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_013">I am confident that wherever I end up I will be successful -- no different than any other time in my life.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_014">I don't know another way.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_015">The one time that I had some short-term hardship last year, you and I agree that I was sold too early, and that too will become self-evident.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_016">As I stated yesterday, the end of this week looks to be the time frame where I will make my a final decision.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS022_017">Thanks for all of you runderstanding, 
</sentence><signature>Larry </signature></text></email></thread></root>
