<root><thread><filename>jones-t_sent_459.txt</filename><name>Re: EOL CP's with Masters using GTC's
</name><id>ECS078</id><email order="1"><date>Thu, 4 Nov 1999 02:25:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>tana.jones@enron.com
</from><to>karen.lambert@enron.com
</to><subject>Re: EOL CP's with Masters using GTC's
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS078_001">Thanks for your email.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_002">It is important on a going forward basis that if we veer from any restriction that Legal has placed on a counterparty (e.g. if Credit says it is ok to trade weather under a GTC instead of a master) that Legal hear before we trade so we all make sure we are on the same understanding as to whether any restriction should be waived.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_003">In response to your email I have the following comments:  
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_004">1.The New York Times Company:  cannot trade derivatives online at all.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_005">Their board resolution and master agreement require that two specific officers must enter into the trade together on a telephone call.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_006">They cannot trade any other way without revising their board resolution and agreement.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_007">All their  trades must be done by telephone.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_008">2.  San Diego Gas &amp; Electric Company:  the California PUC said that utilities such as San Diego cannot enter into derivatives transactions at all! 
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_009">3.  Aspect Resources:  can enter into derivative transactions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_010">We want the transactions to roll up under the existing ISDA Master Agreement between ECT and Aspect.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_011">4.  Brant-Allen Industries:  Is shut down, more or less, for all financial trading.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_012">They cannot enter into another derivative transactions with us, either on the phone or online, until, prior to entering into the trade, they provide us with a board resolution approving the trade or derivative trading in general.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_013">The board resolution they provided with the signed master agreement only approved the one trade we entered into at that time. 
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_014">5.  Cox &amp; Perkins:    We had a master with this counterparty and they have informed us i writing that they didn't want to trade with us anymore.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_015">In reality, if they did another trade, Legal will need to be contacted and we probably would try and reactive the master and roll the trade up under the master if possible.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_016">Credit, keep us informed if they do trade.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_017">6.  Sonoco Products:  We should not be trading with them at all until we resolve this payment dispute.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_018">Sara Shackleton was working on that.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS078_019">We do have a master with them, and if we resolve the payment dispute and begin trading with them, the trade should roll up under the existing master.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
