<root><thread><filename>kaminski-v_personal_297.txt</filename><name>MS 150
</name><id>ECS063</id><email order="1"><date>Fri, 3 Mar 2000 00:50:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>john.norden@enron.com
</from><to>jnorden@enron.com
</to><subject>MS 150
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS063_001">Dear Friends and Family,  On April 15 and 16 I will be joining thousands of riders and volunteers on the MS 150 which is a two day bike tour from Houston to Austin covering 182 miles dedicated to end the devastating effects of multiple sclerosis.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_002">Multiple sclerosis is a disease that is total unpredictable.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_003">Symptoms may be mild such as numbness in the limbs, or severe paralysis or loss of vision.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_004">Most people with MS are diagnosed between the ages of 20 and 40 but the unpredictable physical and emotional effects can be lifelong  
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_005">My wife, Ilene was diagnosed with MS almost three years ago; at first I was at a loss of how I could support her.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_006">That was until I heard of the MS 150, which is one of the greatest challenges of my life.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_007">It is my choice to participate in the MS 150, Ilene does not have a choice, as she has to live with MS every day.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_008">This will be my third year riding in the MS 150 raising money for the National MS Society to fight multiple sclerosis.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_009">In 1998 my goal was simple.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_010">It was to raise money and ride the 182 miles on my own.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_011">I succeeded in my endeavor by completing the ride on my own steam and raising $6,000.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_012">In 1999 I raised my goal to $10,000 and finished the tour.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_013">Not only did I meet my goal, but surpassed it by raising $15,000 to fight this devastating disease with the help of my friends and family.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_014">This year my goal is even greater!
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_015">My wife and I are once again asking for your help.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_016">This year on the 2000 MS 150 bike tour, my goal is to raise $20,000.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_017">Enron is a big supporter of the MS 150.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_018">For the past two years we were the largest bike team and biggest fundraiser of any corporate team nationally.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_019">Last year we raised $310,000 with 300 riders.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_020">Enron will match dollar for dollar on all contributions donated in my name.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_021">Using this secure, fast and easy web page you can make a tax-deductible donation (if clicking on the link below does not work you can cut and paste the link to your browser).
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_022">https://secure2.ntwebhosting.com/ms150/donate.asp?RiderName=John+Norden&amp;RiderE mail=jnorden%40enron%2Ecom  If you would prefer to send a check it should be made out to the National MS Society and sent to the address below.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_023">I appreciate your continued support of the MS Society and the Isuzu MS 150 Bike Tour.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_024">The funds raised on the Isuzu MS 150 Bike Tour provides equipment, financial assistance, self-help groups, counseling, information and resources, as well as education for people with MS and their families.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_025">Your support truly makes a difference in the lives of people with Multiple Sclerosis.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_026">For additional information on MS http://www.nmss.org
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_027">For additional information the MS 150 http://www.ms150.org
</sentence><sentence id="ECS063_028">Thank You for Your Support, 
</sentence><signature>John Norden John Norden Director Technology Enron 1400 Smith St Houston TX 77002 713/853-3240</signature></text></email></thread></root>
