<root><thread><filename>dasovich-j_personal_35.txt</filename><name>Welcome to Traffic School To Go!
</name><id>ECS009</id><email order="1"><date>Sun, 7 Nov 1999 12:48:00 -0800 (PST)
</date><from>help@trafficschooltogo.com
</from><to>jeff.dasovich@enron.com
</to><subject>Welcome to Traffic School To Go!
</subject><text><sentence id="ECS009_001">Nov 7, 1999 12:48 PM  Jeffrey Dasovich,  Your registration for the Traffic School To Go program has been recorded.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_002">We hope that everything is clear and that you will have no problem successfully completing the program but if you need help, please reply to this Email with your questions or phone toll free - (888) 349-8425.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_003">Remember, this is EXACTLY how you will need to re-enter your information when logging back in to the program:  license state = California license number= N7889351  To log into the course, visit the following URL: http://www.trafficschooltogo.com/students/
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_004">If you find you have made an error in entering your license information, use the incorrect information to log in.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_005">Once logged in, you will have the option of correcting the error by hitting the "Personal Information" button on your "Student Control Panel" at the bottom of any page.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_006">Thereafter, the corrected license information will log you in.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_007">Oh, and just to confirm, we have the following mailing address information for you:  366 Dolores St., #3 San Francisco, CA 94110  If this is incorrect, use your "Personal Information" button to fix it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_008">In fact, please be sure to double-check (and change if necessary) all of your "Personal Information" sometime before you finish so that we can reach you if there's a problem or so that your certificate does not go astray due to a typo in your mailing address.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_009">Thanks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECS009_010">Sincerely,  
</sentence><signature>Peggy Goldman Traffic School To Go http://www.trafficschooltogo.com (888) 349-8425</signature></text></email></thread></root>
