<root><thread><filename>lay-k_inbox_245.txt</filename><name>  Appointment</name><id>ECT005</id><email order="1"><date> Sat, 27 Jan 2001 08:31:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>   Krdicker@aol.com@ENRON</from><to>     Lay, Kenneth</to><subject>  Appointment</subject><text><sentence id="ECT005_001">Ken,  Ben Streetman, Dean of the UT School of Engineering, tells me that he  will be in Houston on November 14 and would like to meet with you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_002">I  realize that your schedule is overflowing these days; however, should  time permit, the Dean would sincerely appreciate an opportunity to visit  with you for a few minutes.
</sentence><signature> Thank you.  Kenneth R. Dickerson </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Sat, 27 Jan 2001 08:31:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Kenneth.Lay@enron.com [&lt;mailto:Kenneth.Lay@enron.com]</from><to> IMCEANOTES-Krdicker+40aol+2Ecom+40ENRON@ENRON.com</to><subject> RE: Appointment</subject><text><sentence id="ECT005_003">Hi Mr. Dickerson -  I apologize for the delay in getting back with you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_004">If it would still be convenient for Dean Streetman, Ken Lay can meet with him the morning of November 14 - possibly 9:30 a.m.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_005">Please let me know.
</sentence><signature>Rosalee Fleming Assistant to Ken Lay 713-853-6088 </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Sat, 27 Jan 2001 08:31:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>   John Halton &lt;halton@mail.utexas.edu@ENRON</from><to>     Lay, Kenneth</to><subject>        RE: Appointment</subject><text><sentence id="ECT005_006">Ken, I have confirmed the appointment with Ken Lay for 9:30 a.m. on November 14. Thanks very much for arranging this.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_007">I look forward to seeing you on November 1 at GlenEagles at 9:00.
</sentence><signature>John </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Sat, 27 Jan 2001 08:31:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Fleming, Rosalee on behalf of Lay, Kenneth</from><to> Patrick, Christie</to><subject> FW: Appointment</subject><text><sentence id="ECT005_008">Hi Christie -  Would you be able to join Ken in this meeting?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_009">As you can see, we don't have a lot of information.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_010">If you feel it would be good to talk to John Halton (who will also be attending the meeting with Dean Ben Streetman), he can be reached at 512-471-2120.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_011">Thanks much and take care.
</sentence><signature>Rosie </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Thu, 25 Oct 2001 16:19:51 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Patrick, Christie &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=CPATRIC</from><to>X- Lay, Kenneth &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=KLAY, Fleming, Rosalee &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Rflemin</to><subject> RE: Appointment</subject><text><sentence id="ECT005_012">Rosie...absolutely!! I'll make my schedule work.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_013">However, unless this is a personal favor Ken is doing for the gentlemen involved, I'd also be happy to "field" this for him.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_014">I told Ken we(University Affairs/Public Affairs) would not impose on his schedule for these kinds of visits until after January.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_015">Clearly, there are occasions where some of Ken's many friends contact him directly, and , as kind as Ken is, even at extreme times, he agrees.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_016">However, if this is not a personal visit, I'm quite certain this dean is looking for a better financial and recruiting relationship with Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_017">In fact, we are putting together a "master Plan"" financial relationship with UT overall (Rick Causey is the exec lead), and realistically, we are not recruiting engineers per se.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_018">So Rosie my darling friend, let me know if you'd like me to politely intervene and take this off your list, or if this is one of those personal friendship situations, in which case, I'll be there on the 14th!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT005_019">Thanks and kisses!!
</sentence><signature>--Christie. </signature></text></email></thread></root>
