<root><thread><filename>cash-m_inbox_18.txt</filename><name> lake worth project</name><id>ECT059</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 8 Oct 2001 08:40:14 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Mike.Indivero@nepco.com</from><to> mark.stubley@odnss.com</to><subject> lake worth project</subject><text><sentence id="ECT059_001">mark...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_002">where are with possibly of obtaining local counsel  for the lake worth  project?..
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_003">have we reviewed the fence/gate issue and come to  some  conclusions?...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_004">also what about the training we discussed?...  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_005">pls let me know
</sentence><signature> ..thanks...mike </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 8 Oct 2001 08:40:14 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Stubley, Mark [mailto:StubleMM@odnss.com]</from><to> 'Mike.Indivero@nepco.com'</to><subject> RE: lake worth project</subject><text><sentence id="ECT059_006">I forwarded our recommendation for local counsel to Michelle  Cash.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_007">She  indicated that Enron might want to use another firm.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_008">In the  meantime, we  will continue to use Cole Fitzgerald.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_009">On September 24, I  copied you (as  well as Michelle Cash and David Lund) on Cole's  correspondence concerning  his meeting with the mayor of Lake Worth.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_010">So, his  connections should prove  helpful.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_011">Lund has provided me a copy of NEPCO's subcontract.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_012">Our  review and comments  should be complete by Friday.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_013">We conducted the quick, over-the-phone training for the  management team at  Lake Worth approximately two weeks ago.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_014">We agreed to  conduct on-site  training when more of the project management team is present  at the site.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_015">No  specific time is scheduled.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_016">We have not received a plat for the project.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_017">We have not  determined the gate  setup.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_018">We have determined, however, that all construction  traffic and  deliveries would use the southern gate, not the main gate to  the facility.
</sentence><signature>   </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 8 Oct 2001 08:40:14 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>	B-Mike Indivero</from><to>	B-David Lund</to><subject>	FW: lake worth project</subject><text><sentence id="ECT059_019">David...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_020">fyi...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_021">thought this would have been resolved by  now...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_022">does our movement over to egs change the counsel we work with within  Enron?...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_023">hate to see us not have local counsel ready to go if/when  needed...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_024">setting this up is a minimal cost item...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_025">( by the way staff  training for union avoidance and preventing harassment conducted by odnss  is set up for 11/6)...suggestions/thoughts...
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_026">let me know
</sentence><signature>...thanks...Mike  </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 8 Oct 2001 08:40:14 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	B-David Lund</from><to>	B-Mike Indivero</to><subject>	RE: lake worth project</subject><text><sentence id="ECT059_027">Mike,  I know of no hold up here.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_028">I spoke to Michelle Cash and she had not  withheld or said different to retaining this counsel.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_029">I would suggest  that you call Michelle (713-853-6401) anytime you have a concern with  regard to the progress of any labor and employment matter handled by  outside or inside counsel.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_030">And if Stubley is concerned about who he would  like to work with in Florida, he is equally able to call Michelle and  discuss it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_031">As for a review of the training on union avoidance by Ogletree Deakins, by  copy to Michelle, I'll ask for her input here.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_032">I saw the correspondence from Mr. Fitzgerald regarding his meeting with  the Mayor of Lake Worth.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_033">I interpret this as a public official saying  what is expected, neither favoring the picketers or us, just saying he  will up-hold the law.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_034">We appreciate that.
</sentence><signature> David H. Lund, Jr.  Assistant General Counsel  National Energy Production Corporation  11831 North Creek Parkway N.  Bothell, WA 98011  425-415-3138  Fax: 425-415-3032  David.Lund@nepco.com or davidlu@nepco.com  </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Fri, 5 Oct 2001 08:44:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Mike.Indivero@nepco.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-Mike+2EIndivero+40nepco+2Ecom+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Lund, David &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=FOREIGN CONTACTS/CN=NEPCO/CN=DLUND</to><subject> RE: lake worth project</subject><text><sentence id="ECT059_035">I'll give Michelle a call.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT059_036">I assume she will remain as the Enron contact for NEPCO?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
