<root><thread><filename>donoho_inbox_junk_file_131.txt</filename><name>	SCG Advice 2837-A</name><id>ECT003</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 27 Nov 2001 14:13:22 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	"Dan Douglass" &lt;douglass@energyattorney.com@ENRON</from><to>	Hass, Glen; Harris, Steven</to><subject>	SCG Advice 2837-A</subject><text><sentence id="ECT003_001">Glen and Steve:  The attached supplemental advice filing by SoCalGas replaces the changes to Rule 30, Transportation of Customer-Owned Gas, proposed by AL2837.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_002">The purpose of this filing is to describe the new internal receipt point operating procedures that SoCalGas is implementing, and to request Commission authorization to include the revised operating procedures in Rule 30.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_003">SoCalGas says this step is being taken in anticipation that it will be replaced with a system of firm tradable intrastate transmission rights in Gas Industry Restructuring (GIR) proceeding, I.99-07-003.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_004">During the GIR panel hearings, several parties requested that SoCalGas publish its windowing criteria in tariffs to facilitate a better understanding of the method used to allocate receipt point capacity.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_005">SoCalGas agreed to make such a filing, and D.99-07-015 directed SoCalGas to file an advice letter adding windowing information to its tariffs.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_006">To comply with this directive, on August 6, 1999, SoCalGas filed AL2837, which has not been acted on by the Commission.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_007">Customer complaints about SoCalGas' windowing procedures have convinced SoCalGas that it should replace its internal windowing operating procedures with a system that is open to the maximum operating capacity at each SoCalGas receipt point.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_008">SoCalGas is making these internal operating changes effective November 1, 2001.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_009">SoCalGas held meetings with upstream pipelines on October 17, and with interested customers and stakeholders on October 18, regarding the upcoming changes.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_010">They were invited to ask any questions in the days leading up to the meetings.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_011">Comments and/or protests are due on November 21.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_012">Have a good weekend!
</sentence><signature>Dan Law Offices of Daniel W. Douglass 5959 Topanga Canyon Blvd.  Suite  244 Woodland Hills, CA 91367 Tel:   (818) 596-2201 Fax:   (818) 346-6502douglass@energyattorney.com &lt;&lt; File: mailto:douglass@energyattorney.com  - AL2837-A.PDF &lt;&lt; File: AL2837-A.PDF </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Tue, 27 Nov 2001 14:13:22 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Harris, Steven</from><to>	Donoho, Lindy</to><subject>	FW: SCG Advice 2837-A</subject><text><sentence id="ECT003_013">Lindy , can you please take a look at this and let me know if we should file comments.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_014">Thanks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_015">You might see if Glen has looked at it yet.
</sentence><signature> Steve </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Tue, 27 Nov 2001 14:13:22 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Donoho, Lindy</from><to>	Rapp, Bill; Hass, Glen; Blair, Lynn; Harris, Steven; Kowalke, Terry; Lokey, Teb; Kilmer III, Robert; #99 Tech Support,; Watson, Kimberly; Lindberg, Lorraine; Lohman, TK</to><subject>	FW: SCG Advice 2837-A</subject><text><sentence id="ECT003_016">After discussing with Lynn and Glen, we think that we would like to file comments in this proceeding concerning an issue we have had since this has been implemented on Nov 1.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_017">In instances where SoCal happens to call their OFO in the Intraday 2 cycle, it can cause Transwestern to have Shipper imbalances because we do not have an opportunity to pass-along these reductions to our upstream parties.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_018">We think we would like to file a letter that may mention our general support of the "direction" of SoCal's changes, but that we do have an issue that has developed since actual implementation that we are currently working on with them.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_019">Lynn &amp; I worked on this rough general description we thought could be incorporated into a brief letter.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_020">"If SoCal calls an OFO in the Intraday 2 Cycle, an allocation is passed to Transwestern through the confirmation process with SoCal.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_021">Due to the timing of these OFO's, Transwestern is unable to confirm such reductions with Transwestern's upstream parties."
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_022">Lynn thinks if we are unable to resolve this issue with SoCal, TW could have high Shipper imbalance exposure.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Fri, 16 Nov 2001 14:54:44 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Watson, Kimberly &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=KWATSON</from><to>X- Donoho, Lindy &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ldonoho, Rapp, Bill &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Brapp, Hass, Glen &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ghass, Blair, Lynn &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Lblair, Harris, Steven &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Sharris1, Kowalke, Terry &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Tkowalk, Lokey, Teb &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Tlokey, Kilmer III, Robert &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Rkilmer, #99 Tech Support, &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Notesaddr/cn=6dc63ad-f586aeb5-862566ef-6eede6, Lindberg, Lorraine &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Llindbe, Lohman, TK &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Tlohman</to><subject> RE: SCG Advice 2837-A</subject><text><sentence id="ECT003_023">Lindy, thanks for looking into this.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT003_024">I agree with your comments.
</sentence><signature>Kim. </signature></text></email></thread></root>
