<root><thread><filename>delainey-d_inbox_32.txt</filename><name>	EES Employee Issues</name><id>ECT018</id><email order="1"><date> Thu, 6 Sep 2001 09:39:19 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Delainey, David W.</from><to>	Pieper, Kalen; Brown, Daniel</to><subject>	EES Employee Issues</subject><text><sentence id="ECT018_001">Guys, can you please provide an update/status and plan to manage the following EES employee issues:   
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_002">a) Steve Borden - moving issues on sale of house and furniture;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_003">b) Faye Worthy - moving issues on furniture and apartment;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_004">c) Stuart Rexrode - moving issues on furniture, etc;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_005">d) Kevin Greiner - moving issues, etc;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_006">e) Steven Peterson - moving issues, etc;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_007">Great job on Maureen.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_008">Kalen are you aware of any other EES employee issues (such as what we spoke about on Friday) where I can help.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_009">I believe Dan is looking at this as well.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_010">Do we think it might be a good idea to have a meeting to discuss globally?
</sentence><signature>Regards Delainey </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Thu, 6 Sep 2001 09:39:19 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Leff, Dan</from><to>	Delainey, David W.; Pieper, Kalen; Brown, Daniel</to><subject>	RE: EES Employee Issues</subject><text><sentence id="ECT018_011">Dan Brown will have a complete list of EES employees, by exposure, with $'s and explanation of situation by 12noon on 12/12/01.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_012">Until then, he and Kalen are managing each case 1 x 1.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_013">Once we have the info in hand, we can meet to discuss the next best steps.
</sentence><signature>Dan </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Thu, 6 Sep 2001 09:39:19 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Brown, Daniel</from><to>	Callahan, Timothy; Whiteurst, Lloyd</to><subject>	FW: EES Employee Issues</subject><text><sentence id="ECT018_014">Tim/Lloyd,  As you can see from the emails below, EES leadership is extremely concerned about our exposure to both domestic and international relocations.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_015">I need to obtain the information on our folks by 11:00 a.m.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_016">today so that I can prepare and deliver a document to them.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_017">Please let me know if this will be a problem.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Daniel </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Thu, 6 Sep 2001 09:39:19 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Whiteurst, Lloyd</from><to>	Brown, Daniel; Callahan, Timothy</to><subject>	RE: EES Employee Issues</subject><text><sentence id="ECT018_018">Daniel,  Per our conversation earlier, I am responding to some of your more urgent employee situations:  Faye Worthy -  Faye was one of the individuals who received a letter from All Relo-Services, Inc/Road Runner Moving &amp; Storage regarding non payment of her moving bill.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_019">A number of suppliers hand delivered invoices to Enron on Friday, November 30th.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_020">When information was released on Sunday regarding Enron's filing for bankruptcy, many of the suppliers got extremely nervous.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_021">Faye Worthy's moving bill was for $9,293.69.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_022">On Friday, December 7th., the moving company sent out demand letters to about 33 current and former Enron employees demanding immediate payment since Enron had not yet paid the moving bills.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_023">We were advised that no payments could be made at this time.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_024">Outstanding issues for Faye Worthy:  Unpaid household goods bill - $9,293.69
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_025">Unpaid Temporary Living $8,400.00
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_026">($4,500 per month - November &amp; December unpaid)  It is my understanding that Faye Worthy was going to make the temporary living payments and Judy Gray was going to reimburse her.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_027">The household goods bill remains unpaid.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_028">We are awaiting instructions on how and when the outstanding invoices can be paid.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_029">Stephen Borden  Outstanding issues:  Household goods were not delivered on 12/03/01 as scheduled.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_030">The moving company (Xonex) decided not to release his shipment due to Enron's bankruptcy filing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_031">The amount of the household goods bill is $12,057.38.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_032">New Home Closing Costs - Mr. Borden was scheduled to be reimbursed for his new home closing costs of $22,600.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_033">Mr. Borden purchased his new home and closed on 11/30/01.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_034">He paid all of the closing costs.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_035">When the relocation department received his reimbursement documentation, it was to late to process due to the bankruptcy filing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_036">Per George Wasaff and Judy Gray, they were scheduled to pay Mr. Borden $15,000 maximum including $4,500 severance for all relocation and business expenses.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_037">Mr. Borden has $10,000 in business travel expenses that has not been reimbursed.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_038">Recap:  Household Goods - not paid $12,057.38
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_039">New Home Closing Costs $22,600.00
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_040">(Paid by Borden and not yet reimbursed) Business Travel Expenses - $10,000 (Paid by Borden and not yet reimbursed) Final Move Expenses - not paid $235.00
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_041">Stuart Rexrode -  Outstanding issues:  Mr. Rexrode has been contacted by Prudential household goods moving company.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_042">At this point, his shipment has not yet taken place.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_043">Kevin Greiner -  Air shipment has been received.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_044">His ocean shipment is currently in storage with Transportation Worldwide, Inc., (Houston, TX) pending receipt of payment.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_045">Steven Peterson -  Since December 06, 01, shipment has been held in storage by Transportation Worldwide, Inc. (Houston, TX).
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Wed, 12 Dec 2001 09:28:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Brown, Daniel &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DBROWN4</from><to>X- Leff, Dan &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Dleff, Delaney, David &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ddelaney</to><subject> FW: EES Employee Issues</subject><text><sentence id="ECT018_046">Dan/Dave,  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_047">We are working to gather as much information as possible on our exposure to relocated former and current domestic and international employees impacted by Enron's bankruptcy filing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_048">Lloyd has outlined our position on the urgent issues below.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_049">Please keep in mind that regardless of our obligation, the courts have only approved $15K per employee for all expenses less the $4500 payment if applicable.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT018_050">We will continue to work on getting a comprehensive listing over the next couple of days.
</sentence><signature>Daniel </signature></text></email></thread></root>
