<root><thread><filename>stejjes-j_sent_items_2288.txt</filename><name>     Re: Draft</name><id>ECT035</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Karen.Shea@dynegy.com [mailto:Karen.Shea@dynegy.com]</from><to>&lt;kristiwallis@sprin             "Greenleaf,</to><subject>     Re: Draft</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_001">Steve &amp; Kristi-   Steve, thanks very much for circulating a draft summary of last week's  meeting.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_002">Also, I appreciate Kristi's clarification in her e-mail below.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_003">From Dynegy's perspective, we would oppose the MMU having police and  enforcement power.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_004">The MMU should monitor the market and RTO according  to  carefully articulated criteria.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_005">Enforcement should be by those with the  appropriate authority (states, FERC, SEC, etc.).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_006">Unfortunately I was not on the call for the discussion of the role of  the  States, but I would appreciate further discussion in this area.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_007">Also, was there any discussion of a Market Monitoring Committee?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_008">The  idea  would be to establish a Market Monitoring Committee consisting of  representation by stakeholders from each Cooperating RTO.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_009">The Committee  would interface with the independent market monitor, provide input on  appropriate data collection and screens, evaluate the need for  rule/tariff  changes and review and provide comments on periodic reports.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_010">(The  Committee would have no authority to impose fines, penalties, etc.)
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_011">Last week during our meeting I referred to the MISO independent market  monitor model.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_012">The FERC Order Providing Guidance on Continued  Processing  of RTO Filings (issued Nov 7) points to the Midwest ISO, Alliance and  Southwest Power Pool model as a single, regional market monitoring unit.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_013">The ideas in this proposal perhaps will be useful to our efforts here.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_014">Thanks a lot for the opportunity to comment,  Steve --   Thanks for doing such a prompt, thorough, and great job on the notes!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_015">I've  corrected some typos in the attached  red-lined draft.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_016">Also, as you'll see from my comments, I do not believe  that we have yet agreed that the MME should have  a policing/enforcement role (RTO West agrees at a minimum, that there  needs  to be tariff compliance function, but that  could be done by an entity other than the MME; while RTO West is open to  discussing a policing/enforcement role with  respect to market power issues (and may well agree to it), we're not  there  yet.)
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_017">I have prepared and attach a straw dog work plan.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_018">I look forward to  everyone's comments!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_019">I am out of the office today, but will return tomorrow morning.
</sentence><signature> Karen Shea       Kristi Wallis   &lt;kristiwallis@sprin        To:     "Greenleaf,  Steve"  &lt;SGreenleaf@caiso.com  tmail.com                 cc:     "Sheffrin,  Anjali"  &lt;ASheffrin@caiso.com, Dean Perry  &lt;dean.perry@nwpp.org,  "Comnes, Alan" &lt;alan.comnes@enron.com, "'Nabors,  11/12/01 12:56 PM          Ottie F - PMB-6'"  &lt;ofnabors@bpa.gov, "'reinhold@primenet.com'"  Please respond to          &lt;reinhold@primenet.com,  "'Erin Boyd'" &lt;eboyd@ppcpdx.org, "Perrino,  kristiwallis               David"  &lt;Dave.Perrino@enron.com, "'lnichols@bpa.gov'" &lt;lnichols@bpa.gov,  "Hull, Gerit"  &lt;Gerit.Hull@PacifiCorp.com, "Cook, Gregory"  &lt;GCook@caiso.com, "Shea,  Karen" &lt;karen.shea@dynegy.com, Bud Krogh  &lt;ekrogh@serv.net,  "Johns,  Debbie" &lt;DJohns@caiso.com  Subject:     Re: Draft  Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring  Working Group  Meeting        &lt;r  Steve --   Thanks for doing such a prompt, thorough, and great job on the notes!  I've  corrected some typos in the attached  red-lined draft.  Also, as you'll see from my comments, I do not believe  that we have yet agreed that the MME should have  a policing/enforcement role (RTO West agrees at a minimum, that there  needs  to be tariff compliance function, but that  could be done by an entity other than the MME; while RTO West is open to  discussing a policing/enforcement role with  respect to market power issues (and may well agree to it), we're not  there  yet.)   I have prepared and attach a straw dog work plan.  I look forward to  everyone's comments!   I am out of the office today, but will return tomorrow morning.   Thanks, Kristi   P.S.  These are the individuals that I know plan on attending the 11/16  workshop -- Bud Krogh, Dean Perry, Eric Carter  (BPA), Phil Carver (OR Office of Energy), Alan Comnes (Enron, plus one  other Enron rep - Dave Perrino?), Peter Feldman  (BC Hydro -- plus one other BC Hydro rep), Erin Boyd (PPC), Yong Cai  (SMUD), Gerit Hull (PacifiCorp), Phil Muller  (marketers), Lauren Nichols (BPA), Cindy Crane (PacifiCorp), Shep  Buchanan  (BPA), Ottie Nabors (BPA), Peggy Olds (BPA),  Kristi Wallis.  Also, I sent Debbie a head count for the Filing  Utilities  early last week -- I assume that's still good.   "Greenleaf, Steve" wrote:   All,   Attached are my draft notes from yesterday's meeting.  Please send  edits/additions and I will finalize for distribution to SSG-WI.   &lt;&lt;011109 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes.doc    ------------------------------------------------------------------------  Name:  011109  stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes.doc  011109 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes.doc    Type:  WINWORD  File (application/msword)  Encoding:  base64  (See attached file: 011109 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes  (with  KMW Edits).doc)(See attached file: Draft 11.09.01 Work Plan.doc)   &lt;&lt; File: 011112 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes.doc   ------------------------------------------------------------------------  Name: 011112 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes FINAL.doc  011112 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes FINAL.doc    Type: WINWORD File (application/msword)  Encoding: base64 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from>       Greenleaf, Steve [SMTP:SGreenleaf@caiso.com]</from><to> Shea, Karen; kristiwallis@sprintmail.com</to><subject>    RE: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_020">All,   I have revised the meeting notes per Kristi's suggestions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_021">I have  removed  the reference to "policing" as an MMU core function and identified it as  an  issue to be addressed.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_022">Please review and I will distribute to SSG-WI.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_023">Thanks for your time and effort.
</sentence><signature> </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Nabors, Ottie F - PMB-6 [mailto:ofnabors@bpa.gov]</from><to> 'Greenleaf, Steve'; Shea, Karen; kristiwallis@sprintmail.com</to><subject> RE: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_024">After looking at the latest version I have two observations to make given  the earlier e-mails.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_025">1) Concerning the state role, this will be defined within the framework  of  the current FERC process to address just this issue.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_026">For our purposes I  am  not sure that the wording really state how open-ended this issue is for  the  RTO-MMUs or West-wide Monitor until some Federal/State ground rules are in  place.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_027">I think we just need to state our flexibility and openness to work  with the states in areas where interests converge given the concerns Dave  Perrino raised.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_028">2) As for the use of the term audit; I too, am uncomfortable with its  use.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_029">I believe that a more appropriate description of the role of the MMU in  evaluation of the RTOs is to describe the role as one of evaluating the  effectiveness of RTO rules, operations or behavior in promoting the  development of electricity markets.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_030">In other words does the RTO ensure  fair  and open access to the transmission system?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_031">Does it promote a robust and  transparent market for transmission?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_032">Does the operation of the RTO promote  robust and transparent energy markets by decreasing barriers to entry  (removing geographic and temporal constraints and arbitrage opportunities)  and barriers related to resource allocation transmission vs. generation  additions or demand side responses.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_033">I guess what I just described is  something other then an 'audit' who's meaning is somewhat more legalistic,  fiduciary, or governance in nature.
</sentence><signature> Ottie  </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Greenleaf, Steve [SMTP:SGreenleaf@caiso.com]</from><to>   'Nabors, Ottie F - PMB-6'; Shea, Karen; kristiwallis@sprintmail.com</to><subject>      RE: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_034">Ottie,   Are you suggesting that the latest version of the notes needs to be  updated?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_035">If so, I would appreciate some suggested edits so that we can avoid  additional iterations.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Nabors, Ottie F - PMB-6 [mailto:ofnabors@bpa.gov]</from><to> 'Greenleaf, Steve'; 'Nabors, Ottie F - PMB-6'; Shea, Karen;</to><subject> RE: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_036">Hi Steve;   My suggestion would be to put in some words recognizing that FERC will be  driving the train where state cooperation is concerned.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_037">See my addition in  the attached file.
</sentence><signature> Ottie &lt;&lt;011112 stg SSG-WI MM Working Group Meeting Notes.doc  </signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Kristi M. Wallis [mailto:kristiwallis@sprintmail.com]</from><to> Greenleaf, Steve</to><subject> Re: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_038">Hi --  Here's the revised work plan that incorporates Steve's comments.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_039">(I've added a meeting and moved forward some of our "resolution" dates.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_040">I've also inserted a meeting location rotation.)
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_041">I've attached both a red-line and clean version of the work plan.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_042">I think this is ready to go, although everyone might want to take one last look (especially as it sets out an aggressive schedule).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_043">Steve, I assume you'll take care of forwarding the meeting notes and the work plan to SSG-WI.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_044">Let me know if there is anything else I can do to help.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_045">Thanks!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_046">Kristi  "Greenleaf, Steve" wrote:   Ollie and others,   As shown in the attached, I have accepted your (ollie's) changes and just  added the reference to FERC's "State-Federal Panels".
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_047">With that, I think  we're good to go.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_048">I'll wait and hear from Kristi on the work plan, then I  think we can pass this info along to SSG-WI.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_049">Sound reasonable?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="7"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Comnes, Alan</from><to> Steffes, James D.; Alvarez, Ray; Perrino, Dave; Mara, Susan; Walton,</to><subject> FW: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_050">Attached is a work plan for a 3-RTO working group (known as SSG-WI) to develop a market monitoring plan for CAISO, RTO West, and WestConnect.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_051">It is turning into the (western) United Nations of Market Monitoring.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_052">According to the attached plan, "This work plan is structured to first agree on the MME's authority and responsibilities, and then focus on the best structure to effectuate the agreement.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_053">"  We need to quickly decide our level of participation.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_054">Dave participated in a meeting last week and it got them to not send out biased meeting notes.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_055">To actually steer the BPA-CAISO train into something we live with, however, will take a lot of work.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_056">I suggest that we bring this up on our next "Western" call.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_057">That being said, I will be on a plane on Thurs morning.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_058">(Ray, could we have the Thursday call at 8:30/10:30/11:30 PST/CDT/EST??) 
</sentence><signature>Alan </signature></text></email><email order="8"><date> Wed, 14 Nov 2001 05:36:10 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Steffes, James D. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JSTEFFE</from><to>X- Comnes, Alan &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Acomnes, Alvarez, Ray &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ralvare2, Perrino, Dave &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Dperrino, Mara, Susan &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Smara, Walton, Steve &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Swalto2</to><subject> RE: Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring Working</subject><text><sentence id="ECT035_059">My initial take is to keep engaged through Perrino.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT035_060">I'll try and make the call this Thursday.
</sentence><signature>Jim </signature></text></email></thread></root>
