<root><thread><filename>stejjes-j_sent_items_315.txt</filename><name>	CA question</name><id>ECT031</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Swain, Steve</from><to>	Steffes, James D.</to><subject>	CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_001">I spoke with Mary Lynne today, and she said that once upon a  time (after the PX expired) we filed something asking the  CPUC to make the DJ index a substitute for the PX credit.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_002">Does this ring a bell?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_003">And the more important question --  did we ever withdraw that request?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_004">Thanks.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Steffes, James D.</from><to>	Mara, Susan; Swain, Steve</to><subject>	FW: CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_005">Steve --   We did originally file that the replacement for the PX Credit  should be the DJ Index.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_006">My recollection is that we did  withdraw this argument, however I've include Sue Mara on this  to double check.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_007">If we haven't, I'd guess that is no longer  URM's position?
</sentence><signature> Jim  </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Steffes, James D.</from><to>	Dasovich, Jeff</to><subject>	FW: CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_008">FYI
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Dasovich, Jeff</from><to>	Steffes, James D.; Swain, Steve; Mara, Susan</to><subject>	RE: CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_009">We did recommend using the DJ index.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_010">But subsequent to that,  I believe we filed as part of the "ARM" coalition,  recommending a bottom's-up approach.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_011">Is that right Sue?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_012">However, I don't think it's accurate to say that we  "withdrew" the DJ index recommendation.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_013">Both our original DJ  recommendation, and the bottom's up recommendation, are still  sitting at the PUC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_014">I think that's how things currently stand.
</sentence><signature> Best,  Jeff </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Mara, Susan</from><to>	Dasovich, Jeff; Steffes, James D.; Swain, Steve</to><subject>	RE: CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_015">All,   I think I actually was the one who proposed it in a 1998  "RAP" case three years ago.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_016">The case is long closed and our  suggestion was not accepted.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_017">Therefore, we don't have to  worry about it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_018">If we like the idea, we would have to find a  way to propose it anew -- if we don't like the idea, we just  fail to bring it up again.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Dasovich, Jeff</from><to>	Mara, Susan; Steffes, James D.; Swain, Steve</to><subject>	RE: CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_019">Recognizing that it was Sue's idea (though I'm not sure, Sue,  if you're referring to the DJ index or the bottoms-up  approach), isn't it also true that Harry submitted some  testimony more recently regarding the DJ index method, and  didn't ARM more recently submit some bottoms-up testimony,  comments, etc.?
</sentence><signature> Best,  Jeff </signature></text></email><email order="7"><date> Wed, 2 Jan 2002 09:06:04 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Swain, Steve</from><to>	Dasovich, Jeff; Mara, Susan; Steffes, James D.</to><subject>	RE: CA question</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_020">Before we carry this much further, let me explain some more why I raised the question in the first place.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_021">We currently assume that our exposure to CTC going forward is zero.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_022">Arthur Andersen was questioning this assumption, as market prices in general are lower than embedded gen now (unless you include DWR costs), which implies that if we were under the old CTC regime we could be paying some positive CTC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_023">AA was wondering why we weren't holding some reserves for this eventuality.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_024">Mary Lynne and I told them we weren't reserving b/c we just have no clear idea what will happen in the coming months re:CTC, but that in all likelihood zero is the best guess b/c no one can agree on what PX credit ("market" price) is now that there is no PX.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_025">Besides, though SCE and PG&amp;E are arguing for different methods (the so-called "top-down" and "bottom-up"), in the end the result will be about the same (CTC=0), especially now that PG&amp;E has supposedly stopped "adjusting" the PX credit to recover past undercollections.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_026">And of course, the DWR contracts muddy the waters, since if one includes them in the calculation of utility gen costs, then you could easily get to a negative CTC situation.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_027">Bottom line: we think things are so screwed up that everyone will prefer just to ignore CTC for the few months remaining that it has to run.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_028">In light of all this we thought we might further quell AA's skepticism if we could show that although we had once argued that DJI should be used as a substitute for PX credit, we were now simply arguing that DA should pay T&amp;D only, and that CTC should become a relic of the past.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_029">I think by now it may be a dead issue -- I believe AA has accepted our arguments w/o this extra bit of persuasion, else I would have heard more from Mary Lynne.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT031_030">Thanks for all the background and input from everyone, and please let me know if you have any more relevant comments given this context.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="8"><date> Fri, 12 Oct 2001 12:45:05 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Steffes, James D. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JSTEFFE</from><to>X- Ruffer, Mary lynne &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Mruffer</to><subject> FW: CA question on PX Credit</subject><text><sentence id="ECT031_031">Mary Lynne -  Do you need anything on this?
</sentence><signature>Jim </signature></text></email></thread></root>
