<root><thread><filename>mcconnell-m_sent_mail_678.txt</filename><name> Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation</name><id>ECT013</id><email order="1"><date> Fri, 15 Sep 2000 07:47:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> McKenzie, Lisa</from><to> McConnell, Thomas M.</to><subject> Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_001">Attached is the final version of our comparison of  the JLI POS sales tax rates with the Vertex System's sales tax rates.
</sentence><signature> &lt;&lt; File: JLI POS System.doc </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Fri, 15 Sep 2000 07:47:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Moore, Darwin</from><to> Bassett, Greg; Holley, Gary</to><subject> FW: Final Report - Sales Tax</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_002">Do either of you know what, if anything, was ever  done as a result of this?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_003">Were the stores known to be incorrect ever  contacted and corrected?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Fri, 15 Sep 2000 07:47:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Bassett, Greg</from><to> Moore, Darwin; Holley, Gary</to><subject> RE: Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation for</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_004">Not to my knowledge.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_005">My question is who is responsible for  keeping up with these rates and making appropriate changes.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_006">This  certainly does not seem like anything we should have store level people  responsible for keeping up with and maintaining.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_007">I have always assumed,  perhaps naively, that our sales tax group monitors this, both on the  collections and payment side.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_008">If this is not the case, we need to build a  bridge here, and quickly.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Fri, 15 Sep 2000 07:47:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Moore, Darwin</from><to> Bassett, Greg; Holley, Gary</to><subject> RE: Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation for the JLI</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_009">I can build a bridge (I think) and even enforce keeping the stores  correct, but I need a little more info.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_010">Like, which of several parts  methods do we prefer to use when appropriate (all are legal), and what  disclosure do we want on the invoices.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_011">I hate to call a meeting, but if  we get together and agree on some basics, I can probably make it happen.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_012">How fast is another question.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Fri, 15 Sep 2000 07:47:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Bassett, Greg</from><to> Moore, Darwin; Holley, Gary</to><subject> RE: Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation for the JLI POS</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_013">I agree we need a meeting.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_014">With convention, vacation, and quarterly staff  meeting for various folks all coming up, I suggest either tomorrow or  August 10.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Fri, 15 Sep 2000 07:47:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Bassett, Greg</from><to> "Billings, Tabatha" &lt;TabathaBillings@PZLQS.com, "Holley, Gary"</to><subject> RE: Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation for the JLI POS System</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_015">Tabatha, please schedule this meeting for August 10th.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_016">Greg, Gary and I should be able to handle it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_017">Russell, David, Tom - let Tab know if you want to attend.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_018">Tab, also invite Kevin Lyng, or whoever he designates, so we have someone who can carry the ball on contacting zees who aren't taxing correctly.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_019">Also, does anyone have the document showing the taxes and results by store?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_020">I only have the "here's what we did, here's what we found" letter.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_021">To fix all this, we need to know the correct tax rate per store, the method they should be using, and whether parts and/or labor need to be reported on the invoice.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_022">Then, our little group can make some consistency decisions about how taxes will be computed and reported at the company stores (there are some options we need to nail down), then IT will implement.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="7"><date> Fri, 28 Jul 2000 02:16:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Mike McConnell</from><to>X- "Moore, Darwin" &lt;DarwinMoore@PZLQS.com @ ENRON</to><subject> RE: Final Report - Sales Tax Calculation for the JLI POS System</subject><text><sentence id="ECT013_023">This email was sent to me by mistake.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT013_024">I didn't read it once I realized it was sent to me in error.
</sentence><signature>Mike McConnell </signature></text></email></thread></root>
