<root><thread><filename>stejjes-j_california_issues_51.txt</filename><name>	$.01 surcharge as "tax"</name><id>ECT023</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 17 Oct 2001 10:56:10 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Williams, Robert C.</from><to>	Sharp, Vicki</to><subject>	$.01 surcharge as "tax"</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_001">A typical clause reads as follows:   " 'Taxes' means any and all new or existing governmental or  quasi-governmental taxes, assessments, levies, duties, fees,  charges and withholdings of any kind or nature whatsoever and  howsoever described, including gross receipts, franchise,  sales, use , property, excise, capital, stamp, transfer,  employment, occupation, generatiion, privilege, Utility Taxes  separately defined to include "any and all franchise,  utility, regulatory, BTU or energy, gross receipts,  administrative services, municipality, and utility user taxes  and similar taxes and energy resource and municipal land use  surcharges and other similar surcharges" , regulatory, BTU,  energy, consumption, lease, transaction, license, filing,  recording, and activity taxes, levies, duties, fees, charges  and withholdings, together with any and all penalties, fines,  interest, and additions thereto, but excluding any taxes on  the net income of EESI or any affilitates."
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_002">Under the contracts the Buyer is usually responsible for  taxes "applicable to Power at or after the Delivery Point"  (the meter); the Seller is usually responsible for taxes  "applicable prior to the Delivery Point."
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_003">The surcharge  would seem to be applicable "at the Delivery Point."
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_004">Support for the argument that the surcharge is not a "tax"  under the contracts:   1.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_005">The CPUC refers to it as a "rate increase"   2. It was not imposed by a governmental body (such as a  state, county, or municipality)   3. When first implemented, all proceeds went to the utilities   4. It appears that a portion of the proceeds may  continue to go to the utilities   Support for the argument that the surcharge is a "tax" under  the contracts:   1.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_006">Since the "frozen tariff" remains in place it is  disingenuous to refer to it as a "rate increase"   2. It now appears that the proceeds will go to a  governmental entity, the DWR   3. The definition of "taxes" under the contract is  broad and includes surcharges of all types   4. To the extent the $.01 surcharge is to pay for  generation for bundled customers, those on direct access  receive, if anything, only an indirect benefit, which is  similar in effect to a tax and not to a rate increase 
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 17 Oct 2001 10:56:10 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Williams, Robert C.</from><to>	Dasovich, Jeff; Mara, Susan; 'mday@gmssr.com'; Steffes,</to><subject>	FW: $.01 surcharge as "tax"</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_007">a legal memo follows
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 17 Oct 2001 10:56:10 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Dasovich, Jeff</from><to>	Williams, Robert C.; Mara, Susan; 'mday@gmssr.com';</to><subject>	RE: $.01 surcharge as "tax"</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_008">Thanks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_009">One other question, which seems like a legal  question.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_010">Assume that Enron openly advocates for the PUC to  apply the charges to all customers, including ours,  understanding that our customers neither benefited from or  caused the charges.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_011">If the PUC does it, and we go back to  our customers and claim that an indirect tax has been  applied, are we in any kind of bind for having pushed for it?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_012">I'm hoping that the answer is no.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_013">Thanks for the info.
</sentence><signature> Best,  Jeff  </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Wed, 17 Oct 2001 10:56:10 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Williams, Robert C.</from><to>	Dasovich, Jeff; Mara, Susan; 'mday@gmssr.com'; Steffes,</to><subject>	RE: $.01 surcharge as "tax"</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_014">We could not do that.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_015">On the other hand, if we advocate that  it should only apply to those who directly benefitted, and  the CPUC adopts that reasoning, we would be shooting our tax  argument in the foot.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_016">I think you are right that we need to  understand the implications, both financially and  contractually, of the options before the Commission.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Wed, 17 Oct 2001 10:56:10 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Steffes, James D.</from><to>	Williams, Robert C.; Dasovich, Jeff; Mara, Susan; Wu,</to><subject>	RE: $.01 surcharge as "tax"</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_017">The EWS West Power URM desk will need to determine the $$ at  stake and help us manage our financial exposure and the  appropriate policy response.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_018">It's their $$.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_019">So far, my  understanding from the desk is that our current policy  recommendations (as outlined in the Mike Smith memo) are the  "preferred" outcome - 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_020">I'll reconfirm.
</sentence><signature> Jim  </signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Wed, 17 Oct 2001 10:56:10 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Steffes, James D.</from><to>	Swain, Steve; Tribolet, Michael; Dasovich, Jeff</to><subject>	Enron's Advocacy in California</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_021">Steve --   As you can see from the e-mail chain, we are now at a  decision point on where we want to go with PG&amp;E and SCE.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_022">With the progress of the PG&amp;E bankruptcy and the SCE  Settlement with the CPUC, it is important that we are all on  the same page.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_023">Basically we need to make sure that our advocacy is  consistent with our expected outcomes at the CPUC and with  the nature of your business (both current and hopefully going  forward).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_024">1. Do you have a preferred outcome on the PX Credit mechanism?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_025">2. Our advocacy on allocation of Utility Undercollection,  CDWR long-term contracts, and Bonds to pay off CDWR current  costs is that if a customer never was on DA they should be  "free" of all of these costs.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_026">Following from that logic, we  want to argue that customers who cause these buckets of costs  for limited periods of time should only pay for those  periods.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_027">We need to discuss the probable outcome of the  assignment of these costs and Bob Williams' ideas on the  "tax" passthru.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_028">I have attached Mike Smith's matrix on the outcome for each  bucket of $$.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_029">Let's talk very soon.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_030">We are potentially moving forward with  a SCE strategy.
</sentence><signature> Jim   &lt;&lt; File: CA Surcharge Matrix 10-09.doc    </signature></text></email><email order="7"><date> Wed, 10 Oct 2001 13:14:05 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Swain, Steve &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SSWAIN</from><to>X- Steffes, James D. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Jsteffe, Tribolet, Michael &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Mtribole, Dasovich, Jeff &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Jdasovic</to><subject> RE: Enron's Advocacy in California</subject><text><sentence id="ECT023_031">Jim,  We can talk at greater length if you want, but the quick answers to your questions are:  1. PX Credit: Make it simple and transparent.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_032">Best outcome would be no credit -- DA pays T&amp;D costs only, as they appear in the tariff.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_033">Period, end of story.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_034">2. The UDC Financial Hole: The more relief we can get from these items, the better.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_035">Duh.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_036">The small surcharge ($10) is currently factored into in our curves, so the hope is that whatever ultimately emerges from the sausage factory, the ultimate amount that they try to stick on DA customers is &lt; $10.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT023_037">If our contract language ends up protecting us further, all the better, but I would prefer that not to be our last resort.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
