<root><thread><filename>shackleton-s_inbox_425.txt</filename><name>	Futures relationship and documentation Deutsche Bank-Enron</name><id>ECT037</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 29 Oct 2001 14:24:58 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	"Kelly McKenney" &lt;kelly.mckenney@db.com@ENRON [mailto:IMCEANOTES-+22Kelly+20McKenney+22+20+3Ckelly+2Emckenney+40db+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com]</from><to>	Glover, Sheila</to><subject>	Futures relationship and documentation Deutsche Bank-Enron</subject><text><sentence id="ECT037_001">Dear Sheila,  I left you a voice mail this afternoon with regards to establishing an execution and clearing relationship for exchange traded futures and options.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_002">At the request of Shane Dallman and Aaron Armstrong in London, I have quoted rates for all relevant exchange traded products.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_003">They have expressed an interest in using Deutsche Bank for their futures trading so that we are arranging to have documentation drafted and sent to Houston as soon as possible.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_004">I have asked one of my colleagues, Rob Manders, to contact you to establish the names of the legal entities that should be on the contracts, and the name and address of the person/people to whom all documentation should be sent.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_005">Rob will be coordinating all the documentation and will assure that your operations department is happy with the service that Deutsche Bank will offer.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_006">To that end, he has organised a video conference with Kimberley Hopley in London and Jason Fisher in Houston for the week of 8th October.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_007">I hope that these arrangements meet with your approval.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_008">Should you have any questions, please feel free to call me on 44 207 547 3486.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_009">Equally, you can reach Rob Manders on 44 207 545 2005.
</sentence><signature>Best Regards, Kelly McKenney Phone 020 7547 3486 Fax 020 7545 2327 Email: Kelly.McKenney@db.com </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 29 Oct 2001 14:24:58 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Glover, Sheila</from><to>	Carrington, Clara; Hopley, Kimberly</to><subject>	FW: Futures relationship and documentation Deutsche Bank-Enron</subject><text><sentence id="ECT037_010">Clara and Kimberly, I just spoke with Rob at Deutche and suggested that Clara be on the call that is being arranged for next week.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Sheila </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 29 Oct 2001 14:24:58 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Glover, Sheila</from><to>	Shackleton, Sara</to><subject>	FW: Futures relationship and documentation Deutsche Bank-Enron</subject><text><sentence id="ECT037_011">Sara, The contact for Deutsche is Rob Manders (number and e-mail below) and Barbara Russo, who was listed on the form sent to you on 10/9.
</sentence><signature>Thanks. Sheila </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 29 Oct 2001 14:24:58 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Shackleton, Sara</from><to>	Glover, Sheila</to><subject>	RE: Futures relationship and documentation Deutsche Bank-Enron</subject><text><sentence id="ECT037_012">Sheila:  Can you please forward Rob Manders' fax number?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_013">I don't have an electronic version of the futures agreement to mark so I will need to fax comments.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_014">Thanks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT037_015">Sara 
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Tue, 16 Oct 2001 14:54:26 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Glover, Sheila &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SGLOVER</from><to>X- 'barbara.russo@db.com'</to><subject> FW: Futures relationship and documentation Deutsche Bank-Enron</subject><text><sentence id="ECT037_016">Barbara, Pleases confirm that comments from our Legal may be faxed to your attention at 212-469-2165.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Sheila 713-853-3210 sheila.glover@enron.com </signature></text></email></thread></root>
