<root><thread><filename>cash_inbox_346.txt</filename><name>	H-1B status and transfer expenses</name><id>ECT002</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 13 Aug 2001 19:43:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Tamariz, Angel</from><to>	Mayes, Fran</to><subject>	H-1B status and transfer expenses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT002_001">Fran:  As commented yesterday I will like to leave clear the situation on my H-1B and my transfer expenses in case my working relation with Enron finish in the upcoming days.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_002">As mentioned I was hired by MG Metals (now Enron Metals and Commodity Corp.) in June 2000, to work in Houston.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_003">In October 2000, when I received my working permit I moved into Houston from Mexico City.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_004">Enron took care of all the moving expenses.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_005">In the case my relation with Enron finishes, I need Enron to take care of the moving and relocation expenses as well as any tax derived from the entrance of my house hold again into Mexico.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_006">As I heard I need to pay taxes if I stayed outside Mexico, a period of less of two years.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_007">Also as commented yesterday I will like to know if Enron will notify the INS, about the termination of the working relation and if its possible to delay this notification, to have more time to prepare the moving and any other issues.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_008">Please comment.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_009">Best regards, 
</sentence><signature>Angel Tamariz Enron Industrial Markets Transaction Development Group x 31756 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 13 Aug 2001 19:43:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Mayes, Fran</from><to>	Tamariz, Angel</to><subject>	RE: H-1B status and transfer expenses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT002_010">Regarding your requests below:   
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_011">1.. Enron will pay for the cost of plane tickets to fly you and your family back to Mexico, if your position is eliminated.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_012">2. Enron is not able to adjust the immigration time frame regarding an "Out of status" situation.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_013">We are obligated to  notify the INS 60 days your termination date.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_014">3. You are responsible for any taxes due to your home country.
</sentence><signature> Fran </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 13 Aug 2001 19:43:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Tamariz, Angel</from><to>	Mayes, Fran</to><subject>	RE: H-1B status and transfer expenses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT002_015">Fran, we need to discuss this.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_016">I will not pay on my own the moving expenses and the taxes derived from such situation .
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_017">The contract will be terminated on Enron's option.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_018">When you (Enron) bruoght me and my family into Houston, the inmigration specialists should knew this situation.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_019">The moving expenses does not only include the plane tickets.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT002_020">I need to move my household.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 13 Aug 2001 19:43:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Mayes, Fran</from><to>	Tamariz, Angel</to><subject>	RE: H-1B status and transfer expenses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT002_021">I will forward your concerns to the legal department and immigration for their comments.
</sentence><signature> Fran </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Tue, 27 Nov 2001 14:13:22 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Mayes, Fran &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=FMAYES</from><to>X- Palmer, Lizzette &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Lpalmer</to><subject> FW: H-1B status and transfer expenses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT002_022">Please review and provide me with your comments.
</sentence><signature> Fran </signature></text></email></thread></root>
