<root><thread><filename>donoho-l_inbox_185.txt</filename><name>	Follow-Up</name><id>ECT019</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 12 Dec 2001 09:28:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Brady, Andy</from><to>	Lokey, Teb; Doll, Jeanette; Rapp, Bill; Trevino, Linda; Licciardo, Jeanne; Brown, Elizabeth; Betancourt, Ramona</to><subject>	Follow-Up</subject><text><sentence id="ECT019_001">I know it has been a while, but I wanted to send you the follow-up on our conversation last week, to make sure I heard everything correctly.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_002">Please let me know if the notes don't correctly reflect your memory of the conversations.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_003">Thanks a bunch!
</sentence><signature>ab.  &lt;&lt; File: TW CMS Project Business Meeting Agenda - Results.doc Andy Brady Enron Transportation Service, IT Work Phone - 713-853-7110 Work Fax - 713-853-6756 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 12 Dec 2001 09:28:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Betancourt, Ramona</from><to>	Brady, Andy</to><subject>	RE: Follow-Up</subject><text><sentence id="ECT019_004">Andy, I wanted to clarify on the item related to the West of Thoreau area.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_005">To me, I think that we could create a new Basin in PLE and call it East of California.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_006">The area is still W. of Thoreau with two basins in that area.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_007">Maybe check with Elizabeth to make sure she agrees.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_008">I have attached the POI view of one of the points that should be changed to the East of California basin.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_009">Let me know what you think.
</sentence><signature>Thanks Ramona  &lt;&lt; OLE Object: Picture (Device Independent Bitmap) </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 12 Dec 2001 09:28:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Brady, Andy</from><to>	Betancourt, Ramona</to><subject>	RE: Follow-Up</subject><text><sentence id="ECT019_010">Ramona,  Please take this and run with it and find out what the best solution is.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_011">We need information on what the different options are and what the best solution is for January implementation of the change.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_012">Let me know what help you might need.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_013">The major impact seems to be to TMS and Accounting, with minor affects to CRS and CMS (determining credit and gaining the correct max rate).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_014">We really need to have the solution defined by the Tuesday after Thanksgiving, or earlier if possible.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_015">Thanks a bunch and let me know.
</sentence><signature>ab. </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Wed, 12 Dec 2001 09:28:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Betancourt, Ramona</from><to>	Kedwaii, Hasan; Duff, David; Brown, Elizabeth; Hoang, Joe; Trevino, Linda; Donoho, Lindy; Doll, Jeanette</to><subject>	FW: Follow-Up on East of California Busines Changes</subject><text><sentence id="ECT019_016">Please plan to attend a meeting on Tuesday, 11/27/01 at 3:00pm in room 3907 to discuss PLE, TMS, CBS, &amp; Rate system changes that would be required to add additional areas or basins to TW in order to handle this request from Marketing and regulatory regarding TW's East of California rate structure tariff issues.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_017">If I have missed anyone on the distribution list, please forward.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_018">A decision is needed on this item by 11/29/01.
</sentence><signature>Thanks Ramona </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Wed, 12 Dec 2001 09:28:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Donoho, Lindy</from><to>	Betancourt, Ramona</to><subject>	RE: Follow-Up on East of California Busines Changes</subject><text><sentence id="ECT019_019">I have a 2:00 meeting with a customer.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT019_020">It should only last about an hour, but I might be able to be there until 3:15 or 3:30.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Tue, 27 Nov 2001 09:12:51 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Betancourt, Ramona  &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=RBETANC</from><to>X- Donoho, Lindy &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ldonoho</to><subject> RE: Follow-Up on East of California Busines Changes</subject><text><sentence id="ECT019_021">Can you see if maybe TK can come at 3:00 ?
</sentence><signature>Thanks Ramona </signature></text></email></thread></root>
