<root><thread><filename>delainey-d_sent_mail_405.txt</filename><name> Tembec and US Originators</name><id>ECT009</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 17 Sep 2001 11:25:01 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lozano, Melba &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=MLOZANO</from><to> Rob Milnthorp/CAL/ECT@ECT</to><subject> Tembec and US Originators</subject><text><sentence id="ECT009_001">Rob, We just had a very good meeting with Tembec about Energy procurement and energy outsourcing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_002">While the meeting went well, I am very confused about the Enron team making the pitch to them.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_003">My understanding is that the Canadian originators - particularly the Toronto team for Eastern Canadian companies will be responsible for everything except for pulp and paper swaps and to some extent, new SPV's.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_004">In this instance,  1. Tembec is a Canadian Company 2. All their assets are in Canada 3. Jan has been working with Tembec people in their largest facility 4. We know the executive team at Tembec 5. We clearly are very knowleadgable in all aspects of the Ontario energy market which is their focus right now 6.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_005">We understand and are pitching the overall energy outsourcing arrangement similar to the US pitches  With this in mind, I am not sure why Kellie Metcalf and Bob Anderson flew up here (6 hours flight time there and back, $4,000 to $5,000 in flights and hotels) for a 4 hour meeting with Tembec.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_006">Kelly was quite vocal in saying that this is a client they want to serve out of Houston.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_007">I have stated to her that that does not make any sense in terms of efficiency and costs and knowledge of the market where Tembec's assets are.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_008">Obviously, much of the technical engineering work would and should be done by the engineering team put together in the Industrial Services Group should a deal be struck.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_009">However, the commercial negotiations and marketing should be led by this office!!!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_010">I thought this had been agreed to already.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_011">We managed to piece up the meeting and deliver the "Enron" message, but going forward we need to have this resolved.
</sentence><signature>Cheers, Paul D </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 17 Sep 2001 11:25:01 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lozano, Melba &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=MLOZANO</from><to> Rodney Malcolm/HOU/ECT@ECT, Edward Ondarza/HOU/ECT@ECT, James A</to><subject> Tembec and US Originators</subject><text><sentence id="ECT009_012">Rodney, Edward, Jim - We've been over this issue a number of times and I thought we had reached resolution when we last met with Delainey.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_013">My understanding with respect to coverage of Canadian Industrials is as follows:  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_014">1.) ENA to take lead on industrials that have facilities in both US and Canada and will co-ordinate coverage with ECC with respect to Canadian Facilities.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_015">2.) ECC to take lead on industrials that have Canadian Facilities only.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_016">3.) With respect to Canadian Pulp &amp; Paper Industrials, ENA will cover Pulp &amp; Paper Swaps and SPV structuring.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_017">ECC will cover these industrials for all other Enron products (i.e.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_018">power, gas, services, etc.) Again, coverage needs to be co-ordinated.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_019">Specific to Tembec, I share Paul's concerns on why ENA would send 2 people to talk to Tembec re: outsourcing when Tembec is across the hall from ECC, ECC has an established relationship, and Tembec is a Canadian Company with no US facilities.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_020">It is my hope that we can resolve this amongst ourselves without having to get Dalainey involved.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_021">I would suggest a conference call next week.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_022">In the interim, Paul will forward a CA to Tembec in contemplation of an outsourcing arrangement.
</sentence><signature>Regards, Angela McCulloch for  Rob Milnthorp Assistant to Rob Milnthorp (403) 974-6738 </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 17 Sep 2001 11:25:01 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lozano, Melba &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=MLOZANO</from><to> David W Delainey/HOU/ECT@ECT</to><subject> Tembec and US Originators</subject><text><sentence id="ECT009_023">Dave, attached is some of the background correspondence in anticipation of our meeting with Brian Burnett.
</sentence><signature>Regards Milnthorp </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 17 Sep 2001 11:25:01 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lozano, Melba &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=MLOZANO</from><to> Rob Milnthorp/CAL/ECT@ECT, Max Yzaguirre/NA/Enron@ENRON, Rodney</to><subject> Tembec and US Originators</subject><text><sentence id="ECT009_024">Guys, to end all arguments, I would suggest the following protocol which is similar to what was discussed at Columbia Lakes:   
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_025">a) P&amp;P swaps and anything to do with the network strategy/assets in the paper sector in Canada and Mexico - Industrial Origination;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_026">b) Pure energy commodity positions and stand-alone energy assets (no outsourcing) for all industrial segments in Canada and Mexico - ECC or Enron Mexico;  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_027">c) Energy outsourcing for all industrial segments in Canada and Mexico - I would like Enron Canada and Enron Mexico to develop a written target list in which ECC, Enron Mexico and the Industrial Origination groups would work together to develop, sell and execute on the most profitable and value adding outsourcing product for the industrial customer in Canada and Mexico - ECC and Enron Mexico's understanding of the energy markets in Canada and Mexico coupled with the customer facing, product development and execution skills in Houston should provide a winning team.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_028">I am asking for the three teams to clearly identify the outsourcing targets, lead sales and structuring people and the timing as far as starting discussion with each target customer (ASAP).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_029">I would hope that the Mexican and Canadian teams would lead the sales process and the Houston team lead the structuring, customer facing and execution but I will let you decide the optimum mix.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_030">Either way, I am expecting this target list completed and agreed to in the next two weeks for Canada and Mexico;  and d) for Tembec I don't think it makes sense to change the deal team at this point; however, the US team will keep the Canadian team in the loop and if the products become non-outsourcing related the deal should be passed to ECC.
</sentence><signature>Regards Delainey </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Mon, 17 Sep 2001 11:25:01 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lozano, Melba &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=MLOZANO</from><to> David W Delainey/HOU/ECT@ECT</to><subject> Re: Tembec and US Originators</subject><text><sentence id="ECT009_031">Dave, my thoughts regarding your note:  This is not what we agreed to in Columbia Lakes.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_032">You were very clear on the point that ENA Industrial Marketing had enough to do South of the border.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_033">We have staffed up our Industrial Marketing Team in Toronto and are covering all industrials (on a full-time basis) which meet our load threshold in Ontario.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_034">Unlike the U.S., Ontario is a relatively small market where we can and have complete coverage.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_035">Paul and his group have done a tremendous job at positioning Enron in this marketplace, demonstrating our core competencies, and developing credibility.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_036">The last thing I want is some marketer up here from the U.S. selling the box without knowing how to fill that box (ie does not know the market fundamentals, rules or regulatory regime).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_037">This does nothing for Enron as it confuses the customer on who they should be talking to and destroys whatever credibility we had created to date.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_038">I have attached for your reference, a status report on industrial coverage.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_039">Perhaps the problem lies in how we are defining outsourcing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_040">As you know, there exists a continuum from portfolio management through to the energy island concept.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_041">Enron Canada has been pitching the entire outsourcing continuum recognizing that for many of these industrials, they will want to walk before they run.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_042">The majority that we have talked to are interested in portfolio management, our market expertise &amp; information, wholesale settlement services, and assistance with market opening readiness.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_043">I cant imagine how a U.S. originator could talk to or offer these services to Canadian Industrials.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_044">This is clearly in Enron Canada's wheelhouse.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_045">With respect to the opposite side of the outsourcing continuum, it makes total sense to have ENA utilize its resources in pursuing energy island, asset outsourcing type structures.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_046">With these opportunities, I see ENA taking the lead with ECC second chair.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_047">Where these opportunities are identified by ECC, we will forward these to the appropriate ENA originator.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_048">To date, ENA and ECC have worked well on Blue Circle, Terra, Co-Steel and Nexfor.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_049">As for Tembec, I am confused with what you mean by not changing the deal team.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_050">Kelli Metcalf has been up here twice talking to Tembec about a cogen in an area that does not make any economic sense.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_051">Jan and Paul have met with Tembec a number of times and we have had extensive discussions with Tembec specific to Ontario, Portfolio Management, Wholesale Settlement Services, Supply Procurement, and Asset Optimization.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_052">I realize that Bryan Burnett has an excellent relationship with Tembec and we should leverage off of this, but to simply "keep ECC in the loop" is fundamentally absurd and is not in Enron's best interests.
</sentence><signature>Regards Milnthorp </signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Fri, 4 Aug 2000 09:52:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- David W Delainey</from><to>X- Rob Milnthorp</to><subject> Re: Tembec and US Originators</subject><text><sentence id="ECT009_053">Rob, we may be saying the same thing here - for the EES outsourcing proposition (which is more than just asset management) as being defined by Rodney et al should be managed together by Industrial Origination and ECC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_054">Although, I would agree that ECC should lead the sale process.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_055">My view is that we should not and will not recreate the structuring, customer facing and execution requirements in Canada and Mexico required to do these deals.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_056">It is an important strategic iniative for ENA to complete a number of these deals.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_057">The problem is that a clear target list, joint accountabilities and schedule between the groups has not been rolled out which was discussed at Columbia Lakes.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_058">All other industrial business other than P&amp;P commodity/asset business is the perview of ECC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_059">Ultimately, I have not seen any outsourcing transactions from Canada in the deal structuring/due diligence queue.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT009_060">The US group can help get these done and can help in the pitch.
</sentence><signature>Regards Delainey </signature></text></email></thread></root>
