<root><thread><filename>shackleton-s_inbox_234.txt</filename><name>	Oil Prepay Rollover</name><id>ECT014</id><email order="1"><date> Fri, 28 Jul 2000 02:16:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Jamadagni, Rajaram</from><to>	Bruce, Robert; Shackleton, Sara</to><subject>	Oil Prepay Rollover</subject><text><sentence id="ECT014_001">Sara/ Bob,  Further to my discussions with Sara yesterday evening, and in the absence of any email from both of you to the contrary, I conclude that the confirms as they stand now should be OK from a legal perspective, subject to the credit approval of the entities.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_002">As I mentioned yesterday, Treasa's contact at CSFB here is trying to retain CSFB International as the counter-party as was the case for the 2000 transaction earlier.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_003">Thanks very much for your help.
</sentence><signature>Regards Rajaram Jamadagni </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Fri, 28 Jul 2000 02:16:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Shackleton, Sara</from><to>	Jamadagni, Rajaram; Bruce, Robert; Rohauer, Tanya</to><subject>	RE: Oil Prepay Rollover</subject><text><sentence id="ECT014_004">Raj: CAVEAT: I never heard back from Tanya about whether the CSFB confirmation would have a carve-out for margining pursuant to the master agreement.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_005">Bob was going to send me the format he drafted for the prior CSFB deal but which was never executed so that I could incorporate that language.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_006">Tanya may agree to allow this trade to margin under the agreement just like the confirm which terminated 9/12/01.
</sentence><signature>Sara Sara Shackleton Enron Wholesale Services 1400 Smith Street, EB3801a Houston, TX  77002 Ph:  (713) 853-5620 Fax: (713) 646-3490 </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Fri, 28 Jul 2000 02:16:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Rohauer, Tanya</from><to>	Shackleton, Sara; Jamadagni, Rajaram; Bruce, Robert</to><subject>	RE: Oil Prepay Rollover</subject><text><sentence id="ECT014_007">As I do not have any details of this deal, I cannot comment on the need for a carve out of margining rights.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_008">The only issue that I have been aware of is the Cayman branch possibility.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_009">My comment on that to bothe Raj and Teresa was that if it is in fact a different legal entity (as determined by legal) then I will need financial information to make an assessment of this entity.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_010">If it is a branch and part of CSFB International, which is sometimes the case with financial institutions, we would have recourse to CSFB International and it would be confirmed under the existing document.
</sentence><signature>Regards, Tanya </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Fri, 28 Jul 2000 02:16:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Shackleton, Sara</from><to>	Boyle, Dan</to><subject>	FW: Oil Prepay Rollover</subject><text><sentence id="ECT014_011">Dan: Neither credit nor legal has ever received info about the "Cayman branch" (if it is a branch) so we have never assessed that entity in full.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_012">Treasa and Raj were trying to avoid use of that entity and trying to stick with CSFBI.
</sentence><signature>Sara </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 15:43:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Boyle, Dan &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DBOYLE</from><to>X- Shackleton, Sara &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Sshackl</to><subject> RE: Oil Prepay Rollover</subject><text><sentence id="ECT014_013">I agree.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT014_014">I have told James that we would like to close with CSFB International and work after the closing to change, if possible, as appropriate.
</sentence><signature>Dan O. Boyle Vice President Enron Global Finance Phone:        713-853-1532 Mobile:        713-417-3532 Pager:         877-390-2838 Skytel PIN:  880FBF5 </signature></text></email></thread></root>
