<root><thread><filename>martin-t_inbox_137.txt</filename><name> Memorial Chase Web Site</name><id>ECT034</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 22 Oct 2001 07:09:28 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Lyne Martin</from><to> Cindy Knapp</to><subject> Memorial Chase Web Site</subject><text><sentence id="ECT034_001">Cindy, Oak Creek is wanting to start their own web page.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_002">We had looked at the Memorial Chase page last year and were very impressed by what you all had done with it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_003">Is there someone at Memorial Chase that was involved with setting up your web page that might be willing to answer a few questions for us?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_004">We have a board member that is familiar with how to set it up, but I thought it might be beneficial for them to talk to someone that had done the same thing for a NWAL team before they go much furthur.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_005">Thanks for your help.
</sentence><signature>Lyne Martin </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Sat, 5 Jan 2002 14:29:25 -0600</date><from> "Cindy Knapp" &lt;clfauxde@houston.rr.com</from><to> "Bain, Mark &amp; Debbie" &lt;mbain0@hotmail.com</to><subject> Fw: Memorial Chase Web Site</subject><text><sentence id="ECT034_006">Hi Mark, I am forwarding an email from Oak Creek.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_007">Think you could answer some questions for them?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_008">Lyne's husband Tom is their team rep this year.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_009">Their home email is lynemartin@msn.com
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Cindy </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Sat, 5 Jan 2002 14:29:25 -0600</date><from> mark bain</from><to> lynemartin@msn.com</to><subject> Re: Fw: Memorial Chase Web Site</subject><text><sentence id="ECT034_010">Lyne, My name is Mark Bain and I'm the Web Site Adminstrator for the Mariners.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_011">I would be glad to help out in any way.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_012">Please pass this email and my phone numbers (281-379-6896 hm. 281-518-3251 wk.) to your website person.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_013">I put alot of info in this email to help get started but if it is a little overwhelming, just call.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_014">A previous board member, Steve Burleigh, created our web site last year and gave me alot of ideas.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_015">For this year, I found a web site called eTeamZ that hosts web sites for sports groups.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_016">Check out our new page: http://www.eteamz.com/swimmariners/
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_017">eTeamsZ is really easy to use and does not require much web site knowledge.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_018">They do the formatting and you supply the info.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_019">If your web guru wants to get creative, they can do some custome stuff as well.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_020">The best part, however, is that it is FREE.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_021">Of course with free you have to put up with a little advertising but since this site is tailor made for sports (meet schedules, practice schedules calendars, news, maps, etc.) , I think it is worth it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_022">If you don't decide to use eTeamZ, that's fine too.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_023">I've created some other web sites and should be able to answer some questions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_024">Sounds like you have some experience so it should be no problem.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_025">Good luck and let me know what else you need.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_026">eTeamZ TIPS: Oh, here are some tips on getting started with eTeamZ.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_027">(difficulties that I had anyway): Registration- http://www.eteamz.com/company/sites/register/
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_028">The toughest part was coming up with a nickname and a user name for the websites.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_029">Seems that most of the users are into baseball and Mariners was taken.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_030">I think I used Mariners Swim Team for nickname and goMariners for the username because I kept hitting other name that were being used.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_031">WebSite- When I got to the "build you web" page, I chose Team Web Site.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_032">They also had options for Leagues and Orgs.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_033">My best advice is to start populating things via the admin page and bring up another windows to check the progress of what is actually displayed.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_034">PLUS - They have a premium service called PLUS that you pay for but I didn't see much use for it except you get rid of some of the advertising banners.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_035">They also show that you can use this site for registration and other things but we are keeping it pretty simple.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Sat, 5 Jan 2002 14:29:25 -0600</date><from> Lyne Martin</from><to> mark bain</to><subject> Re: Fw: Memorial Chase Web Site</subject><text><sentence id="ECT034_036">Dear Mark,  Thank you so much for your e-mail.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_037">I am forwarding it to our website coordinators, Wendy &amp; Eric Lijewski.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_038">They may be in contact with you if they have any questions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_039">I am going to ask them to look into the eteamz.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_040">It sounds like just what we need.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_041">Thanks for the suggestions and helpful hints!
</sentence><signature>Lyne Martin Oak Creek Cudas </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Mon, 7 Jan 2002 10:56:03 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- "Lyne Martin" &lt;lynemartin@msn.com@ENRON</from><to>X- Martin, Thomas A. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=TMARTIN</to><subject> Fw: Fw: Memorial Chase Web Site</subject><text><sentence id="ECT034_042">Tom, We received this information from Memorial Chase.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT034_043">Wendy is going to look into it.
</sentence><signature>Lyne </signature></text></email></thread></root>
