<root><thread><filename>shapiro-r_retail_markets_31.txt</filename><name>	APS Filing</name><id>ECT032</id><email order="1"><date> Fri, 12 Oct 2001 12:45:05 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Nord, Sue</from><to>	Shapiro, Richard; Steffes, James D.</to><subject>	APS Filing</subject><text><sentence id="ECT032_001">Are we (or EPSA) taking an active role in the filing APS made with the Arizona Commission to use the unregulated affiliate of its parent as the wholesale provider of last resort?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_002">(There's an article on the filing in today's Electric Power Daily that says they've filed to push back the requirement that they purchase 100% of their power from the competitive market by 2004 to a requirement that they purchase 25% of their power competitively by 2008).
</sentence><signature>Sue Nord Senior Director Government Affairs 713-345-4196 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Fri, 12 Oct 2001 12:45:05 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Shapiro, Richard</from><to>	Kaufman, Paul</to><subject>	FW: APS Filing</subject><text><sentence id="ECT032_003">Thoughts?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Fri, 12 Oct 2001 12:45:05 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Kaufman, Paul</from><to>	Shapiro, Richard</to><subject>	RE: APS Filing</subject><text><sentence id="ECT032_004">We fought this issue at the ACC when it was first presented several years ago.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_005">Recall that this was the settlement where we were joined at the hip with the industrials, the industrials cut and run for a rate reduction, and we ended up litigating the case (testimony by Mark Frankena--on local market power, Tom Delaney, Harry Kingerski, and another consultant).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_006">We got our bottoms kicked--although I think we won on the credit for billing our own customers (APS wanted to credit ESPs $0.25/customer--we got the number up somewhere above the cost of postage).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_007">My recollection is simliar to Leslie's re: the asset transfer and affiliate as the PLR.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_008">It was part of the settlement.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_009">We fought the arrangement and lost.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_010">Recall that we appealled the ACC's decision on the basis of bias and lost.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_011">I'm not a big fan of the ACC ... given our track record.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_012">We have much better political contacts in Arizona now; however, the contacts are with the Gov's office and not the ACC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_013">Recall that the ACC is elected and is one of Arizona's four branches of government--i.e., the judiciary, the legislature, the executive branch and the ACC (by virtue of Arizona's constitution).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_014">APS may be pushing back a little hard here (25% by 2008), but I'd want a firm indication that there was interest in Arizona before we fight it, and I'd want a clear indication that the market wasn't competitive from a retail perspective without the PLR being 100% short.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_015">When we fought it last time, Frank Vickers and ENA had some interest in the PLR.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_016">We tried to negotiate a deal with Jack Davis to swap some power so the PLR was instaneously being served by other than APS.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_017">We were entirely unsuccessful and Vickers dropped Arizona like it had the plague.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_018">Having said all that, I'm always up for a good fight.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_019">If we can EPSA to step in and spend some money, I'd be happy to help out in any way I can.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Fri, 12 Oct 2001 12:45:05 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Kingerski, Harry</from><to>	Lawner, Leslie; Kaufman, Paul; Nord, Sue</to><subject>	RE: APS Filing</subject><text><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Fri, 26 Oct 2001 12:05:28 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Kaufman, Paul &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=PKAUFMA</from><to>X- Kingerski, Harry &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Hkingers, Lawner, Leslie &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Llawner, Nord, Sue &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Snord</to><subject> RE: APS Filing</subject><text><sentence id="ECT032_020">Mark Frankena is now an advisor to the Chair of the FTC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT032_021">Leslie--when do you start?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
