<root><thread><filename>farmr-d_eol_5.txt</filename><name>	Intrastate Gas</name><id>ECT008</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 19 Jun 2001 17:04:52 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Lauer, Kara</from><to>	Farmer, Daren J.</to><subject>	Intrastate Gas</subject><text><sentence id="ECT008_001">Hi Daren, Bryan Hull gave me your name.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_002">A customer was interested in trading Intrastate Gas and Bryan had informed me that our Exxon-Katy location is intrastate.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_003">I was wondering if you would be interested in changing the long description on EOL for this location to include the phrase intrastate gas so that any customers that are interested would be able to see that.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_004">If this is okay with you, I will forward it on to our product development team.
</sentence><signature>Thanks. Kara Kara Boudreau Lauer EnronOnline Marketing 713/853-0570 kara.lauer@enron.com </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Tue, 19 Jun 2001 17:04:52 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Farmer, Daren J.</from><to>	Lauer, Kara</to><subject>	RE: Intrastate Gas</subject><text><sentence id="ECT008_005">That will be fine.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_006">Most people know that the gas in this area is intrastate.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_007">But, if someone wants to see that in the description, we can add it.
</sentence><signature>D </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Tue, 19 Jun 2001 17:04:52 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Lauer, Kara</from><to>	Lees, Lisa</to><subject>	FW: Intrastate Gas</subject><text><sentence id="ECT008_008">Lisa, what is involved in changing a product description to include this phrase?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_009">I do have some customers in Texas that are legally bound to only trade intrastate gas and they are fearful of trading anything that doesn't specifically state that.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_010">Since it is probably only a handful of customers, if it is a major production, it may not be worth it, but I wanted to check.
</sentence><signature>Thanks. Kara </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Tue, 19 Jun 2001 17:04:52 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Lees, Lisa</from><to>	Lauer, Kara</to><subject>	RE: Intrastate Gas</subject><text><sentence id="ECT008_011">Kara,  The product development team will check with Legal on this and we'll get back with you.
</sentence><signature>Thanks.  Lisa </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Mon, 17 Sep 2001 11:25:01 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lozano, Melba &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=MLOZANO</from><to>X- Dickson, Stacy E. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Sdickso, Hodge, Jeffrey T. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Jhodge</to><subject> FW: Intrastate Gas</subject><text><sentence id="ECT008_012">Stacy,  Could we add the following phrase (as shown below in RED) to the Exxon Katy location?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_013">This is to reassure our customers that the delivery is in fact intrastate.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_014">Please let me know if this is possible to do and if we have your approval.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_015">ExxonKaty The transaction is for delivery of intrastate gas at the tailgate of the Exxon Katy Plant.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT008_016">Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in the General Terms and Conditions, if applicable, this Transaction is between Counterparty and Enron North America Corp.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Melba Lozano 713-345-8986 713-646-8511 Fax 713-698-4847 Pager </signature></text></email></thread></root>
