<root><thread><filename>dasovich_inbox_1689.txt</filename><name> Forthcoming Direct Access DASR's</name><id>ECT040</id><email order="1"><date> Thu, 27 Sep 2001 14:23:11 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Heckmann, Thomas [ mailto:HeckmaT@sutterhealth.org</from><to> Lee, Rod</to><subject> Forthcoming Direct Access DASR's</subject><text><sentence id="ECT040_001">Rod,   On the question of whether new accounts can be added to old  contracts ...   The October 12 PG&amp;E implementation plan for direct access  "wind-down" you  recently shared with me gave deadlines of October 5 and November 1,  respectively, for ESP's to provide names of customers and details of  customer accounts to be added to direct access.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_002">I quote additional wording referring to the above " ... time-lines  require  ESP's to specify ... those customers by name whose contracts qualify  them  for the submission of additional DASR's"   Thus PG&amp;E's plan clearly contemplates the addition of new accounts  to old  contracts.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_003">Now, October 20, CPUC ruling D.01-10-036 states:   "For purposes of utility compliance with D.01-09-060, we want  to make  it clear that, unless otherwise directed or allowed to in a  subsequent  Commission decision, utilities cannot set a deadline after which  they  could refuse to  process DASRs relating to contracts executed on or before  September 20,  2001."
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_004">Therefore, it being PG&amp;E's intent to let new accounts be DASR'd to  old  agreements which include a provision for adding new accounts, and it  being  the CPUC's explicit ruling that no time limit be set on this  activity,  Sutter Health is moving forward with plans to add a number of  accounts to  its current direct access arrangement with Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_005">Please let me know if you anticipate any barriers to this action at  your  end, as arrangements with Enron will take a lot of time and energy.
</sentence><signature> Cordially,   Tom Heckmann, PhD  Contract Analyst  Sutter Health System Procurement  1600 Cebrian St  West Sacramento, CA  95691  (916) 373-3420 phone  (916) 373-3470 fax  (916) 373-6706 page  &lt;heckmat@sutterhealth.org     </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Thu, 27 Sep 2001 14:23:11 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>	Lee, Rod [SMTP:RZL1@pge.com]</from><to>	'Heckmann, Thomas'</to><subject>	RE: Forthcoming Direct Access DASR's</subject><text><sentence id="ECT040_006">Tom,   The CPUC's Decision 01-09-060 specifically prohibits any new  contracts, agreements &amp; "arrangements" post Sept 20th.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_007">Accounts that  were  under contract on or prior to September 20th, are eligible for DA at  anytime  afterwards.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_008">The Commission has ordered the UDCs to accept DASRs  indefinitely  for customer accounts that meet the Sept. 20th customer "contract"  deadline.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_009">The November 1 deadline still exists &amp; presumably Enron has  submitted Sutter's valid account numbers on that list.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_010">If DASRs are  submitted on accounts that are not on the list they will be rejected until  such time that verification of a legitimate contract exists.
</sentence><signature> Roderick Lee  Corporate Account Manager  Office - 415  973-4830  Cell Phone 415 244-1647  Fax - 415  973-8494   </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Thu, 27 Sep 2001 14:23:11 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>	"Heckmann, Thomas" &lt;HeckmaT@sutterhealth.org@ENRON@EES</from><to>	'Lee, Rod'</to><subject>	Dueling rulings on direct access</subject><text><sentence id="ECT040_011">But CPUC D.01-10-036 of 10/10/01 states:   "For purposes of utility compliance with D.01-09-060, we want to  make  it clear that, unless otherwise directed or allowed to in a subsequent  Commission decision, utilities cannot set a deadline after which they  could refuse to  process DASRs relating to contracts executed on or before September 20,  2001."
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_012">Our contract is before Sept 20.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_013">New DASR's can occur any time.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_014">Since we disagree, I suppose we may have to get an opinion from the CPUC.
</sentence><signature> Tom Heckmann, PhD  Contract Analyst  Sutter Health System Procurement  1600 Cebrian St  West Sacramento, CA  95691  (916) 373-3420 phone  (916) 373-3470 fax  (916) 373-6706 page  &lt;heckmat@sutterhealth.org   </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Thu, 27 Sep 2001 14:23:11 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>	Lechner, Michael</from><to>	Riley, Tom</to><subject>	FW: Dueling rulings on direct access</subject><text><sentence id="ECT040_015">Per your request re.: Tom Heckmann of Sutter Health.
</sentence><signature> Regards,   T. Michael Lechner, P. E.  Service Manager  Enron Energy Services  Phone:	925-543-3833  Pager:	888-562-9418  Cell:	925-698-5670  Fax:	925-543-3550  </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Thu, 27 Sep 2001 14:23:11 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Riley, Tom</from><to> Huddleson,Diann; Mara, Susan</to><subject> RE: Dueling rulings on direct access</subject><text><sentence id="ECT040_016">Sue, Diann,  It appears PG&amp;E is telling our customers they cannot add accounts where allowed by a contract as well.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_017">What can we do to get PG&amp;E to stop providing misinformation to our customers?
</sentence><signature>Tom </signature></text></email><email order="6"><date> Thu, 15 Nov 2001 11:14:36 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Mara, Susan &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SMARA</from><to>X- Riley, Tom &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Notesaddr/cn=f6b8c5b8-5b1e9b79-2f12c0c7-df0c3468, Huddleson,Diann &lt;dhuddles@EESHOU.TheBentleyCompany.com</to><subject> PG&amp;E Rep and Sutter Health on Adding Facilities</subject><text><sentence id="ECT040_018">Tom, Diann and Michael,  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_019">I gave Peter Ouberg a call but then I read the PG&amp;E rep's answer again ..  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_020">I think Tom Heckman misinterpreted what Rod Lee said.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_021">I agree with Rod Lee.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_022">He did not say that Enron could not submit DASRs -- he said we had to have the account on the list and if we did then the DASR would be processed.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_023">If we did not have the account on the list, there would have to be some verification that the contract was signed on or before 9/20/01.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_024">Enron and the other ESPs previously agreed with this approach (although the utilities did not fully buy into it).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_025">I believe Diann submitted the account information, as we had agreed, on Nov 1.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_026">I take a little bit of issue with the comment that they will reject DASRs for accounts not on the Nov 1 list until the contract is verified, but I believe it follows the general spirit of what we agreed to at the meeting with ESPs and utilities on Oct 2.  I think Mr. Heckman thought he was being told that he could not add new facilities, but that's not how I read the reply from Mr. Lee.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_027">So, I called Peter Ouberg back and said told him there didn't appear to be a problem after all, but that I would let him know if one cropped up.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT040_028">IF you would like me to speak to Mr. Heckman, I would be happy to do so.
</sentence><signature>Sue Mara (415) 782-7802 </signature></text></email></thread></root>
