<root><thread><filename>lay-k_inbox_488.txt</filename><name>	401k from DSG</name><id>ECT046</id><email order="1"><date> Fri, 4 Jan 2002 07:11:57 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Beavers, Debbie</from><to>	Barnard, Marla</to><subject>	401k from DSG</subject><text><sentence id="ECT046_001">Marla ,  I am a former employee of DSG.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_002">We were purchased by Enron, Dec. of 1999 .
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_003">We were promised that our 401K's would be moved to Enron's 401k plan.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_004">This has never happened.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_005">I no longer receive AUL (401k company) statements.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_006">AUL claims that it sends the statements to the administrator of the plan at Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_007">I would really like to transfer my money to Enron's 401k or at least receive a statement of my account at AUL.
</sentence><signature>Thanks! Debbie Beavers (713) 345- 6363 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Fri, 4 Jan 2002 07:11:57 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Barnard, Marla</from><to>	Beavers, Debbie</to><subject>	RE: 401k from DSG</subject><text><sentence id="ECT046_008">Debbie, I forwarded this message to Mikie Rath in benefits - did you get a response?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_009">If not, I do have some info.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_010">I can provide, but she would need to assist you with any particular details.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_011">Please see below - I just learned recently that it does not appear much of this info.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_012">was communicated to DSG employees after the acquisition.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_013">1- The assets contained within the DSG 401(k) plan cannot be transferred to the Enron plan because the plan was never authorized by the IRS.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_014">2- Prior DSG employees cannot transfer funds out of the AUL 401(k) into a self directed IRA, because Enron purchased the assets of DSG.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_015">Therefore termination applies to Enron employment, not employment by DSG in regards to transfer of said assets to a self directed account.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_016">3- The DSG plan with AUL will remain intact and Enron will pay all associated administrative fees until all employees represented by the plan are no longer in employed by Enron   4- Since the plan is frozen, vesting service should continue to accrue as long as the employee remains with Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_017">Only if the plan is terminated does "super vesting" occur.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_018">The purchase agreement may have assumed that the plan was going to be terminated which could explain that language.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Fri, 4 Jan 2002 07:11:57 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Beavers, Debbie</from><to>	Barnard, Marla</to><subject>	RE: 401k from DSG</subject><text><sentence id="ECT046_019">I did not receive any info from Mikie Rath.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_020">Does this mean that I can not borrow from my AUL 401k?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_021">The majority of my money (11 years) came from Amoco not DSG.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_022">Does that matter?
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Fri, 4 Jan 2002 07:11:57 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Barnard, Marla</from><to>	Rath, Mikie</to><subject>	FW: 401k from DSG</subject><text><sentence id="ECT046_023">Mikie, can you please respond to Debbie's question below?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_024">thanks 
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Thu, 4 Oct 2001 10:02:26 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Beavers, Debbie &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DBEAVERS</from><to>X- Lay, Kenneth &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Klay</to><subject> 401k from DSG</subject><text><sentence id="ECT046_025">Mr. Lay,  A group of former DSG employees have tried to receive information about the status of our DSG 401k's.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_026">We were promised that our accounts would be super-vested and then moved to Enron's 401k plan.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_027">We expected this change to take at the most 6 months.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_028">It has been two years... We were told on several occasions that our accounts had been super-vested and we were waiting on Enron to move the accounts.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_029">We are now being told that our AUL accounts can not be moved and in fact are frozen.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_030">Marla Barnard was our HR representative at the time of the acquisition.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_031">She has directed my questions to Mike Rath in Benefits, who has never responded.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT046_032">Can someone please explain why the super-vesting and moving of the funds did not occur, the rules associated with the account freeze and why we are not receiving our statements from AUL?
</sentence><signature>Debbie Beavers (713)345-6363 </signature></text></email></thread></root>
