<root><thread><filename>shackleton-s_inbox_412.txt</filename><name> Prime Brokerage Clearance Services Agreement</name><id>ECT021</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 08:33:37 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Grice, Regan [mailto:regan.grice@funb.com]</from><to> Doukas, Tom</to><subject> Prime Brokerage Clearance Services Agreement</subject><text><sentence id="ECT021_001">Mr. Doukas:  On September 27, we opened a prime brokerage account in the name Enron Credit Inc. Bear Stearns is acting as Prime Broker on this account, and First Union Securities, Inc. is executing your securities.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_002">The SEC requires the Clearing Broker (us) to have the attached agreement on file for our prime brokerage clients.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_003">If you would be so kind as to have this agreement signed, I would greatly appreciate it.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_004">If you have any questions, you can call me at 704-593-7024.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_005">Once it is completed, it can be faxed back to my attention at 704-593-7032.
</sentence><signature>Thank you and best regards, Regan Grice First Union Capital Markets, Documentation Phone: 1-800-735-1470 or 704-593-7278 Fax: 704-593-7032  &lt;&lt;Enron Credit 151.doc </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 08:33:37 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Doukas, Tom</from><to> Shackleton, Sara</to><subject> FW: Prime Brokerage Clearance Services Agreement</subject><text><sentence id="ECT021_006">I have another one for you guys.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_007">I do not anticipate any urgency on this, but would still like it out of the way.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Tom </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 08:33:37 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Shackleton, Sara</from><to> Doukas, Tom</to><subject> RE: Prime Brokerage Clearance Services Agreement</subject><text><sentence id="ECT021_008">Please forward your email to the RAC group requesting the opening of this account.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_009">Thanks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_010">Sara 
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 5 Nov 2001 08:33:37 -0800 (PST)</date><from> Doukas, Tom</from><to> Schultz, Cassandra; Bradford, William S.; Lowry, Donna</to><subject> RE: Prime Brokerage Clearance Services Agreement</subject><text><sentence id="ECT021_011">Bill, Cassandra, and Donna,  Please reply to this mail with your approval of the signing of the below documents which are needed to maintain an account that had previously been in use by ECT/ENA for execution of Bond Trades through prime broker acocunts.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_012">As Enron Credit has now split out into its own entity new documents must be provided to the executing brokers.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_013">Since we were trading in the old name prior with the counterparties this has only recently come up.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_014">It is now disrupting our trading ability as vital couterparties have been restricted from further transactions with us.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_015">Can we have a blanket approval to set up all bond counterparties registered with ECT/ENA to be set up for ECI as well.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Tom Doukas </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Tue, 16 Oct 2001 11:31:13 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lowry, Donna &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=DLOWRY</from><to>X- Doukas, Tom &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Tdoukas, Schultz, Cassandra &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Cschult, Bradford, William S. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Wbradfo</to><subject> RE: Prime Brokerage Clearance Services Agreement</subject><text><sentence id="ECT021_016">I agree that the account documentation should be signed asap.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_017">The accounts should have been reregistered with appropriate documentation when trading began with Enron Credit Inc.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT021_018">Any questions or if I can help with anything, please let me know.
</sentence><signature>Donna Lowry, RAC Compliance </signature></text></email></thread></root>
