<root><thread><filename>cash_inbox_182.txt</filename><name>	Year End Reorgs and Mass Transfers</name><id>ECT042</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 11:20:04 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Figueroa, Regina</from><to>	Becker, Melissa; Blaylock, John; Booth, Khymberly; Broussard, Tharsilla; Brown, Daniel; Buckley, Karen; Campos, Karen E.; Clyatt, Julie; Curless, Amanda; Davies, Neil; De Jesus, Frank; Fitzpatrick, Amy; Foster, David; Funkhouser, Shanna; Galloway, Sonja; Gray, Judy; Hankamer, Cecilia; Hickok, Kim; Huynh, Catherine; Jones, Robert W.- HR Exec; Kearney, Julie; Kinningham, Laura; Labbe, Anne; Lopez, Leasa; Mayes, Fran; McLoughlin, Hector; Migliore, Todd; Oquinn, Kari; O'rourke, Tim; Parra, Veronica; Petteway, Alisa; Pieper, Kalen; Pierce, Shelly; Roberts, Paulette; Rodriguez, Grace; Russi, Estalee; Ryan, Noel; Seleznov, Ryan; Slone, Jeanie; Tessandori, Bobbi; Walton, Sheila; Whitney, Jennifer; Yeverino, Norma; Zarkowsky, Sarah; Zermeno, Rosalinda; Barnard, Marla; Pena, Renee; Harkreader, Jerry ; Houston, Rita; Hutcherson, Leesa; Robles, Eduardo; Reese, Frances</to><subject>	Year End Reorgs and Mass Transfers</subject><text><sentence id="ECT042_001">It's time for year-end reorganizations and mass transfers at Enron again.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_002">Attached are documents that explain the Mass Reorg and Transfer process for this year as well as templates to submit the data for processing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_003">Please make sure that the appropriate templates are submitted.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_004">&lt;&lt; File: Reorg_MassTransf_HR_121901.ppt &lt;&lt; File: Org_Structure_Approvals.doc &lt;&lt; File: InterComoveTemplateProgram.xls &lt;&lt; File: IntraComoveTemplateProgram.xls
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_005">We will be discussing these items in tomorrow's HR Generalist meeting.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_006">Let me know if you have any questions, and please forward this e-mail to anyone I may have missed.
</sentence><signature>Regina Figueroa Corp HR 713-345-9608 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 11:20:04 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Davies, Neil</from><to>	Oxley, David; Cash, Michelle</to><subject>	FW: Year End Reorgs and Mass Transfers</subject><text><sentence id="ECT042_007">David/Michelle  Based on your knowledge of the deal structure :  1 ) Do you think that we should transfer all Netco employees to ENA w.e.f 1/1/01.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_008">(from ENW/CORP etc) and at the same time do letters confirming assignment of EEA's for those on EEA's with Corp/ENW etc who have an assignment clause.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_009">Also suggest we ask those who do not have the assignment term in their agreement to sign an amendment to their agreement assigning the contract to ENA.  2) Also as we are likely to apply for new H1 visas for all L1 visas - I would think it makes sense for new visa's this to be with ENA - as I assume this is the most likely company to be part of the acquisition ?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_010">Therefore we will need to do transfer letters for those employees who are not ENA employees as part of this exercise.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_011">Tyndall and Forster will probably require an upfront payment to apply for these visa's - @ $3,500 + $1000 for the premium processing.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_012">Therefore we will need to cut a cheque to them for (18 L1 transfers) of circa $ 80,000 - we may be able to negotiate this down some.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_013">We can then if necessary transfer over the H1's at the appropriate time to the new entity.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_014">We should try to get these exercises to coincide.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_015">David/MIchelle - can you discuss this approach with the deal team/counterparty - especially 1 (as 2 seems a no brainer).
</sentence><signature>Neil </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 11:20:04 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Cash, Michelle</from><to>	Davies, Neil; Oxley, David</to><subject>	RE: Year End Reorgs and Mass Transfers</subject><text><sentence id="ECT042_016">I do think transferring all Netco employees to ENA would be effective.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_017">We easily could do a master assignment of all the employment agreements on a single document that does not have to be signed by the employees.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_018">For those without assignment clause, we could do a document in which the employee agrees and consents to the assignment to ENA and to any other company that may buy the trading business of ENA.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_019">On visa issues, I agree with your approach, although would suggest that no deal with T&amp;F is possible given that we already owe them over $150K on pre-petition fees.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_020">I don't think the deal team or counterparty would have any say in this.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_021">We will let them know that all relevant employees are in ENA, and that should do it.
</sentence><signature>Michelle </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 11:20:04 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Oxley, David</from><to>	Cash, Michelle; Davies, Neil</to><subject>	RE: Year End Reorgs and Mass Transfers</subject><text><sentence id="ECT042_022">I agree.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_023">Bobby/Kathy, any objections?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_024">May be premature until Amy and Jeanie have verified that all names on list are in agreement to transfer.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Thu, 20 Dec 2001 09:01:20 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Schultea, Kathryn &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=KSCHUL2</from><to>X- Oxley, David &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Doxley, Cash, Michelle &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Mcash, Davies, Neil &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ndavies</to><subject> RE: Year End Reorgs and Mass Transfers</subject><text><sentence id="ECT042_025">I agree.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_026">If the names are closer to being verified I can help with getting reports on visas, etc.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_027">Let me know.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT042_028">Thanks.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
