<root><thread><filename>delainey-d_sent_mail_43.txt</filename><name> Re: Cuiaba I Team</name><id>ECT011</id><email order="1"><date> Tue, 21 Aug 2001 08:17:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lakho, Shahnaz &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SLAKHO</from><to> Miguel Padron/SA/Enron@Enron, Brett R Wiggs/SA/Enron@Enron</to><subject> Re: Cuiaba I Team</subject><text><sentence id="ECT011_001">Cuiaba 1 team currently consists of:  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_002">Rick Lammers -lead developer 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_003">john novak- legal 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_004">Rob G Gay- Finance part time
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_005">Traci Bersoni- support Finance part time 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_006">Stephen Gray- support Finance part time 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_007">Felipe Ospina- project analyst 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_008">Gabriela Aguilar -support -gas part time 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_009">Emmanuel Rengade- Sudam financing and Equity Sale 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_010">Marcus Stephen-Sudam financing and Equity Sale  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_011">Joao Carlos Alberquerque- support PPA 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_012">Jose Bestard- support PPA and regulatory  Asset management 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_013">Laine A Powell-construction management and operations 
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_014">Christiaan Huizer-Project analyst  
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_015">Let me know if I can help furtherh
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Tue, 21 Aug 2001 08:17:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lakho, Shahnaz &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SLAKHO</from><to> James M Bannantine/ENRON_DEVELOPMENT@ENRON_DEVELOPMENT, Joe</to><subject> Re: Cuiaba I Team</subject><text><sentence id="ECT011_016">To all, Here is the Cuiaba I Team....
</sentence><signature>Miguel </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Tue, 21 Aug 2001 08:17:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lakho, Shahnaz &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SLAKHO</from><to> Rebecca McDonald/ENRON_DEVELOPMENT@ENRON_DEVELOPMENT</to><subject> Cuiaba I Team</subject><text><sentence id="ECT011_017">Subject: Cuiaba I Team  the list below is going to Delainey - it is accurate from my perspective - if the project ends up in your shop for completion and fixing up - and if it ends up under me - some of these part time guys should become full time and some of the full time guys should take a back seat.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_018">I would have the full time dedicated team be -  Jose Bestard (he currently is chief of regulatory for South America) - he negotiated the original PPA and has indepth knowledge of how the regulatory system does and does not work.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_019">Joao Carlos Alberquerque - top notch Brazilian power expert - has the right contacts and relationships and can get us through the maze of Brazilian resistance.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_020">Currently he is headed for wholesale merchant.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_021">John Novak - best legal mind - needs to curb the use of outside lawyers a bit - has been on the project continuous from day one - and needs to be rejuvenated a bit - but has thourough understanding of how bthe entire project is wired together.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_022">Rob Gay - Finance  Laine Powell - is currently President of the oeprating companies - Cuiaba is producing 300 mw of power which is being sold and paid for.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_023">Felipe Ospina - modeler - I don't know this guy - he is relatively new to the project and seems satisfactory  Would recommend also a fresh set of eyes on the project - not front line negotiator - but someone good at structuring - or work outs - to review overall project structure objectively and challange conventional wisdom.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_024">Other folks on the list below can support the dedicated team - part time.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_025">Would tell these guys - this is your only job - and here is your starting point - new deal.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_026">Your job is not just to close financing - it is to get Enron's money out or otherwise improve the returns of the project.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_027">You will get paid based on this point forward.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_028">It will take at least 9 months to implement a solution that improves our returns or gest more than just financial close achieved.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_029">This leaves some sticky situations - Rick Lammers has absolutely busted his ass getting things done and moving the project forward - he has been lead developer - but has had lots of "help" from Bannantine and the entire team.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_030">Help tended to obscure responsibility and accountability.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_031">I am not sure anyone could have gotten this thing done by now - but certainly there were some things that could have been done better - in 20/20 hindsight - and some things that can be done better now.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_032">The things that come be done better now - I am pushing into Laines's area of responsibility this week.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_033">People need to get rededicated and fired back up - I also think it is kind of difficult to "take over" the project without making some changes in the way it is being run.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_034">For the review on Monday - I have asked the following people to present -  Rick Lammers Laine Powell Jose Bestard  Also in attendance will be John Novak, Joe Kishkill, Brett Wiggs, Rob Gay and myself.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_035">The guys asked if Jim Bannantine should be present - I said no - let me know if you would like him there.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_036">You should see - a brief description of the overall project (not the strategy - just how it is wired together- where the money is intended to be be) and then straight to a listing of all things that need to get done to "finish" the project to the point where we have financial close and a functioning supply and PPA.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_037">Joe and I and Rob will be in Houston and the rest of the team will dial in a conference call.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_038">Let me know if the above format is ok.
</sentence><signature>Pete </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Tue, 21 Aug 2001 08:17:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Lakho, Shahnaz &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=SLAKHO</from><to> David W Delainey@ECT</to><subject> Cuiaba I Team</subject><text><sentence id="ECT011_039">Dave,  I am sorry that I was unable to meet with you yesterday on Cuiba.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_040">Jim has told me what the two of you decided and it is fine with me.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_041">Below is a note that I received this morning from Pete.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_042">The meeting he is referencing is an indepth update on the project that I requested a week ago.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_043">You are more than welcome to attend if you would like to - just let me know.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_044">I am not sure that Pete is the right guy to work this or not, but I do agree that we need to introduce someone else into the process - I am thinking either Chris Hunt or Mariella Mahan.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_045">I would be happy to discuss with you why I recommend one of those two individuals.
</sentence><signature>Rebecca </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Thu, 30 Nov 2000 07:16:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- David W Delainey</from><to>X- Rebecca McDonald</to><subject> Cuiaba I Team</subject><text><sentence id="ECT011_046">Rebecca, if you wouldn't mind I would like to sit in on the Monday meeting.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_047">I think that Mariella from what I have seen and heard is very capable.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_048">I strongly believe that we need to put a dedicated (with fresh eyes) SWAT team on this one that has control of the complete commercial, technical and financial aspects of this project.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_049">This is the only way to be effective.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT011_050">Whether it is with you or me or both, I am indifferent  I would like to ensure that Kishkill, Wiggs, Gonzales and Alberquerque are not buried in this project given other goals and objectives.
</sentence><signature>Thanks Regards Delainey </signature></text></email></thread></root>
