<root><thread><filename>benson-r_inbox_237.txt</filename><name>	LI and CO2</name><id>ECT056</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 4 Feb 2002 15:51:42 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Jacobson, Lisa</from><to>	Schoen, Mary</to><subject>	LI and CO2</subject><text><sentence id="ECT056_001">Got it -- let's talk before I call the County office.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_002">I have several questions myself.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_003">Thanks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_004">http://www.co.suffolk.ny.us/exec/press/2001/emissions.html
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_005">Under the law taking affect March 1, 2002 any power plant in the county that generates over 1,800 pounds of CO2 emissions per Megawatt/hour would be fined two dollars for every ton above the limit.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_006">An additional $1 per excess ton would be charged in each consecutive year.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_007">The bill contains several alternatives to paying fines including buying emission credits through nationally recognized CO2 trading markets, investing in alternative energy sources or donating penalties to community environmental groups.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_008">The Suffolk County Department of Health Services will be responsible for compliance and will set rules and reporting requirements by October 1, 2001.
</sentence><signature>Lisa Jacobson Enron Manager, Environmental Strategies 1775 Eye Street, NW Suite 800 Washington, DC 20006 Phone: +(202) 466-9176 Fax: +(202) 331-4717 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 4 Feb 2002 15:51:42 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Schoen, Mary</from><to>	Philip, Willis</to><subject>	FW: LI and CO2</subject><text><sentence id="ECT056_009">Thanks Mary.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_010">Please let me know if you find anything else, and what you find insofar as similar developing legislation in NYC.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_011">I will send you a list of threatened plants in Suffolk, if you are interested.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_012">Here is a copy of the press release from Suffolk County.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_013">I'm not sure if it is any more informative than the Electric Power Daily blurb.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_014">Lisa and I are working on gathering more details for you.
</sentence><signature>Willis  -----Original Message----- From: 	Schoen, Mary Sent:	Tuesday, August 21, 2001 12:00 PM To:	Philip, Willis Cc:	Jacobson, Lisa Subject:	FW: LI and CO2 &lt;r Here is a copy of the press release from Suffolk County.  I'm not sure if it is any more informative than the Electric Power Daily blurb.  Lisa and I are working on gathering more details for you. Mary Schoen Environmental Strategies Enron Corp 415.782.7803 (phone) 415.782.7854 (fax) </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 4 Feb 2002 15:51:42 -0800 (PST)</date><from> 	Schoen, Mary</from><to>	Philip, Willis</to><subject>	RE: LI and CO2</subject><text><sentence id="ECT056_015">Willis - that would be great.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_016">We have some very tentative information on NYC: there is a proposed law currently in committee at the NYC City Council level.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_017">The law would require EGUs greater than 25 MW to reduce CO2 according to a schedule set out in the rule, eventually leading to a 30% reduction from 1999 levels.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_018">A trading program would be possible and there is a fine of $5 for every ton above the allowed emission rates.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_019">We are working on getting a copy of the proposed rule and the status of the rule.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_020">Will keep you posted.
</sentence><signature>Thx. Mary Mary Schoen Environmental Strategies Enron Corp 415.782.7803 (phone) 415.782.7854 (fax) </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Tue, 21 Aug 2001 14:36:04 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Philip, Willis &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=WPHILIP</from><to>X- Benson, Robert &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Rbenson, Gupta, Gautam &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Ggupta, Broderick, Paul J. &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Pbroder, Davis, Mark Dana &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Notesaddr/cn=ab167e54-8eec877d-862564b5-7715f6</to><subject> FW: LI and CO2</subject><text><sentence id="ECT056_021">Wow - this is potentially HUGE.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_022">I will keep you all posted as far as any developments.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT056_023">I do not think this is on anyone's radar screen.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
