<root><thread><filename>fisher-m_inbox_16.txt</filename><name>	Raptor unwind tax accounting</name><id>ECT015</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 15:43:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Dewar, Donette</from><to>	Locklear, Essie</to><subject>	Raptor unwind tax accounting</subject><text><sentence id="ECT015_001">Essie:  The purpose of this message is to communicate to you, for co-ordination with the appropriate "MARC" personnel, the relevant facts of the transactions that closed on Friday, September 28, to unwind the Raptor structures.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_002">As I likely will not return to the office until just at the time of September close, I thought it might make sense for you, with Brent's assistance, to make sure that the appropriate reporting personnel are notified of the tax adjustments that should be made to book these transactions.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_003">Each of the "top tier" Raptor entities (Harrier, Roadrunner, Pronghorn, and Grizzly) "purchased" from LJM the membership interest that LJM owned in the "bottom tier" Raptor entities (Talon, Bobcat, Porcupine, and Timberwlf, respectively).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_004">Harrier paid $6 mil, Roadrunner and Grizzly each paid $15 mil, and Pronghorn paid $1,000.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_005">As a result of these transactions, the purchased entities became book consolidated with Enron.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_006">Also as a result of these transactions, a total book loss of around $600 mil was recorded (divided among the books of each one of the four structures).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_007">For tax purposes, the purchasing and purchased entities are all disregarded entities of Enron Corp. (or EES, in the case of Pronghorn and Porcupine).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_008">The repurchases are to be treated as merely a final payment made by Enron Corp. (or EES, as the case may be) on a contingent debt instrument.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_009">Accordingly, the entire book loss should be reversed for tax, and instead an interest deduction recorded on the tax books of each purchasing entity for the amount that was paid to purchase the bottom tier entity.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_010">For examply, Harrier will record an interest expense deduction for $6 mil.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_011">We have not been told yet exactly how the book loss will be spread among the four structures, and whether it will be booked on the top tier or bottom tier entities' books.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_012">Ron Baker likely will have an answer on this issue by the time you see this message.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_013">Please leave me a voice mail if you need assistance before I return to the office on October 10.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_014">Thanks!
</sentence><signature>DMD </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 15:43:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Locklear, Essie</from><to>	Fischer, Mary; Ng, Mark</to><subject>	FW: Raptor unwind tax accounting</subject><text><sentence id="ECT015_015">FYI
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 15:43:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Swafford, John</from><to>	Caminos, Facundo</to><subject>	FW: Raptor unwind tax accounting</subject><text><sentence id="ECT015_016">Facundo: See the note below.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_017">Please note that you will need to reverse the book loss recorded on the upper tier entities (Harrier, Roadrunner, Pronghorn and Grizzley) for the purchase of the lower tier entities in the amount of about $600 million.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_018">In place of the reversal of the book loss, you should record a tax Schedule M to deduct the same (about $600 million) of interest expense.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_019">I am working with Essie to determine which entities will report how much of the $600 million purchase price.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, John. </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 24 Sep 2001 15:43:15 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Locklear, Essie</from><to>	Swafford, John; Caminos, Facundo; Merritt, Michelle</to><subject>	RE: Raptor unwind tax accounting</subject><text><sentence id="ECT015_020">I just talked to Ron Baker, who advised me that the total losses to be booked are $710,594,336 and they will be booked as follows:  Raptor I Harrier I LLC $406,326,409 Raptor II Grizzly I LLC $15,531,889 Raptor III Pronghorn I LLC $309,508,781 Raptor IV Roadrunner I LLC ($20,772,742)  Please check SAP to see if the numbers have been booked before the close as Ron wasn't sure if they had been booked or not.
</sentence><signature>Essie </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Tue, 9 Oct 2001 16:23:25 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Swafford, John &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JSWAFFO</from><to>X- Caminos, Facundo &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Fcaminos</to><subject> FW: Raptor unwind tax accounting</subject><text><sentence id="ECT015_021">Facundo: Essie and I will confirm with Donette tomorrow, but for the time being, plan on reversing the $710 million book loss on the entities listed below (if you determine that they were in fact booked) and include Schedule M adjustments to deduct as interest expense the purchase price paid by Harrier $6 mill., Roadrunner and Grizzly $15 mill.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_022">each, and Pronghorn $1,000 for the lower tier entities purchased from LJM.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT015_023">We will confirm and let you know before noon tomorrow.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, John. </signature></text></email></thread></root>
