<root><thread><filename>kitchen-l_americas_103.txt</filename><name>	electronic trading</name><id>ECT045</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 1 Oct 2001 10:27:57 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	"Flood, Scott L [GCO]" &lt;scott.l.flood@ssmb.com@ENRON</from><to>	Taylor, Mark E (Legal)</to><subject>	electronic trading</subject><text><sentence id="ECT045_001">Mark,  Thanks for the call yesterday .
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_002">It was very helpful.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_003">Can you send me a  copy  of the electronic trading and pass word application agreements ?
</sentence><signature>Thanks </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 1 Oct 2001 10:27:57 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Kitchen, Louise &lt;Louise.Kitchen@enron.com</from><to> Flood, Scott L [GCO] &lt;sf06840@imcnam.ssmb.com</to><subject> FW: SSMB lawyer's request</subject><text><sentence id="ECT045_004">Scott   Mark Taylor forwarded me your request, I thought it may be helpful to  introduce myself and Dave Forster, Dave is the Vice President in charge of  the commercial/operational aspects of EnronOnline (that was!).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_005">We do have a  relaunch plan in place which highlights critical timings which need to be  met over the next weeks.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_006">I hope this will assist you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_007">As Mark probably  already informed you we are taking the opportunity to update the PA and ETA.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_008">Under the timescale we do plan to have these with you today.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_009">Should Citigroup be the winning bidder, we are currently planning to use  the website name "citigroupenergy.com, 'ssmbenergy.com' or 'ssbenergy.com'.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_010">If you intend to give us one of your own doamine names please let us know.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_011">If you have any questions on the timetable, please do not hesitate to  contact Dave or myself, or on the form of the agreements Mark Taylor.
</sentence><signature> Thanks   Louise   Louise Kitchen  Chief Operating Officer  Enron Americas  Tel:  713 853 3488  Fax: 713 646 2308     &lt;&lt;relaunchtimetable.xls  </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 1 Oct 2001 10:27:57 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	"Flood, Scott L [GCO]" &lt;scott.l.flood@ssmb.com@ENRON</from><to>	Kitchen, Louise</to><subject>	Re: FW: SSMB lawyer's request</subject><text><sentence id="ECT045_012">Louise, thank you for your timeline.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_013">Is it envisioned the distribution of  the ETA on monday will include revised general terms and conditions or will  that be sent later ?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_014">Thanks  
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 1 Oct 2001 10:27:57 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Kitchen, Louise [mailto:Louise.Kitchen@enron.com]</from><to> "Flood, Scott L [GCO]" &lt;scott.l.flood@ssmb.com@ENRON</to><subject> RE: FW: SSMB lawyer's request</subject><text><sentence id="ECT045_015">The following documents are the two agreements which facilitate the online trading.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_016">These contracts govern the actual transaction process and are accepted the counterparty either in writing or electronically.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_017">Password Application - In writing Electronic Trading Agreement - Electronically  These documents do not have any customer specific terms (eg credit etc) as they are not intended to govern the underlying commodity transactions, but simply the utiliszation of the website.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_018">The General Terms and Conditions will be issued to the known Buyer as they do have credit terms etc.  Please let me, Dave Forster or Mark Taylor know if you would require further information.
</sentence><signature>Louise  &lt;&lt;Netco ETA v.1.doc  &lt;&lt;Netco PA v.1.doc </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Fri, 4 Jan 2002 07:11:57 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- "Stuckey, Richard A [FI]" &lt;richard.a.stuckey@ssmb.com@ENRON</from><to>X- Kitchen, Louise &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=LKITCHEN</to><subject> RE: FW: SSMB lawyer's request</subject><text><sentence id="ECT045_019">Louise  Saw in the WSJ today that the judge allowed Enron to "end" 600-700 supply contracts.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_020">Is that EES?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_021">If so are they going to still be in business?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_022">I ask because of my question from yesterday re the annual load carve-out.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT045_023">Is there anything left to carve out?? 
</sentence><signature>Thanks Rick </signature></text></email></thread></root>
