<root><thread><filename>kaminski-v_personal_78.txt</filename><name> New Commodity Marketplace Opportunity</name><id>ECT004</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 24 Jan 2001 15:49:37 -0600</date><from> Al Arfsten &lt;arfsten@bflassociates.com</from><to> mark.lay@enron.com</to><subject> New Commodity Marketplace Opportunity</subject><text><sentence id="ECT004_001">Mark Lay: I shared confidentially with Vince Kaminski my developing  concept of a highly inefficient not-for-profit enterprise with  dramatically increasing costs.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_002">I believe that a for-profit economic  model is possible that should reverse these skyrocketing costs and  ultimately lower the commodity thereby having a national, if not, global  impact of health care costs.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_003">Vince seems to also believe in the  concepts potential.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_004">The CEO of one of the biggest U.S. blood banks has  already asked to become involved.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_005">I would like involve more people  with vision, means and desire to help make this a reality.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_006">I would look  forward to meeting with you to talk further.
</sentence><signature>Al Arfsten 713 965 2158  - LifeTrak Vision Chart 012601.doc </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 24 Jan 2001 15:49:37 -0600</date><from>   Al Arfsten &lt;arfsten@bflassociates.com@ENRON</from><to>     Lay, Mark</to><subject>  [Fwd: New Commodity Marketplace Opportunity]</subject><text><sentence id="ECT004_007">Mark: Per our brief conversation this morning, the attached email was  sent to you yesterday.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_008">I hope that you might understand that I am  conceptually looking for "founders" and at the "pre" business plan  stage.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_009">There is an enormous problem existing with a very attractive  economic reward and willing participants needing this solution.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_010">I need  help.
</sentence><signature>Al Arfsten 713 965 2158 </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 24 Jan 2001 15:49:37 -0600</date><from>   Al Arfsten &lt;arfsten@bflassociates.com@ENRON</from><to>     Lay, Mark</to><subject>  [Fwd: New Commodity Marketplace Opportunity]</subject><text><sentence id="ECT004_011">I did understand that you were still at the concept stage.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_012">It is a very  interesting proposal and I would like to think about it.
</sentence><signature> Thanks,  Mark </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Sat, 27 Jan 2001 08:31:00 -0800 (PST)</date><from>X- Al Arfsten &lt;arfsten@bflassociates.com</from><to>X- Mark.Lay@enron.com</to><subject> Re: [Fwd: New Commodity Marketplace Opportunity]</subject><text><sentence id="ECT004_013">Mark Lay: Again, thank you for listening to my concept.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_014">In my search for co-foounder/collaborators and angel investors, disclosing the concept (for lack of a better title now, I call the system "LifeTrak") and formulating a simple, clear picture is not easy.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_015">The attached schematic depicts an overview of the effort.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_016">Part of the diagram hopes to separate the special interests as participants and member organizations so as to be helpful in the public sector with social issues.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_017">The groups fall into two natural sectors; (1) supply generators; and (2) user/service organizations.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_018">In the middle is the system and its management that interconnects those benefiting groups and the donor/recipient LifeTrak cardholders.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_019">I can embellish more on these later.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_020">The diagram gives us a place to begin discuss and talking points in order to try to simplify how the concept could be developed and supported and where the revenue model which creates dramatic efficiencies generates management and license fee.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_021">I hope we can get together soon.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT004_022">Although Vince Kaminski cannot directly contribute due to his other commitments, I have copied him to keep him advised (hoping that he might be able to do more at a later date.).
</sentence><signature>Best regards, Al Arfsten </signature></text></email></thread></root>
