<root><thread><filename>stepenovitch-j_inbox_124.txt</filename><name>  Discovery Responses</name><id>ECT044</id><email order="1"><date> Wed, 23 Aug 2000 11:20:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>   Jonda Stowell &lt;jls@fullenweider.com@ENRON</from><to>     Stepenovitch, Joe</to><subject>  Discovery Responses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT044_001">Dear Joe,   Would it be possible for you to come in one day next week at about  3:00  p.m. to go over your discovery responses?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_002">Alternatively, you could  come in two days at 4:00 p.m. On Thursday, I leave early for my  son's  soccer practice.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_003">Perhaps Tuesday and Friday would be good for  you???
</sentence><signature> Jonda L. Stowell  Legal Assistant  The Fullenweider Firm  4265 San  Felipe, Suite 1400  Houston, TX  77027  (713) 624-4100  Telephone  (713) 624-4141 Facsimile  e-mail:  jls@fullenweider.com </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Wed, 23 Aug 2000 11:20:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Joe.Stepenovitch@enron.com [mailto:Joe.Stepenovitch@enron.com]</from><to> jls@fullenweider.com</to><subject> RE: Discovery Responses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT044_004">Good Morning Jonda,   I would like to met with Mr. Fullenweider today if that is possible?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_005">I'm  going out of town Thursday thru Sunday of this week.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_006">I think it is very  important that I speak with him as soon as possible.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_007">Please let me know  if  today is good for him.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_008">Thanks again, 
</sentence><signature> -Joe </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Wed, 23 Aug 2000 11:20:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>   Jonda Stowell &lt;jls@fullenweider.com@ENRON</from><to>     Stepenovitch, Joe</to><subject>  RE: Discovery Responses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT044_009">Dear Joe,   I'm sorry but I have Mr. Fullenweider scheduled in back-to-back  meetings,  hearings and depositions this week.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_010">I might be able to arrange a short  telephone conference today or tomorrow.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_011">Otherwise, his deposition  schedule  may clear up on Wednesday and Thursday depending on how the Judge rules  at a  hearing tomorrow morning.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_012">If the depositions get reset by the Court, I  could fit you in on Wednesday or Thursday.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_013">I absolutely must visit with you this week about your discovery  responses  because I will be out of town next week and they are due next Friday.
</sentence><signature> Jonda </signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Wed, 23 Aug 2000 11:20:00 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> Joe.Stepenovitch@enron.com [mailto:Joe.Stepenovitch@enron.com]</from><to> jls@fullenweider.com</to><subject> RE: Discovery Responses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT044_014">Jonda,  I understand Mr. Fullenweider has meeting but after what Tonya put me and my family through last week we would like some answers and action.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_015">I have cut off all communication with her and now she is sending me emails (trying to act like nothing happened) I'm sure her lawyer is telling her to do that so she can say she has been keeping me informed of my son.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_016">(I will forward them to you) I am very upset and I'm sure you can understand why, I really think there is something really wrong ( I just have that feeling or she is mentally unstable ) How can she be aloud to keep me from my son?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_017">Anyway, If I can't meet with Mr. Fullenwerider can you and I meet to go over the discovery responses and does this mean were going to a jury trial?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_018">Why are they aloud to ask these questions and are we doing the something to Tonya?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_019">I don't understand....
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_020">I can't get out of leaving on Thursday, this is a business meeting for work (not pleasure) I can come Today, Tuesday and Wednesday anytime after 3:30.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_021">I hope that helps 
</sentence><signature>Thanks again, -Joe </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Mon, 1 Oct 2001 10:27:57 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Jonda Stowell &lt;jls@fullenweider.com@ENRON &lt;IMCEANOTES-Jonda+20Stowell+20+3Cjls+40fullenweider+2Ecom+3E+40ENRON@ENRON.com</from><to>X- Stepenovitch, Joe &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=JSTEPENO</to><subject> RE: Discovery Responses</subject><text><sentence id="ECT044_022">Joe,  Can you come Tuesday at 3:45 to meet with me?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT044_023">I have given Mr. Fullenweider a message to call you in the interim.
</sentence><signature>Jonda </signature></text></email></thread></root>
