<root><thread><filename>shackleton-s_inbox_208.txt</filename><name>	Assignment of crude/Brent spread trades from ECTRIC to ENA</name><id>ECT053</id><email order="1"><date> Mon, 22 Oct 2001 12:10:29 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Shackleton, Sara</from><to>	Nelson, Roderick</to><subject>	Assignment of crude/Brent spread trades from ECTRIC to ENA</subject><text><sentence id="ECT053_001">Hey, Rod (the "Dude"):  Mr. Jason Williams of the Houston office has directed me to you.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_002">I spoke with Harvard (has an ENA ISDA Master Agreement (the "Master") in place) who is trading on EOL (and all ENA trades are confirmed under the existing Master).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_003">Harvard executed a crude/Brent spread trade on EOL and discovered that the counterparty was ECTRIC (and not ENA).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_004">Boy, were they surprised!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_005">Harvard's request is whether ECTRIC can assign the trade to ENA.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_006">Then, all of Harvard's trades would be subject to the ENA Master and could be netted.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_007">Is this a commercial issue?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_008">Does ENA need a "Brent book" to receive this trade?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_009">An assignment from ECTRIC to ENA would be only an "accommodation" to Harvard.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_010">Please let me know what you think.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_011">Thanks.
</sentence><signature>SS P.S.  I never made it to London in June.  My boyfriend's mother was in the hospital then and she died two weeks later.  My mother died a few weeks ago.  It's been a bad summer.  But, I'm taking a vacation from August 23 - 31 and will be in London (staying at the Ritz).  Maybe we can have that drink! Sara Shackleton Enron Wholesale Services 1400 Smith Street, EB3801a Houston, TX  77002 Ph:  (713) 853-5620 Fax: (713) 646-3490 </signature></text></email><email order="2"><date> Mon, 22 Oct 2001 12:10:29 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Nelson, Roderick</from><to>	Shackleton, Sara</to><subject>	RE: Assignment of crude/Brent spread trades from ECTRIC to ENA</subject><text><sentence id="ECT053_012">Hi Sara.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_013">This issue comes up fairly often.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_014">My understanding is that Brent deals are automatically booked to ECTRIC for tax reasons.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_015">The Brent product stack is managed here in London by folks who live, work and eat in the UK.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_016">Since they are in effect generating earnings for the firm 'in' the UK, the tax argument is that the Inland Revenue should collect tax on this amount.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_017">We could book to ENA, but I here that this could cause double taxation (being taxed again by the IRS).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_018">Perhaps ECTRIC could do a back-to-back trade with ENA at the Brent mid price - thus still managing the product in the UK but generating no UK earnings (Inland Revenue may call foul though).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_019">Having said this, we have successfully re-booked in the past when trades were done on the phone (apparently without tax consequence).
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_020">No one has taken a hard stand on the above - that I know of anyway.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_021">I would recommend just telling the book admin to rebook to ENA and see if we get any resistance.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_022">Clearly, from a credit perspective we would much prefer to book both legs at ENA.  Hope all else is going well.
</sentence><signature>Rod </signature></text></email><email order="3"><date> Mon, 22 Oct 2001 12:10:29 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Shackleton, Sara</from><to>	Lebrocq, Wendi</to><subject>	FW: Assignment of crude/Brent spread trades from ECTRIC to ENA</subject><text><sentence id="ECT053_023">fyi
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email order="4"><date> Mon, 22 Oct 2001 12:10:29 -0700 (PDT)</date><from> 	Lebrocq, Wendi</from><to>	Rohauer, Tanya</to><subject>	FW: Assignment of crude/Brent spread trades from ECTRIC to ENA</subject><text><sentence id="ECT053_024">Tanya:  Apparantly, Presidents &amp; Fellows of Harvard wants to trade on EOL.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_025">They were given a long-term guest ID that has since been closed out.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_026">However, they still want to do these Brent deals and have them booked back-to-back so that they are under the ISDA with ENA.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_027">Two things:  1) We do not show the ISDA in CAS ?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_028">$20MM Threshold ?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_029">Executed as of 11/20/00 2) Shouldn't the Brent deals that were booked back-to-back with ECTRIC be showing up in CAS, given that the purpose of this action was to bring the exposure under the ISDA?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_030">?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_031">Deal #s: QP4223 and VA0834  Are we still ok with doing this back-to-back booking?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_032">Also, how do we feel about this entity trading Metals (or should they even be trading Metals)?
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_033">The below email is from Rod to Sara in relationship to this whole issue.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_034">I will be out tomorrow, but I told Sara today that I would be running this by you to see what your thoughts were on the issue.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_035">Thanks for your help!
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_036">Would you let me know of the outcome.
</sentence><signature>Regards, Wendi LeBrocq 3-3835 </signature></text></email><email order="5"><date> Thu, 20 Sep 2001 11:34:52 -0700 (PDT)</date><from>X- Rohauer, Tanya &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=TROHAUE</from><to>X- Shackleton, Sara &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Sshackl, Williams, Jason R (Credit) &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=Jwilli10, Nelson, Roderick &lt;/O=ENRON/OU=NA/CN=RECIPIENTS/CN=EU/cn=Recipients/cn=rnelson</to><subject> FW: Assignment of crude/Brent spread trades from ECTRIC to ENA</subject><text><sentence id="ECT053_037">Problem is that if Harvard does a deal with ENA and ENA back-to-backs it withe ECTRIC, we lose it from an exposure perspective.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_038">ENA probably never records the deal since it has a closed position.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_039">Then ECTRIC thinks it has a position with ENA so we lose the third party exposure.
</sentence><sentence id="ECT053_040">The simple answer, I think, is if they want to trade Brent on EOL, then they probably need an ECTRIC ISDA since ENA cannot trade Brent on EOL, right?
</sentence><signature>Tanya </signature></text></email></thread></root>
