<root><thread><filename>APT014.txt</filename><name> check this
</name><id>APT014</id><email id="1"><date> Fri, Jan 28, 2011 at 1:20 PM
</date><from> suj &lt;suj@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;, sus &lt;sus@gmail.com&gt;, sau &lt;sau@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> check this
</subject><text><sentence id="APT014_001">http://www.nature.com/naturejobs/2011/110127/full/nj7331-570a.html
</sentence><sentence id="dummy"></sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="2"><date> Sat, Jan 29, 2011 at 11:53 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> check this
</subject><text><sentence id="APT014_002">I do agree that students need to be proactive and think outside the box asap after entering the grad program, but I also think that initially the advisor can at least smooth the relationship by looking into what the student needs.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_003">Since each student is different, they need different amounts of mentoring.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_004">Sometimes, even students themselves are not sure what exactly they want, and can't articulate their need.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_005">In such cases, it will always do good to an advisor to start an open and friendly communication from the very beginning.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_006">If the student feels confident about his/her advisor, (s)he will start sharing many details that otherwise would have been very hard to find.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_007">And open+serious communication can win any beginning grad student, and make him/her feel confident.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_008">Once the advisor has gleaned enough details about a student, he should think about how he can use those details to guide the student towards his/her degree.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_009">I think there should be three key steps in advising:
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_010">(a) Spoonfeeding (initial stage - for one year - (un)necessary courses, candidacy, paper discussion and understanding, mutual agreement and "coming to the same page", teamwork (start building collaborative teams))
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_011">(b) Teaching (middle stage - teaching the "tricks of the trade" - research topics, browsing, focusing, writing, communicating ideas, doing research, preserving and respecting copyright, no plagiarism, critical thinking, brainstorming, teamwork - for two/three years - leading to comprehensive)
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_012">(c) Fading (gradually moving away from the student giving him more freedom and less guidance - just "tuning here and there" - for the last one/two years - culminating in the thesis)
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_013">Of course, not all advisors are the same and we can't expect them to be psychologists, but I think instead of focusing on grad students only, there should be courses on improving advising style (like courses on improving public speaking) that actually help you become a better advisor.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="3"><date> Sat, Jan 29, 2011 at 11:57 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> check this
</subject><text><sentence id="APT014_014">The other thing that every advisor should keep in mind is that an advisor is also a teacher.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_015">He is helping students learn something.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_016">So the advising should be tuned according to the student's expectations, aspirations and psychological bent.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_017">For example, for a grad student who is more motivated by industry research than by academia, the advisor should stress the pros and cons of industry houses rather than academia examples.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="4"><date> Sat, Jan 29, 2011 at 7:20 PM
</date><from> suj &lt;suj@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> check this
</subject><text><sentence id="APT014_018">Just caught up with this e-mail.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_019">I think we had a similar mail exchange several months back.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_020">And what you are saying is the "ideal" situation
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_021">Mike. While I do agree with all of it, since our case is far from ideal and we have no hopes from our advisors, we can only look elsewhere, try to be as proactive as possible and get out as soon aswe can.
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_022">Sad but true!
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="5"><date> Sun, Jan 30, 2011 at 11:09 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> check this
</subject><text><sentence id="APT014_023">Yes, it's unfortunate but true. :-(
</sentence><sentence id="APT014_024">The only reason I keep stressing on the "ideal" is that one day we might be advisors, so our students will also expect ideal behavior.
</sentence><signature>Mike </signature></text></email></thread></root>
