<root><thread><filename>APT018.txt</filename><name>
</name><id>APT018</id><email id="1"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 2:33 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sum &lt;su@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_001">Sumit,
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_002">Finally Mitraji agreed not to submit the draft to ECIR.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_003">Instead he asked me to submit it, with classification experiments, to IJCAI as a full paper.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_004">This is kind of a battle won, because last night there was a small drama before he let me know his decision. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_005">He called me at 1:45 AM at night and kind of rebuked me hard that I'm just dodging his commands and working on my own whims.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_006">If I want to continue my funding, then I should obey whatever he asks.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_007">The chastising continued for about 10 minutes, after which he kind of subsided, and asked me to submit a full paper to ECIR.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_008">I was kind of enjoying his rebukes, though, because at least he was concerned enough to call me up at night.   :-D
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_009">The reason he called was that on Thursday he told me to send one version everyday, so that he can edit them asap and send back.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_010">But I couldn't send anything on Thursday because of Dan's course talk.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_011">Instead, I sent the modified Introduction section Friday night.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_012">Now, this modified Intro section I wrote with the view of ECIR short paper, so it was only 1 page long.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_013">He was suddenly infuriated at having received only a one-page draft and nothing else.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_014">So he called me up.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_015">Today I checked the mail.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_016">Looks like he went through my one-page condensed Intro section, and was finally convinced that the material was not suitable for ECIR.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_017">He mentioned that I should finish the classification experiments before I submit, so ECIR is not possible.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_018">Instead, submit to IJCAI because that is broader in interest and there is some time.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_019">He sent this mail half an hour later, at 2:27 AM. I was kind of amused and pleasantly surprised, because it is usually very hard to convince Mitraji, but looks like at least in this case, finally he convinced himself.  :-P  :-D 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_020">But the amusing thing is he put the blame totally on me.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_021">He kind of mentioned that it would have been good for ecir, but only because of my worthless dilly-dallying of the matter, we couldn't submit.  :-) :-)
</sentence><signature>Regards, Mike </signature></text></email><email id="2"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 2:36 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_022">Hi Sujatha,
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_023">Finally Mitraji agreed not to submit the draft to ECIR.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_024">Instead he asked me to submit it, with sentence classification experiments, to IJCAI as a full paper.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="3"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 3:03 PM
</date><from> suj &lt;suj@hotmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_025">Hi Mike,
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_026">This is very upsetting. I am shocked.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_027">First, at the outrageous way he rebuked you at 1.45AM.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_028">If it was work for some paper deadline may be but only to scold you?
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_029">One hardly expects this from a professor.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_030">Second, it is ridiculous to think that your paper is a good fit for ECIR and the only reason you cannot submit is because you were not working and not because he did not read your manuscript even a month after you sent it.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_031">I think he never heard of "people in glass houses should not throw stones".
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_032">Third, I think it is paltry that he should keep using the funding threat anytime he wants to exert authority.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_033">If someone earns my respect I have no problems subjecting myself to authority but using the same threat every single time?
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_034">Doesn't he tire of it?
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_035">I suspect that though he keeps saying "Dr. Giles" in my case, it is more of his method to torture students.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_036">I never got to ask you whether you discussed the Prof Xiaofeng(?)'s comments with him.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_037">I don't know about IJCAI but his idea about ACL seems like a more suitable and reasonable one to me.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_038">I don't know how you managed to remain so calm and actually did not mind the unreasonable chastising in the middle of the night.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_039">Don't you think we deserve better? I wish things were better .
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_040">I am willing to try making it on my own probably with somebody's help like Dan's or like you suggested clubbing up with others but I wish I could tell them "if you cannot encourage or help me atleast do not demotivate me or tell me that I am loser".
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="4"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 3:52 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_041">You know what, well, he at least called me up.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_042">That means he was concerned about me.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_043">True, I hate the way he handles students, or research, in general, but still I noticed that as a person or human being, he might not be that bad.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_044">Even with Dr Giles, I think this is true.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_045">The main problem with them is they are both very complacent and egotistic.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_046">But it's also true that without Dr Giles' recommendation, NEC thing would not have happened.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_047">I have seen how happy Dr Giles was when Jian Huang graduated.  It's the sign of a paternal heart.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_048">A stone-hearted person wouldn't have cared.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_049">I am not saying that these things should make us lick their boots, but what let me remain calm, was the consideration that well, at least he cares about what I sent him.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_050">My mom's advisor did not even want to sign the final draft of her thesis, so definitely Mitraji or even Dr Giles is much better than that.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_051">I know why you are angry.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_052">But remember that nobody is perfect.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_053">And you can't expect people to work the way you want them to.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_054">So the best way is just to try to be friendly with them as far as possible, not lose your calm and your originality and freshness of mind even in the midst of problems, and also, to pray sometimes for salvation and love (which I'm sure you do :-) ).
</sentence><signature>Regards, Mike </signature></text></email><email id="5"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 4:01 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_055">Also, I talked to him regarding Xiaofei Lu's comments and advice, but he was not very impressed I guess.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_056">I think he didn't like the idea of short papers.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_057">Be it ACL or IJCAI, he wants a full paper.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_058">IJCAI is at least broader than ECIR, so the classification part can be submitted there, while the rest (i.e., the work in the writeup) can be submitted to ACL as short paper.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="6"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 4:04 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> suj &lt;suj@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_059">But don't worry about it.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_060">Something will be done.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_061">At least I won't have to rush for ecir right now, so I'll have some more time.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_062">I'll talk to Xiaofei this week regarding a work plan and what we can do within December.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_063">This time I am feeling a new surge of hope, so let's see what happens.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_064">I wish the same for your NEC work as well.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_065">You also have two months to prove yourself.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_066">These are trying times, but if you can tear through it, there isn't a bigger satisfaction.
</sentence><signature>Mike </signature></text></email><email id="7"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 4:26 PM
</date><from> suj &lt;suj@hotmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_067">Thanks Mike,
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_068">I am glad that you are able to look at all this in such positive light.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_069">I know that Dr. Mitra is very good as a person.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_070">I don't really expect him to behave the way I like but I think he is not willing to be the better person he can be if he wants.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_071">And I know both of them care somewhat about our own ambitions but do not care enough to actually help us out despite being our advisors.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_072">I have noticed that both Dr. Mitra and Dr. Giles don't give any reasonable advice at the same time are not very appreciative of other professors comments.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_073">Remember Dr. Giles' comments when Dr Faloutsos visited.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_074">I remember Dr. Mitra also was like well I told you so types when I was trying to explain what Dr. Kifer went deep and explained to me.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_075">But you are right. If we can get through these trying times, it is like we can face just about anything. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_076">Now that we are already in the water, the only ay out is to figure out how to swim :). 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_077">Hope Yanjun(NEC) and Prof. Xiaofei will help both of us through this period.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_078">So "NO QUITTING, we do not quit" :)
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="8"><date> Sat, Oct 9, 2010 at 11:25 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sum &lt;su@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_079">Sumit,
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_080">I was in a bong meeting, so could not receive your call.  :-P
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_081">Now I'm back home.
</sentence><signature>Mike </signature></text></email><email id="9"><date> Sun, Oct 10, 2010 at 12:09 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sum &lt;su@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_082">Checked my psu mail just now.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_083">Xiaofei Lu has replied after reading my writeup.  :-) :-)
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_084">It is a very detailed, minute and constructive review.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_085">The email is really big and covers lots of points and insight, so I think I'll read it tomorrow with fresh mind.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_086">He suggested several pointers and improvements, and at the same time, reorganized the whole material into seven different sections.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_087">Looks like he read the technical part really well, because he was able to point out several strengths and weaknesses.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_088">And finally, he's kind of positive that it should go to acl as short paper.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_089">So maybe, as you said, the classification expt can be put into ijcai 6-page, and this one as acl short paper.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_090">But what Xiaofei really wanted is to put this one + classification expt together as one acl short.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_091">So just see his notion of quality.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_092">But let's see what happens.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="10"><date> Sun, Oct 10, 2010 at 12:51 AM
</date><from> sum &lt;su@hotmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_093">That is great Mike :) 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_094">Finally, World is making sense again.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_095">Can you please forward me his mail? 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_096">How long is ACL short paper?
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_097">I think we have no option but to submit something to IJCAI to pacify Mitraji. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_098">See, IJCAI is due in Jan 3rd week and ACL short paper after that. After my WWW submission, I will also have more time.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_099">So, we can do sufficient stuff for both classification (IJCAI-6 papers) and linguistic related stuff for ACL.
</sentence><sentence id="APT018_100">I am not going India this December, so that also provides us more time.
</sentence><signature>Sumit </signature></text></email><email id="11"><date> Sun, Oct 10, 2010 at 2:21 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sum &lt;su@hotmail.com&gt;
</to><subject>
</subject><text><sentence id="APT018_101">yes, I'm also not going this December.  :)</sentence><sentence id="dummy"></sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
