<root><thread><filename>APT002.txt</filename><name> update
</name><id>APT002</id><email id="1"><date> Wed, Dec 21, 2011 at 8:29 PM
</date><from> Chi&lt;c@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> X &lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_001">Dear Prof Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_002">Hope you are doing great. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_003">I got PhD admission from two universities - U Texas Dallas and Illinois Institute of Technology. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_004">But they didn't mention funding. Right now, I'm waiting for a few more schools to turn up, and also mailing the faculty members for support.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_005">Unfortunately, my political science funding from Prof Burt Monroe has expired - so in Spring, I have no appointment. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_006">I have applied to TLT for an assistantship and also a few other places, but I'm not sure.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_007">Spring is probably the last sem I'll need funding for.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_008">Could you please let me know in case you have support for one semester (tuition+stipend) or if anybody you know has some support?
</sentence><signature>Thank you very much and sincere regards, Chi </signature></text></email><email id="2"><date> Tue, Dec 27, 2011 at 11:29 AM
</date><from> X&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_009">Hi Chi,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_010">Great to hear the positive news.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_011">It's still early and I'm sure you'll hear positive news from more universities within the next 2 months.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_012">Unfortunately I do not have any support for next semester.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_013">I hope you will be able to figure something out.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_014">Wish you a productive and fruitful year ahead.
</sentence><signature>Xi </signature></text></email><email id="3"><date> Tue, Dec 27, 2011 at 9:19 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_015">Thank you very much, Prof Lu. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_016">I'll keep you updated on the applications.
</sentence><signature>Regards, chi </signature></text></email><email id="4"><date> Thu, Mar 1, 2012 at 1:43 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_017">Dear Prof Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_018">I got admission from U of North Texas, Florida International University, and U Illinois Chicago, in addition to Illinois Institute of Technology, and U Texas Dallas. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_019">Among these five, I was offered funding from U North Texas (UNT), U Illinois Chicago, and U Texas Dallas.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_020">I'll probably join UNT this fall under Prof Rada Mihalcea.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_021">This spring and summer I got funding from Architectural Engineering department (Prof Richard Mistrick).
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_022">This is java programming and debugging of a large software project.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_023">So far I like this work. :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_024">I'm visiting UNT as a prospective grad student in spring break (March 2 - March 4).
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_025">Thank you very much for your kind help, support and appreciation.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_026">I can never repay my debt to you.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_027">I'd need another letter of recommendation from you. :P :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_028">This is for UNT. The addressees are:
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_029">Stephanie Deacon &lt;Stephanie.Deacon@unt.edu&gt;, Bill Buckles &lt;Bill.Buckles@unt.edu&gt;
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_030">(UNT Computer Science and Engineering)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_031">They will accept MS Word or PDF letters as email attachment.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_032">The admission decision cannot be finalized before they receive the recos.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_033">Thank you very much again, and wish you a very happy Spring Break.
</sentence><signature>Best, chi </signature></text></email><email id="5"><date> Thu, Mar 1, 2012 at 2:03 PM
</date><from> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_034">Dear chi,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_035">Congratulations on your success. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_036">UNT will be a great choice. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_037">I've just sent them a letter.
</sentence><signature>Best, Xi </signature></text></email><email id="6"><date> Thu, Mar 1, 2012 at 2:57 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_038">Thank you very much, Prof Lu.
</sentence><sentence id="dummy"></sentence><signature>Regards, chi </signature></text></email><email id="7"><date> Thu, Mar 1, 2012 at 3:08 PM
</date><from> D&lt;de@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_039">Dear Dr. Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_040">I thank you for submitting your letter of recommendation for chi. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_041">I will gladly place this in his application packet.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_042">Again, I thank you for your prompt response!
</sentence><signature>Kind regards, Stephanie </signature></text></email><email id="8"><date> Fri, Mar 16, 2012 at 1:20 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_043">Dear Prof Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_044">I got teaching assistantship at UNT for 2012-2013.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_045">My visit to UNT was also successful, and I talked to Prof Rada Mihalcea on the formality problem.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_046">She was really interested, and said it would be a nice idea to pursue.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_047">Texas is pretty hot in summer, but otherwise fine. Prof Mihalcea said she thought you were my PhD advisor, and she probably met you in a conference/seminar earlier.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_048">Thank you very much for your kind support and wishes. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_049">I'll keep you updated on any news.
</sentence><signature>Regards, chi </signature></text></email><email id="9"><date> Fri, Mar 16, 2012 at 1:26 PM
</date><from> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_050">Great. I co-organized a workshop at NAACL 2007 in Rochester, and we invited her to give a plenary at the workshop. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_051">She is amazingly productive, and it would be great if you could work with her.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="10"><date> Thu, May 3, 2012 at 11:02 AM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_052">Dear Prof Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_053">I have converted from PhD to Masters, and will graduate with a non-thesis Masters from PSU in summer.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_054">Moving to UNT in August (August 5 starting from SCE - reaching TX Aug 7). I'll be driving to TX - hope that's going to be exciting. :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_055">I have been offered an additional GATS scholarship by the CSE department at UNT.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_056">This was in addition to the teaching assistantship.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_057">In the meantime, I couldn't yet look into the formality problem and extension to implicature score as we discussed.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_058">I'll probably not be able to do anything on this line before reaching UNT, because in the summer, I'm funded by a professor in Architecture Engineering Department, so I have to work for him.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_059">Once at UNT, I'll try to secure an independent study (3 credits) under Prof Mihalcea.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_060">If it works out, then I'll start discussing with you again on the implicature score.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_061">I have some more ideas from complex network theory that can be applied to this issue, but I need to read more on that.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_062">I took a course last semester in complex networks - it's helping a lot.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_063">Looks like there are many aspects of style (e.g. coherence, cohesion, syntactic variations, etc) that are closely linked with networks of words and their properties - it might be clustering coefficient, betweenness centrality, pagerank or degree distribution of a network.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_064">And also, there is a lot of work along this line to begin with. So I was just wondering if there could be a relation between word networks and implicature as well - I conceived some ideas. But I'll explore more on this after summer.
</sentence><signature>Hope you are doing well, and best regards, chi </signature></text></email><email id="11"><date> Thu, May 3, 2012 at 8:20 PM
</date><from> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_065">Hi chi,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_066">Thanks for the update. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_067">I'm glad to hear that everything is going well, and I'm sure you'll do we at UNT.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_068">I'd also certainly be happy to continue our discussion on style, as your research on that front continues. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_069">I'm spending May and June in China this year, and it has been fun.
</sentence><signature>Best, Xiaofei Lu </signature></text></email><email id="12"><date> Fri, May 4, 2012 at 9:05 AM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_070">Yes, I'm sure the weather is now really awesome there !! :-) :-) :-)
</sentence><sentence id="dummy"></sentence><signature>Thanks, and have a nice holiday, chi </signature></text></email><email id="13"><date> Mon, Jul 9, 2012 at 4:41 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_071">Dear Prof Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_072">Hope you had a nice holiday in China with your family. :)  
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_073">Are you back at PSU ?  
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_074">I was wondering if we could meet and discuss on the implicature score, especially previous work and data.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_075">If you are in State College, could you please give me some time this week ?
</sentence><signature>Thanks and regards, chi </signature></text></email><email id="14"><date> Mon, Jul 9, 2012 at 5:54 PM
</date><from> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_076">Hi chi,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_077">Yes, we had a good vacation in China.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_078">What about this Wednesday either 10:30-11:30am or 1:30-2:30pm? 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_079">I will have a meeting from 12-1pm on that day.
</sentence><signature>Best, Xiaofei Lu </signature></text></email><email id="15"><date> Mon, Jul 9, 2012 at 7:57 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_080">Prof Lu, I'll meet you at 1:30 on Wednesday.
</sentence><sentence id="dummy"></sentence><signature>Thanks and regards, chi </signature></text></email><email id="16"><date> Mon, Aug 20, 2012 at 4:02 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_081">Dear Prof Lu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_082">I have arrived at UNT, and now kind of settled.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_083">Here it's really hot in the noon, but gets cooler during afternoon and evening.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_084">The 1300-mile drive from PA to TX was amazing too. :) :) 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_085">Fortunately, my car didn't go wrong.  :) :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_086">I'll always remember this trip :) 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_087">It's like you start with the mountains in PA and WV - cross the wild, wild WV - to enter rolling meadows of KY and TN, and then cross the Mississippi to AR.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_088">I think I also crossed Tennessee river somewhere in TN, and Arkansas river near Little Rock, AR. It was truly amazing :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_089">Here I talked to Rada. She is great :) :) 
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_090">I had a very productive meeting with her.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_091">She also invited me to a dinner party in honor of one of her students graduating and getting a job.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_092">There I met most of her students and their family, plus two faculty members and their family.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_093">We spent a nice evening there.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_094">Regarding research, Rada is flexible but she'd rather want me work on authorship attribution using complex networks.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_095">So I did not start anything on the Implicature and Formality scoring yet.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_096">I'm looking for some undergrad students here (or in my college in India) so that they can help me out on the formality problem and I can concentrate more on the problem with Rada.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_097">I'll keep you informed on this.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_098">I'm a TA for this year, and will be taking three courses in Fall, as follows:
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_099">NLP (under a new faculty, Rodney Nielsen (he's from UColorado Boulder))
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_100">Rada's NLP Seminar
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_101">Game Design (under Prof Ian Parberry) - I wanted to take this course because I have a plan on designing a game on getting labeled text data
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_102">I'll still have to figure out who to approach for inviting a guest speaker.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_103">I'd really like you to visit here :) :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_104">I like TX much more than PA.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_105">It might be hot, but it's very beautiful and vibrant :) :)
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_106">Hope you are doing well with your family. :)
</sentence><signature>Best regards, C </signature></text></email><email id="17"><date> Mon, Aug 20, 2012 at 5:59 PM
</date><from> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_107">Hi chi,
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_108">Great to hear that you had an exciting and safe trip and that you like it down there.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_109">I'm sure you'll do well.
</sentence><sentence id="APT002_110">I'm not sure I have something interesting enough for a CSE audience at the moment, so don't worry about that for a while. The fall semester will be a busy semester for me, but hopefully I'll survive everything.
</sentence><signature>Best, Xiaofei Lu </signature></text></email><email id="18"><date> Mon, Aug 20, 2012 at 6:21 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> xi&lt;x@xxx.edu&gt;
</to><subject> RE: update
</subject><text><sentence id="APT002_111">ok, I'll keep you posted.
</sentence><sentence id="dummy"></sentence><signature>Thanks and regards, chi</signature></text></email></thread></root>
