<root><thread><filename>APT003.txt</filename><name> how r u?
</name><id>APT003</id><email id="1"><date> Wed, Feb 9, 2011 at 1:36 PM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> le &lt;ll@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how r u?
</subject><text><sentence id="APT003_001">Hi Lei,
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_002">How are you? Haven't heard from you in a while. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_003">I guess you went back to China already. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_004">How are things working out?
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_005">We are ok here, and Sujatha has got back to NEC. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_006">She will be there till March. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_007">I am working on a problem with Partha.
</sentence><signature>Best, Shibu </signature></text></email><email id="2"><date> Wed, Feb 9, 2011 at 7:45 PM
</date><from> le &lt;ll@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how r u?
</subject><text><sentence id="APT003_008">Hey Shibu,
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_009">I am in Beijing now living in my friend's dorm and looking for a room to stay.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_010">We just had our lunar new year festival, so I went back home last several days and spent time with my parents.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_011">I didn't have much time living with my parents since I have sth else to do here.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_012">I am getting busy. What I am doing is related to economics and I am trying to find research idea in it.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_013">Also I am happy to get in contact with my old labmates again and I can also do some study with them. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_014">And for you to know, I sold my malibu, and subleased my room in parkway.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_015">I am hoping that I can do sth in the next 6 months, maybe submit a couple of papers, then I can go back to penn state to have my comprehensive exam expectedly in August or September.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_016">After all these years living in the US, I found that now it doesn't really matter to me where I live, I will just live where I can find more friends and have somereal stuff to do. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_017">Isn't it also interesting to move to another country/city once in a while and enjoy your life there?
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_018">Let me know if you have plans going back Asia, you can stop by Beijing and we can meet here :-) also if there is any change in penn state, please get me updated.
</sentence><signature>See you! Leilei </signature></text></email><email id="3"><date> Thu, Feb 10, 2011 at 11:48 AM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> le &lt;ll@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how r u?
</subject><text><sentence id="APT003_019">Yes, you are right. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_020">I'll definitely let you know if I go to Beijing/ China. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_021">It's good that you spent some time with your family. :-)
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_022">Here I and Partha are working on some problems related to multi-agent systems, game theory and clustering.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_023">Now hopefully things will work out, because Partha is a very good friend as well as a great collaborator.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_024">I wish and hope things will work out very good on your part as well.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_025">Just one thing to let you know.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_026">I am going to Tokyo on Feb 19 for a conference (CICLING 2011), and will be coming back on Feb 27.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_027">I had a paper accepted there. Right now I've couple more papers in submission - one with Partha to IJCAI, another short paper to JCDL.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_028">I had to argue really hard with Dr Mitra to make him understand what I'm going to submit, where and why.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_029">Finally he admitted what I was doing, although not fully convinced.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_030">In any case, I am funding my trip to Tokyo, not Dr Mitra, so I don't think he can say anything much about it.
</sentence><signature>Best, Shibu </signature></text></email><email id="4"><date> Thu, Feb 10, 2011 at 11:58 AM
</date><from> s&lt;s@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> le &lt;ll@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how r u?
</subject><text><sentence id="APT003_031">For the Greek project, I am collaborating with Dr Zoe Stamatopoulou.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_032">She is a faculty in classics department, and knows both Ancient and Modern Greek really well.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_033">She took a lot of interest in the project, and is advising me on its key aspects and research issues.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_034">And for my colloquialism (formality-informality) problem, I am collaborating with an applied linguist at PSU, Dr Xiaofei Lu.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_035">He is a really nice person and advises so well.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_036">I am taking a corpus analysis course under him in this semester.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_037">In that course, he is teaching us Awk and Python.
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_038">So, finally, I'm also learning Python and I'm loving it!   :-) :-)  
</sentence><sentence id="APT003_039">Partha also took this course with me, and he has also fallen in love with Python.  :-) :-)
</sentence><signature>Wish you all the best in life. Shibu P.S. - Good timber does not grow with ease: The stronger the wind, the stronger the trees; The further the sky, the greater the length; The more the storm, the more the strength. - Douglas Malloch</signature></text></email></thread></root>
