<root><thread><filename>APT015.txt</filename><name> How Are You :-)
</name><id>APT015</id><email id="1"><date> Thu, Aug 4, 2011 at 4:51 PM
</date><from> sum &lt;sum@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> How Are You :-)
</subject><text><sentence id="APT015_001">Hi Mike,
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_002">How are you?
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_003">How is everything going?
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_004">Is your internship over or are you still there? How did your work go?
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_005">I was at SIGIR last week and probably had most intellectually satisfying one week of my PhD.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_006">Met some great people and had some great discussions.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_007">Needless to say, discussions there were much more useful than with our "advisor" in past three years.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_008">Even though the discussions will not help me solve problems I want to address but still, people tried to understand what I was saying and gave some really good suggestions.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_009">I also feel kind of depressed given our miserable state.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_010">Mitraji is coming to Almaden next week as a self invited visitor.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_011">I asked him if we can visit some of his friends in search companies in valley to see if we can get some data.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_012">He said, "Sure, who do you like to meet?"  I was like, "Okay, let us try to meet Lary Page and Sergey Brin".
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_013">I mean WTF? I don't know who your friends are. I asked him if he knows anyone who works in related areas and then, as usual, no reply.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_014">And here at IBM, these people are doing jugaad pe jugaad....they are like an ass's asshole. No chance of a paper whatsoever.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_015">Forget the paper, no chance of any useful work :P
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_016">Totally frustrated and want to go back to India :( :( :( :) :) ;)
</sentence><signature>Sum </signature></text></email><email id="2"><date> Fri, Aug 5, 2011 at 10:42 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sum &lt;sum@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> How Are You :-)
</subject><text><sentence id="APT015_017">It's ok.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_018">Just one more week left, then I'm done.  :-) :-) :-)
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_019">I don't think the work was any good, but well, at least I got some money. :P :D
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_020">Nice to hear about your SIGIR experience.  :-) :-) :-)
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_021">Yes, it is really those kind of people you want to network with, not like Mitra ji.  :P :D
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_022">Don't worry about Mitra ji's friends.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_023">He has none.  :P :D
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_024">Unfortunate, but true.  :P
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_025">And don't worry about internship work, either.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_026">Usually it's all jugaad, nothing else.  :P :P
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_027">Don't be frustrated.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_028">Go and visit different places if you can.  :-) :-) :-) :-)
</sentence><signature>Mike </signature></text></email><email id="3"><date> Fri, Aug 5, 2011 at 10:49 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sum &lt;sum@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> How Are You :-)
</subject><text><sentence id="APT015_029">The only way to end this impasse is to do Masters here and apply to other places (e.g., under Bruce Croft).
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_030">Now you have a very good chance that you'll be accepted.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_031">Then only you can get a solution.
</sentence><sentence id="APT015_032">But the problem is it will take 4 more years, so it is a life-turning decision I feel somewhat shaky to make.
</sentence><signature>Best, Mike </signature></text></email></thread></root>
