<root><thread><filename>APT010.txt</filename><name> how are you
</name><id>APT010</id><email id="1"><date> Sat, Aug 21, 2010 at 12:09 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_001">Hey Sujatha,
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_002">How are you doing ?  :-)  :-)
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_003">I have reached SCE yesterday. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_004">Did Mitra ji contact you ? 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_005">Also, what about Saumen?
</sentence><signature>Regards, Mike </signature></text></email><email id="2"><date> Sun, Aug 22, 2010 at 1:27 AM
</date><from> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_006">Hi Mike,
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_007">Oh tum wapas chale gaye.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_008">How does it feel to be back???
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_009">I finished my internship on Friday.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_010">I am not in a good state.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_011">I had lengthy chats with both Dr. Mitra and Dr. Giles.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_012">Both of them totally think
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_013">that I dont seem to take my PhD seriously and Mitraji even suggested that I should consider leaving with a masters.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_014">I tried to tell them I will try extra hard this semester and make things works.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_015">I have applied for leave of absence for next semester but there seem to be some serious visa
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_016">issues since a leave would invalidate my F1 state. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_017">So I am kind of trying to sort things on this front.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_018">That's abt it. Visiting my sister in Pune at the moment. More later.
</sentence><signature>-sujatha </signature></text></email><email id="3"><date> Sun, Aug 22, 2010 at 1:50 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_019">Did you have a chat with Saumen yet ?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_020">Did he suggest anything ?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_021">Also, please let me know your phone no.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_022">I didn't take it with me when I came back to SCE.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_023">Dr Mitra gave me one last chance of survival for this semester.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_024">I had sent one writeup which apparently satisfied him, albeit for a moment.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_025">I don't know what lies ahead, but I'll have to try my best. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_026">Could you do me a favor ?  
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_027">Please review the writeup once and let me know if anything makes sense.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_028">Find attached the writeup.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_029">Hope everything works out.  Let me know your number.
</sentence><signature>Mike </signature></text></email><email id="4"><date> Mon, Aug 23, 2010 at 3:36 AM
</date><from> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_030">hey Mike,
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_031">I am traveling, so will look at this as soon as I get a chance and let you know.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_032">My Phone number at Hyderabad: 040-27220775, 810-609-0460
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_033">Didnt talk to Prof Soumen yet but more on phone.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, Sujatha </signature></text></email><email id="5"><date> Mon, Aug 23, 2010 at 2:13 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_034">ok, just a few more thoughts:
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_035">1&gt;  Just give this a try.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_036">Write up whatever you have done (kind of a summary of your research findings, include any and every thing).
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_037">Then try to convince Dr Mitra and Dr Giles to either submit it as a technical report in CSE department, or as a technical report in ArXiv.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_038">Contact CSE dean if you need any mediation.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_039">Nobody can actually prevent you from submitting your research finding as a tech report.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_040">The good thing about ArXiv is that its publications are not peer-reviewed, but they are GoogleScholar-indexed, unlike normal technical reports.  So you can mention ArXiv submissions on your resume as well.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_041">Then try to use this tech report as a means of securing funding.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_042">2&gt;  Leilei told me today that there are several other funding opportunities at PSU.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_043">For example, Haibin did some web server maintenance-related stuff.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_044">Many Chinese IST students don't get a TA because they don't pass the English exam in first semester.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_045">So they look for outside jobs.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_046">For more details and info regarding this, contact Leilei ( 814-206-4539 ).
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_047">Finally, don't lose hope.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_048">Difficult times do come in life, but they are never insurmountable.
</sentence><signature>Take care, Mike </signature></text></email><email id="6"><date> Mon, Aug 23, 2010 at 2:49 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_049">Also check your cse mail.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_050">There are several job-related mails.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_051">For example, today there was a mail that they need a grader for CMPSC 455 and CMPSC 221.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_052">Keep checking these.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="7"><date> Tue, Aug 24, 2010 at 1:48 AM
</date><from> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_053">Dear Mike,
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_054">I really appreciate your mails and your words of encouragement.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_055">I recollect the time you helped me out while studying for candidacies.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_056">I need some advice here:
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_057">Basically IBM IRL is willing to take me on for an internship in Fall.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_058">I told them about my fix, finding a phd problem etc and the person I spoke to thought we could try to find  a problem which Dr. Mitra could be interested in too.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_059">There seem to be some wage-payroll positions which can give me a stipend but wont pay for the tuition and since I have not done my comprehensive I have to registered for 9 credits.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_060">This is the whole problem in trying other options.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_061">When Sumit was here, he suggested that  i take up the internship since atleast i wont have to spend time on something arbitrary like grading or programming and can instead focus on research problems although I am away from campus.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_062">Since we cannot expect any advice from dr. mitra and in turn might waste too much time doing something random in the name of RA i thought may be this is a better option. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_063">It is slightly upsetting since I was hoping to be on campus and do some good courses and get on with research. But after some thought this IRL thing does not sound bad either. What do you think?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_064">Let me know if you get a chance.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_065">I could use some direction.
</sentence><signature>Thanks, -Sujatha </signature></text></email><email id="8"><date> Tue, Aug 24, 2010 at 7:59 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_066">ok, I think IRL is fine. 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_067">But make sure two things:
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_068">1&gt; The funding is ensured.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_069">2&gt; When you are in IRL, they might want you to do "their" tasks. Make sure these tasks involve research and publication.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_070">Push hard for publication from the very beginning.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_071">Remember, nobody will do anything unless you push them hard.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_072">People are too fallible.  Just start pushing from today.  :-) :-) 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_073">And never, ever stop pushing people in research.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_074">By pushing, What I mean is send them mails at least once a day.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_075">By doing this, they will not be able to shake you off.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="9"><date> Tue, Aug 24, 2010 at 8:28 AM
</date><from> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_076">thanks Mike, i will try to see IRL meets the "demands".
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_077">i need another favor from you, could you perhaps help?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_078">I need some info from karen.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_079">Calling from here is turning out to be v. expensive and moreover she seems busy with the new students and hence not responding to my email.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_080">Basically last week i had sent her my "leave of absence" email.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_081">You can mention my name to her and say you are asking all these questions for me.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_082">I want to know the following:
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_083">-Can I revoke the "leave of absence" now by registering for courses?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_084">-Can I do an internship that involves registering for one credit for next semester thereby avoiding "leave of absence"?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_085">-if yes, since the internship is in India what are the procedures I must take care of?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_086">-any other todos with the international students office ?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_087">could you do this today?
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_088">I really need to make some decision w.r.t. my travel next week, so i will be v. relieved to get the information as soon as possible.
</sentence><signature>thanks very much, -Sujatha </signature></text></email><email id="10"><date> Tue, Aug 24, 2010 at 1:01 PM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_089">I met Karen.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_090">She said that she didn't yet receive any paperwork from you regarding leave of absence.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_091">Karen suggested contacting Kern as well as Boucke to figure out what status you are in.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_092">Call them up right now.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_093">Yes, you can still register for courses, since it's only first week of class.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_094">For an internship, you need to register for one credit of CSE 596.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_095">For an internship in India, contact Boucke for the procedures.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="11"><date> Tue, Aug 24, 2010 at 10:24 PM
</date><from> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</from><to> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_096">Thanks a lot Mike for talking to Karen.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_097">I sent mails to ISS and Dr. Mitra yesterday but there is no response.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_098">I sent overall 3 emails to Karen re. leave of absence and I don't understand
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_099">what she means by paperwork. She herself told me that I could just send an email to her to initiate the process and then fill out an exit form on the ISS website.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_100">I will try calling all of these people today.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_101">Is Dr. Mitra not around? I sent a long mail explaining how things are and asking for advice and did not hear back from him either.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_102">Could you send me your phone number? 
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_103">Thanks again.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_104">I guess its better to come over as scheduled and sort these thing sout before taking a break again.
</sentence><signature></signature></text></email><email id="12"><date> Wed, Aug 25, 2010 at 7:44 AM
</date><from> s &lt;s@email.com&gt;
</from><to> sumi &lt;sm@gmail.com&gt;
</to><subject> how are you
</subject><text><sentence id="APT010_105">Dr Mitra is now here, so I think you'll get his reply.
</sentence><sentence id="APT010_106">My number is 814-321-7351.</sentence><signature></signature></text></email></thread></root>
